<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<STBLKeyStringList><Text Key="0198D4F5">Pick a Cause of Death!</Text><Text Key="027DBC04">The selected age group does not have this cause of death available and will be removed.</Text><Text Key="D3EBF2F3">The selected occult does not have this cause of death available and will be removed.</Text><Text Key="7DB8D41F">Caution</Text><Text Key="C21BEE42">Toggle Ghost Overlay On</Text><Text Key="8612535D">Toggle Ghost Overlay Off</Text><Text Key="E176A72D">Pick an Occult!</Text><Text Key="60235B2A">Dependent Sims must merge with an existing household.</Text><Text Key="380FD75A">Dependents must be placed in a household with a Teen or older.</Text><Text Key="379FD670">Please wait and try again as the Gnomes try to fix the failure.</Text><Text Key="29D07256">The Soul's Journey denotes the overall satisfaction of {0.SimFirstName}'s existence. Filling the Soul's Journey rewards {0.SimFirstName} with various perks to help them in life, death, and whatever comes afterward.\nSome things that increase the Soul's Journey are:\n\n• Completing Unfinished Business Goals\n• Completing Aspirations\n• Completing Wants</Text><Text Key="B47BC90B">The Soul's Journey denotes the overall satisfaction of {0.SimFirstName}'s existence. Filling the Soul's Journey rewards {0.SimFirstName} with various perks to help them in life, death, and whatever comes afterward.\nSome things that increase the Soul's Journey are:\n\n• Completing Bucket List Goals\n• Completing Aspirations\n• Completing Wants</Text><Text Key="5FFD1729">\n- Completing New Years Resolutions</Text><Text Key="60FD189C">\n- Completing a Midlife Crisis</Text><Text Key="9EAB8F69">Number of times this Sim has been Reborn.</Text><Text Key="AB92C97D">{0.SimFirstName} has completed {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} Soul's Journey and earned the Burning Soul Trait. Visit &lt;b&gt;Baleful Bog&lt;/b&gt; in the Mourningvale neighborhood of Ravenwood at any time to Rebirth!</Text><Text Key="1C232AA6">{0.SimFirstName}'s Unfinished Business</Text><Text Key="D1F10555">{0.SimFirstName} has completed {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} Soul's Journey as a living Sim, and can now choose to be reborn at the moment of death! More journey awaits {0.SimFirstName} after death, unlocking the true potential of Rebirth as well!</Text><Text Key="7E36FFEE">{0.SimFirstName}'s Bucket List</Text><Text Key="C4DA5CB1">Complete {0.String} quests to earn Event Points and unlock new rewards!</Text><Text Key="8731E3B0">Event Ends {0.DateLong}</Text><Text Key="CDE76091">This week's quest rewards</Text><Text Key="DCF8D304">Ends in</Text><Text Key="DDF770B9">{0.Number} Event Points Weekend!</Text><Text Key="C56DCB00">Hey! You have {0.Number} {S0.reward}{P0.rewards} waiting for you.</Text><Text Key="D6B9CA1B">This reward is claimable!</Text><Text Key="F2772205">This reward has been claimed!</Text><Text Key="C54EE355">You must be in Live Mode to claim this reward.</Text><Text Key="A8329DDF">Quest {0.Number}</Text><Text Key="8A722FF3">This reward is locked. Complete new {0.String} quests to earn more Event Points and claim it!</Text><Text Key="7F70255C">Complete {0.String} quests to earn Event Points to claim this reward!</Text><Text Key="B298297C">Unlocks Soon!</Text><Text Key="61C89DA8">{0.Number}</Text><Text Key="611BCB61">x{0.Number}</Text><Text Key="D20CDF34">OK</Text><Text Key="60850092">Please wait and try again as the Gnomes try to fix the failure.</Text><Text Key="18B6069E">Claim Failed</Text><Text Key="CD126443">Please go online to save your Event progress and receive rewards.</Text><Text Key="42F62F63">Online Connection is Required</Text><Text Key="23926F54">Unlocks:</Text><Text Key="082F7CB1">You have completed all of the quests in the {0.String} event!</Text><Text Key="CDBA4650">You've completed all of these quests. Keep going to unlock more rewards and check back for new quests!</Text><Text Key="4C2BFB24">Event Completed</Text><Text Key="FF510EDF">All Quests Completed</Text><Text Key="DE5AF16B">Discover winter traditions, collaborate with Jasmine Holiday, and earn Event Points for festive rewards!</Text><Text Key="B8957F90">Cozy Celebrations</Text><Text Key="5AD3A0C6">Reaper's Rewards</Text><Text Key="8905D078">Work alongside Grim to discover the secrets of Ambrosia, earn Event Points, and unlock bone-chilling rewards!</Text><Text Key="D2CC85AF">Blast from the Past</Text><Text Key="4C13AE4B">Help Emit unravel a mystery through time, earn Event Points, and unlock nostalgic rewards from the past!</Text><Text Key="5FEAFD84">Event Points Progress</Text><Text Key="B5F29902">Event ends {0.DateLong}, {0.TimeShort}.</Text><Text Key="A2A9A710">Complete!</Text><Text Key="0144F6C9">Next Reward</Text><Text Key="0634FB98">{0.Number} EP</Text><Text Key="7C9EF6A1">Level Up</Text><Text Key="C76753A3">{0.Number} / {1.Number}</Text><Text Key="5C64227D">EP Limit</Text><Text Key="E6B4B65E">Reward</Text><Text Key="CA26FB7E">Ends in</Text><Text Key="BA7D30FE">{0.Number} EP Period</Text><Text Key="7A964D28">Active Event Quests will be cleared and reset to the last known progression point.</Text><Text Key="261FAE3B">OK</Text><Text Key="1E8A5630">Error While Syncing Data with Server</Text><Text Key="2699D865">LEARN MORE</Text><Text Key="7E01DF46">Toggle Ghost Overlay</Text><Text Key="C4939970">Next Tab</Text><Text Key="33242EBC">Previous Tab</Text><Text Key="BED990A5">Soul</Text><Text Key="85453B4E">Grimbrosia Source</Text><Text Key="BF2CAA6E">Death Frog</Text><Text Key="814A7578">Thanatology Skill</Text><Text Key="596D2773">Horror</Text><Text Key="D9C4AFBB">(From Losing an Acquaintance)</Text><Text Key="7EE184BE">A Sim in a previously played Household has died. What do you want to do?</Text><Text Key="66B34D98">{0.SimName} has died.</Text><Text Key="70FA52AE">Have Sim's Inventory remain with their Ghost.</Text><Text Key="77CC724C">{0.SimFirstName}'s Ghost won't be around forever! Any items in {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} Inventory will be lost after Moving On. A Ghost's connection to the mortal world is tenuous and will decay over time.</Text><Text Key="8CB24F46">Delete Sim's Inventory.</Text><Text Key="B1F30D84">This will clear all items in the Sim's Inventory.</Text><Text Key="E2B47D11">Move Sim's Inventory to former Household Inventory.</Text><Text Key="2D7AAA75">Move all Inventory items for this Sim into the Household Inventory of the Household that this Sim belonged to before passing.</Text><Text Key="C006C217">You've earned enough Event Points to claim a reward! Go to the Event UI to claim it.</Text><Text Key="56AFFFD5">Reward Unlocked</Text><Text Key="C51C4248">Go to Event UI</Text><Text Key="FA1EC780">The Tarot Card Collection is complete!</Text><Text Key="13745E49">&lt;i&gt;To commence the collection of the Order of Lenore, seek the ancient Tarot Tome Shrine. Therein lies the book of tarot, a tome of secrets and lore.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="57BFC594">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Widowed Father Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="007F37FE">&lt;i&gt;In the depths where the living dare not tread, among the silent watchers of the dead, a chalice card rests with secrets to be read. In these hallowed crypts, let your steps be led.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="BFC5A7DB">&lt;i&gt;Beneath the cold stone of forgotten souls, where shadows whisper secrets untold, lies the card of swords, amidst the crypts of old. Seek where the dead repose, and the truth shall unfold.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="160609E4">&lt;i&gt;Where golden dreams turn to dust and decay, in the crypts where the lifeless lay, a coin's visage in card form holds sway. Venture forth, and let the shadows guide your way.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="B3E4DAD9">&lt;i&gt;When the moon is full and night sky is bright, and the Moon Revelry festival is alight, seek the card of the moon while digging in this mystic rite. Only under Luna’s gaze, will its secrets ignite.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="3A394632">&lt;i&gt;Within the hollow of an ancient tree, two cards lie hidden for those who see. But take heed of Alice, the sorrowful ghost, who mourns her lost child, her vigil unending at this haunted post.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="C548A908">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Ghost Host Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="B4AE2D6D">&lt;i&gt;In the depths of the Well of Longing and Regret, where darkness consumes and chaos unfolds, what lies hidden, their secrets untold. Beware of Edith, avoid her mark, lest your fate be sealed in the eternal dark.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="7AF67EC3">&lt;i&gt;Among the gravestones in Crow's Crossing there, where the departed rest in silent despair, a hidden card awaits with intuition's glare. Seek with care, for the past's whispers linger there.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="5103B04B">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Widowed Father Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="4212D403">&lt;i&gt;To find the card of Suspension's plight, search through Crow's Crossing graves with careful sight. Or, with ghostly powers, levitate a victim slight, and the hidden card shall come to light.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="98AC7286">&lt;i&gt;In the heart of Crow's Crossing, where specters roam and memories intertwine, converse with the restless souls for a glimpse divine. Through their tales of catharsis, the hidden card you shall find.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="79F9F321">&lt;i&gt;To uncover a card of arcane might, seek the spectral merchant Waylon, cloaked in night. His dealings are secret, his presence a blight, but treasures await those with courage to sight.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="EDDF8E97">&lt;i&gt;Befriend a crow, black as the night, and earn its trust with gentle might. In return, a card of the World’s insight shall be bestowed, a gift from flight.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="72210A5A">&lt;i&gt;When twenty-five cards you have amassed, Death himself shall appear at last. With a solemn gaze and eternal breath, he shall bestow the final card: Death.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="593AF0AE">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Death Obsessed Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="FA24855D">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Death Obsessed Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="402C9EB8">&lt;i&gt;By the eerie waters of Baleful Bog, where mists arise and shadows clog, use intuition, let senses guide, The Empress within shall hide.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="8B3D451F">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Ghost Host Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="1F053762">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Grim Enthusiast Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F7702891">&lt;i&gt;Within the shadows where Lenore's Order lies, Find the members, heed their cries. Complete their quests, though paths are hard, and win yourself a sacred card. The Grim Enthusiast Member is the one to seek.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="4ECE65DC">&lt;i&gt;Amidst the tombs where silence binds, a wand’s card in the crypts one finds. Yet, should darkness deter your quest, the wand shop offers a safer rest.&lt;/i&gt; </Text><Text Key="3A461AB2">Tarot Cards</Text><Text Key="C16A2D80">Tarot Cards can be found after discovering the Order of Lenore. By doing favors for the Order and exploring Ravenwood, Sims embark on a cosmic quest for the full deck.</Text><Text Key="08CDC664">Freezer Boney collection complete!</Text><Text Key="B0970C1E">Freezer Boneys</Text><Text Key="933A5484">Freezer Boneys can be earned by completing quests in the Reaper's Rewards limited time event!</Text><Text Key="406EFBAD">Missing Sim Milk Cartons Collection Complete!</Text><Text Key="073F6FD1">Cozy Wreaths (Cozy Celebrations Event)</Text><Text Key="77300D49">The Missing Sim Milk Cartons can be earned by completing quests in the Blast from the Past limited time event!</Text><Text Key="9C54D54E">Cozy Celebrations Event Collection Complete!</Text><Text Key="E1D44424">Missing Sim Milk Cartons</Text><Text Key="BA92A35A">Cozy Wreaths can be earned by completing quests in the Cozy Celebrations limited time event!</Text><Text Key="1008815B">Red</Text><Text Key="CB16CDC6">Indigo</Text><Text Key="653D422A">Lime</Text><Text Key="83EE48BF">Cyan</Text><Text Key="78A75E88">Fuchsia</Text><Text Key="BB883F9D">Blue</Text><Text Key="2005F3C6">Magenta</Text><Text Key="64F7A75B">Orange</Text><Text Key="8C0D4814">Coral</Text><Text Key="E5887582">Green</Text><Text Key="6C277E69">Gray</Text><Text Key="371E2214">Aqua</Text><Text Key="2EFF22BF">Purple</Text><Text Key="104E1C2A">Gold</Text><Text Key="6699199D">Yellow</Text><Text Key="23B83888">White</Text><Text Key="0AE8BC13">Pink</Text><Text Key="AF74689E">Violet</Text><Text Key="9F7A26B0">Enable Mood Color</Text><Text Key="8E070ADE">Current Owner: {0.SimName}</Text><Text Key="69B946DD">{0.SimName}'s Heirloom</Text><Text Key="9CA7FCFD">Lock for Rebirth</Text><Text Key="B33E261A">Bills are lower here to compensate for any...strangeness.</Text><Text Key="779B218C">Cemetery</Text><Text Key="F087C7AA">From</Text><Text Key="740F8078">Adorn your finest room with an heirloom that captures timeless family bonds. This vintage portrait adds a touch of historical charm while boasting the personal touch of the residing household.</Text><Text Key="12527F44">Lasting Legacy Family Portrait</Text><Text Key="5304E7D9">This antique music box features a tiny Grim Reaper figurine and plays a haunting lullaby, merging timeless elegance with the allure of the macabre. As an heirloom, this would withstand the test of time.</Text><Text Key="1D1FC19D">Mournful Melodies Music Box</Text><Text Key="D33C81B6">Slip on this luxurious downy mask when you’re feeling at your most deliciously wicked. Masquerading in this fowl finery will ensure nobody can see what nefarious plans you’re plotting.</Text><Text Key="EEA80B66">Plumed Elegance Mask</Text><Text Key="78347F0E">Macabre Mementos Digital Content</Text><Text Key="516997B3">This is a private retreat featuring a mysterious hidden entrance, elegant antique vanity, charming tea set, and more high-end touches sure to delight Sims with a sense of refinement.</Text><Text Key="9384FF53">An Opulent Oasis</Text><Text Key="05D0B7BA">These finely-tailored Italian-inspired fashions are polished, sophisticated, and feature classic silhouettes. It’s a cohesive collection that feels curated, as if hand-picked by someone with exquisite taste.</Text><Text Key="E849EE72">Flawlessly Fashionable</Text><Text Key="FA72745B">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Secret Sanctuary Kit</Text><Text Key="90236472">An Endless Journey</Text><Text Key="AC2BAF6A">Build your Sim's Bucket List with goals based on traits and relations. Complete them for powerful rewards. They can also be finished in the afterlife as Unfinished Business. The ultimate reward is Rebirth, but you can also Move On or stay as a Ghost.</Text><Text Key="ED9165CB">Join Grim’s career to reap souls and help ghosts, or become a Mortician to deal with death in another way. Explore Crypts, build Thanatology skills, and pursue the Ghost Historian Aspiration. Bond with a Pet Crow or collect Tarot Cards; ideal for Macabre Sims.</Text><Text Key="DD507FAB">A Ghastly, Gorgeous Life</Text><Text Key="C79DEA54">Sims grieve in 4 ways based on personalities and relationships. Customize Grieving Rituals to fit your story. Create Wills to pass down Heirlooms, assign guardians, and distribute Simoleons. Honor the departed with memorials, urns, and Custom Gravesites.</Text><Text Key="584CF0F8">Goodbye (For Now)</Text><Text Key="23D6EB65">Linger as a Ghost, helping or terrorizing the living. Grow abilities, assist with chores, or levitate Sims for fun. Earn Fear or Goodwill essences from interactions. Enjoy afterlife activities, including special spectral WooHoo with another Ghost.</Text><Text Key="84C09761">Friendly or Fiendish?</Text><Text Key="46986BB4">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death</Text><Text Key="EE7F12B2">A jumbo, state-of-the-art TV and stylish modern furniture will make your den an undeniable hotspot. Have friends over for a chill night at the card table – or have a date over for an exciting night on your stylish, well-loved leather sofa.</Text><Text Key="0FFD35AA">Elevated Evenings</Text><Text Key="2770BB0B">Dress in high-quality, understated fashions made for the masculine Sim. These styles are relaxed, achieving a polished look that is still a bit rough around the edges.</Text><Text Key="BF291EEB">Effortless Style</Text><Text Key="43A96BF4">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Casanova Cave Kit</Text><Text Key="4C9D649E">Give your Sims more ways to express their creativity. There’s a new easel, tablet, and woodworking table for Sims to use in their artistic endeavors. Place inspiring still-life references, a backdrop, and other props to really help your creativity flow.</Text><Text Key="5065958E">An Artist’s Tools</Text><Text Key="4825D687">Add an artistic flourish to your canvas and your studio. Add paint splatter to the ground and clutter items like palettes, cans, tubes, brushes, and stacked sketch books to every shelf and corner.</Text><Text Key="80B8696F">Artful Décor</Text><Text Key="FA526DD0">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Artist Studio Kit</Text><Text Key="9A2BEA93">Inspired by classic fairy tales and the elegance of ages past, this collection features delicately crafted toys, pleasant wallpaper, a dreamy mobile, and a dollhouse modeled after the traditional home of an old, prominent family.</Text><Text Key="A7D209B3">A Touch of Whimsy</Text><Text Key="43B06E9A">Raise your little one among ornate furniture including shelves and a changing table. Some of these items, like the crib with the sweeping canopy and the tasteful chandelier, may have been passed down through the generations.</Text><Text Key="5691FBD2">A Legacy of Elegance</Text><Text Key="FCC020BB">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Storybook Nursery Kit</Text><Text Key="F830D21C">Use the décor in this kit to make your computer area feel homey, relaxing, and completely yours with plants, clutter, and gaming accessories. There are even cubed cubbies for displaying knickknacks and other treasured items that make you happy!</Text><Text Key="35A61C60">A Personal Touch</Text><Text Key="D811780D">Who wouldn’t want a mini cow plant hanging over their head? This kit has all kinds of callouts to The Sims, including a grilled cheese mini-library and an adorable alarm clock.</Text><Text Key="29F013C9">A Little Sims-y</Text><Text Key="A60BF512">Welcome to The Sims™ 4 Comfy Gamer Kit</Text><Text Key="DB7FFEDB">A Personal Touch</Text><Text Key="68601328">A Little Sims-y</Text><Text Key="39209672">Comfy Gamer</Text><Text Key="BA78E9BB">Comfy Gamer</Text><Text Key="3D700B1E">Settle in for a cozy time at the computer with The Sims™ 4 Comfy Gamer Kit.</Text><Text Key="4EC2002A">An Artist’s Tools</Text><Text Key="720DA81D">Artful Décor</Text><Text Key="EE70A7A7">Artist Studio</Text><Text Key="C8FD2ECE">Artist Studio</Text><Text Key="524F468F">Design an inspiring space for Sims to hone their creative skills with The Sims™ 4 Artist Studio Kit.</Text><Text Key="6639410F">Cozy and Stylish </Text><Text Key="9E31B786">Sweet Slumber Party</Text><Text Key="2FBDB77F">Sweet Slumber Party</Text><Text Key="D11A5962">Look cute even when the venue of your party is your own bedroom with The Sims™ 4 Sweet Slumber Party Kit.</Text><Text Key="FA757169">A Touch of Whimsy</Text><Text Key="BD0E9666">A Legacy of Elegance</Text><Text Key="B316F9BC">Storybook Nursery</Text><Text Key="C841B88D">Storybook Nursery</Text><Text Key="1A819C84">Surround new additions to the family with the elegance they deserve in The Sims™ 4 Storybook Nursery Kit.</Text><Text Key="EDDDCD9B">Play With Color</Text><Text Key="829D1632">Cozy Kitsch</Text><Text Key="5F1F1A7B">Cozy Kitsch</Text><Text Key="9EE23BDE">Embrace vibrant colors and mid-century modern design with The Sims™ 4 Cozy Kitsch Kit.</Text><Text Key="F79699A7">Hand Picked</Text><Text Key="A4B3171E">Refined Living Room</Text><Text Key="88537AC7">Refined Living Room</Text><Text Key="AEB7318A">Embrace elegance and sophistication with The Sims™ 4 Refined Living Room Kit.</Text><Text Key="D65862D9">An Endless Journey</Text><Text Key="5650DC96">A Ghastly, Gorgeous Life</Text><Text Key="C7D94B73">Goodbye (For Now)</Text><Text Key="AF1FF680">Friendly or Fiendish?</Text><Text Key="ADBF23B5">A Town Worth Haunting</Text><Text Key="5FA854F2">Want some Ghosts? Mourningvale is a literal ghost town, and Crow's Crossing village is clearly haunted! Soak in the spooky during Ravenwood's many festivals, become a temporary Ghost by taking a dip in the Baleful Bog, and possibly even run into Grim himself.</Text><Text Key="FA1018F0">Ghosts &amp; Grim</Text><Text Key="BD16564B">Crypts, Cemeteries, the Afterlife Anonymous meeting, and little consoling Specters! Ravenwood is the perfect place to lift the spirits.</Text><Text Key="85085E6F">Memorial Sites</Text><Text Key="9722DAD4">Stop by the Collector Signs in any of the three neighborhoods, explore a Crypt, discover the secrets of the Tarot Tome Shrines, or check out the eerie ruins of Whispering Glen.</Text><Text Key="2243F786">Chilling Collections</Text><Text Key="B9D8FC1E">Things always get a little spooky in Ravenwood. The Whispering Glen with its nightly Moon Revelry festivities is perhaps the most "normal" part of the area, where locals have settled down for a slice of quiet, country life. Crow's Crossing village, however, is clearly quite haunted—swings swaying by themselves, that Merchant fellow down by the Crypt, scary little Edith guarding the Well of Longing and Regret…but despite the hauntings, the living have certainly made it their home as well with a variety of festivals and places to explore. Mourningvale is where things get extra ethereal! It's well known as a home for Ghosts and those seeking them. Sometimes Grim even stops by!</Text><Text Key="B5EE4321">Ravenwood</Text><Text Key="B446D60C">Life &amp; Death</Text><Text Key="1CA8CB7D">Life &amp; Death</Text><Text Key="AD8A07D4">Peel back the veil to uncover the secret to fuller Sim lives and beyond in The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death Expansion Pack.</Text><Text Key="01EECDD7">Tailored for Success</Text><Text Key="CEF7F7EE">Business Chic</Text><Text Key="6E6A4BB7">Business Chic</Text><Text Key="73FC0C9A">Give your Sims a professional edge with chic and stylish outfits from The Sims™ 4 Business Chic Kit!</Text><Text Key="17CC9901">An Opulent Oasis</Text><Text Key="D753D33E">Flawlessly Fashionable</Text><Text Key="C6DAC9F4">Secret Sanctuary</Text><Text Key="F38143F5">Secret Sanctuary</Text><Text Key="CB72188C">Indulge in iconic fashion and lavish décor with The Sims™ 4 Secret Sanctuary Kit.</Text><Text Key="138959BD">Elevated Evenings</Text><Text Key="C8D8E14A">Effortless Style</Text><Text Key="719EDD90">Casanova Cave</Text><Text Key="CD000391">Casanova Cave</Text><Text Key="03824B18">Impress guests with a modern entertainment space and suave fits from The Sims™ 4 Casanova Cave Kit. </Text><Text Key="FD760377">The {1.String} Household dependents could not be placed in the {2.String} Household because there are too many Sims. Go to &lt;b&gt;Manage Worlds&lt;/b&gt; and use &lt;b&gt;Manage Households&lt;/b&gt; to merge the dependents into another household.</Text><Text Key="B4AEA13F">Note: So long, suckers!</Text><Text Key="CA053AC1">{1.String}</Text><Text Key="84E9B3B3">The Will of {0.SimName}</Text><Text Key="740979CE">&lt;i&gt;The following actions will take effect when &lt;b&gt;all Sims aged Teen and older&lt;/b&gt; in the {0.String} Household die:&lt;/i&gt;\n</Text><Text Key="069285A4">&lt;i&gt;The following actions will take effect when {0.SimFirstName} dies:&lt;/i&gt;\n\n{1.String}</Text><Text Key="18ACC086">{0.SimFirstName}'s Will has arrived!\n\n{1.String}</Text><Text Key="09CF8799">{0.SimName} goes to the {1.String} Household.\n</Text><Text Key="25F6CE54">{0.Number}% of Simoleons will be donated to charity.\n</Text><Text Key="9A1F47BC">{0.Number}% of Simoleons go to the {1.String} Household.\n</Text><Text Key="1D54DD51">&lt;b&gt;Sim Remains Preference&lt;/b&gt;: {0.ObjectCatalogName}\n</Text><Text Key="D7708239">&lt;b&gt;Preferred Funeral Activities&lt;/b&gt;: {0.String}.\n</Text><Text Key="2EF41A54">&lt;b&gt;Heirloom&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;i&gt;{0.ObjectName}&lt;/i&gt; will be given to {1.SimName}.\n</Text><Text Key="D38FF385">&lt;i&gt;This will was written in a way that makes Sims feel {0.String}!&lt;/i&gt;\n</Text><Text Key="31B8F572">Personal Note: {0.String}</Text><Text Key="F16BF7B3">Find this item in Build Mode under Activities and Skills, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="AF975762">Congratulations, you earned two rewards. With the smaller Festive Starter Hedge and the longer Festive Hedge Row combo. Both are available in a variety of color options. What better way to lift the holiday spirit around your home.</Text><Text Key="71BA8FDD">Festive Hedge Collection</Text><Text Key="4007F7A9">The Slick Panel Jacket is not just stylish, it's weather resistant too. Available in multiple color options, you will be the center of attention when out and about.</Text><Text Key="BE032B8C">Slick Panel Jacket</Text><Text Key="8278780D">Find this item in Build Mode under Decorations, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="8688A6FC">Nothing prepares your guests for the Cozy Celebrations like the Festive Feeling Welcome Mat. Just make sure your guests use it before entering, no one likes cleaning muddy footprints.</Text><Text Key="CAAE0453">Festive Feeling Welcome Mat</Text><Text Key="53067286">Find this item in Build Mode under Electronics, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="B3A6290B">The Festive Frame TV adds a touch of festive class to any home. This TV doubles as a piece of art while it's off and lets you enjoy your shows or play console games when turned on.</Text><Text Key="AE19958A">The Festive Frame TV</Text><Text Key="0103F68E">This festive season, keep yourself happy and your feet even happier with a pair of Feet Friend Slippers. Available in a range of animal designs from Create a Sim this adorable footwear is perfect for lounging in.</Text><Text Key="3970E4B1">Feet Friend Slippers</Text><Text Key="3184F275">This retro console brings the nostalgia and comes with cartridge and disc capabilities and with support for up to two players for that cozy night in playing games.</Text><Text Key="F3E24B10">Super Dream Cube</Text><Text Key="369F7D78">Only during the festive period do Sims feel comfortable throwing their sense of fashion and donning these Ugly Jolly Jumpers. Available in a variety of designs in Create a Sim.</Text><Text Key="BAC6AF77">Ugly Jolly Jumper</Text><Text Key="BCAC23A7">Some Sims revel in the idea of seeing others miserable during the holidays and are extremely happy when their actions are the source of that misery. Unlock this trait and assign it to a Sim in Create a Sim to let the grouchy mischief begin.</Text><Text Key="E14F34DE">Grouch</Text><Text Key="5D4CBD2A">Prepare for the elements while looking stylish with the Cozy Neck Scarf. Available in Create a Sim under Accessories, the neck warmer comes in multiple colors and designs to fit any mood.</Text><Text Key="2A05C5B5">Cozy Neck Scarf</Text><Text Key="1A702859">There is a reason why things become classics, they just stand the test of time. Put this festive wreath up and it'll bring that feeling of holiday nostalgia to your home.</Text><Text Key="0DE54BDC">Cozy Festive Wreath</Text><Text Key="C0FFAB12">Looking for something different while keeping it classy? This floral wreath not only looks good, but it also probably smells good too.</Text><Text Key="D0BB662D">Cozy Floral Wreath</Text><Text Key="7B77B40F">Bring that sense of playfulness the holidays bring to your decorations by putting up this Freezer Bunny adorned wreath.</Text><Text Key="729AEDD6">Cozy Freezer Bunny Wreath</Text><Text Key="630D6DE8">Not quite ready to get into the full festive spirit? This wreath will give that autumn feeling, no matter the weather outside.</Text><Text Key="603DB407">Cozy Autumnal Wreath</Text><Text Key="A05E4138">Electronics</Text><Text Key="6EF3B1A7">Find this item in Build Mode under Audio, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="9E2F1C36">A supernatural sound system with a direct line to Grim himself, allowing his mortal acquaintances to summon him day or night. It can also play your favorite tunes, if you're into that sort of thing.</Text><Text Key="8A2E8C69">The Grimophone</Text><Text Key="85B98C28">Find this item under Piercings in Create a Sim, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="7388381D">While wearing these earrings, you can always feel the cold hand of the Grim Reaper tugging at your soul.</Text><Text Key="59E27B08">Earrings of Imminent Demise</Text><Text Key="86F030D6">Lot Challenge</Text><Text Key="52D43851">This Lot Challenge can be found in the Traits Panel in Build Mode.</Text><Text Key="2D1BB060">Lots with this challenge fill Sims with eldritch excitement, and attract other Sims looking for a ghoulishly good time.</Text><Text Key="2716AFAF">Scare Seeker Lot Challenge</Text><Text Key="572D0882">Find this item under Bottoms in Create a Sim, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="E5DC7107">Darkness meets denim with these sleek and traditional goth jeans.</Text><Text Key="828AEEBE">Trad Goth Jeans</Text><Text Key="30DC3E64">Activities and Skills</Text><Text Key="4169287B">Find this item in Build Mode in the Misc category under Activities and Skills, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="7E8F280A">Once thought lost in the Von Haunt Estate fire of 1898, this treatise contains the secrets to making Ambrosia and appears to have been authored Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot herself.</Text><Text Key="FD6FD915">The Green Lady's Lost Tome</Text><Text Key="604F719C">Find this item under Shoes in Create a Sim, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="F40E3B71">These boots are perfect for a moonlit stroll through the local cemetery.</Text><Text Key="C17B5744">Trad Goth Buckled Boots</Text><Text Key="7B48C402">Comfort</Text><Text Key="971B0455">Find this item in Build Mode under Beds, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="8E11DAA4">A traditional burial casket adorned with a floral skull inspired by the Grim Reaper himself. This model has been fitted with extra padding and sound proofing, guaranteeing a peaceful rest for the occupant.</Text><Text Key="2C8B71EB">Casket of Quiet Repose</Text><Text Key="414264E6">Find this item under Tattoos in Create a Sim, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="1ECE936B">No one appreciates the circle of life more than the Grim Reaper.</Text><Text Key="33B01C6A">Life &amp; Death Tattoo</Text><Text Key="B799371F">Find this item in Build Mode under Paintings &amp; Posters, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="E307CCEE">A portrait of Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot enjoying an afternoon in the gardens of the Von Haunt estate. Some people say they've seen the painting move, but that's probably just an urban legend, right?</Text><Text Key="12BCB291">Portrait of Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot in the Garden</Text><Text Key="BD933C25">Find this item under Tops in Create a Sim, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="3CFC80B4">Embrace the night in this elegant, goth-chic button-up.</Text><Text Key="3AFE3D1B">Trad Goth Button-Up</Text><Text Key="E763DB2B">Transportation</Text><Text Key="33A4C6AC">Find this item in Build Mode under Transportation, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="F7373D41">Travel the mortal realm in style with this faithful replica of the Grim Reaper's cruiser bike!</Text><Text Key="AFD54E74">Grim's Cruiser</Text><Text Key="BCC02D8B">This eye color can be applied in Create a Sim, under the Eyes category.</Text><Text Key="D1D5591A">Supernatural feline eyes suitable for stalking the night in search of prey.</Text><Text Key="D25DAC45">Prowling Peepers</Text><Text Key="86A6653D">Drink Recipe</Text><Text Key="B69F4852">Find this item under Make Drinks on a Bar</Text><Text Key="079E3F17">A cloying concoction that will give Sims a taste of the afterlife in one ghastly gulp.\n\n&lt;b&gt;Requires Mixology Skill Level 6&lt;/b&gt;</Text><Text Key="BEB070EE">Spectral Spritzer</Text><Text Key="FB8B7498">Collection</Text><Text Key="9F4C459E">Find this item in your Sim's inventory.</Text><Text Key="F14FF703">A supremely skeletal Freezer Boney. It would be much more terrifying to stumble upon one of these if they weren't so darn cute. </Text><Text Key="4E5FA852">Original Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="0D602570">A Freezer Boney from beyond our solar system. Its plastic frame shimmers with the vastness of a distant galaxy.</Text><Text Key="2F19961F">Starborn Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="080B9A6D">A colorful Freezer Boney calavera, commemorating The Day of the Dead. This Freezer Boney is often placed upon the ofrendas of departed Sims.</Text><Text Key="C435AF38">Sugar Skull Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="6EE04A9A">A Freezer Boney so shiny, you can see your reflection in it... assuming you have one. </Text><Text Key="5E20C8C5">Metallic Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="A4A93097">An exceptionally fluffy Freezer Boney for those cold nights when you want to curl up on the couch, wrap yourself in a cozy blanket, and ponder your own mortality. </Text><Text Key="4A738D6E">Plush Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="DA077234">Sporting an eerie green glow, this Freezer Boney is the perfect companion for a late-night goth rave. </Text><Text Key="C6C1599B">Glow-in-the-Dark Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="10ACEB3C">Find these items in Build Mode under Decorations, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="475F9811">Remember cords, wireless handsets, and answering machines? Or when caller ID meant answering the phone and asking "who is it?"\n\nThe Retro Deco Phone Set brings back all the memories from those early days. So take a seat by the ol'rolodex, and re-live life before call waiting.</Text><Text Key="90120B64">Retro Deco Phone Set</Text><Text Key="B284C71B">Find these items in Build Mode under Floor and Ceiling Patterns, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="5FD10F2A">Wood and parquet as a set? Absolutely!\n\nAt Retro Floors &amp; Floors, we have spent countless years lounging in all the best homes of yesterday—your home!\n\nNothing says Blast from the Past like unexpected floor material changes!</Text><Text Key="175E1BB5">The Yesterday Set</Text><Text Key="77995FA2">Find this item in Build Mode under Electronics, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="BF3075A7">"Time waits for no Sim", but with the return of the classic Get Up! Alarm Clock you'll never be late because you lost track of time, again!\n\nSet it, forget it, and let this trusty gadget do the rest.</Text><Text Key="CEA78ADE">Get Up! Alarm Clock</Text><Text Key="1245CF36">Accessories</Text><Text Key="94036171">Find this item in Create a Sim under Accessories, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="3D00A680">Emit often found the burst of sunlight as he emerged to each new arrival to be overwhelming. If only he had some way to block the sun's light.\n\nAfter many years of dedication, Emit developed his specially made "sun" glasses to keep his eyes shaded.</Text><Text Key="C39BB64F">The Future's So Bright "Sun" Glasses</Text><Text Key="A5A2AB48">Find this item in Build Mode under Comfort, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="F102D03D">Feeling deflated? Inflate some fun with the Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part One!\n\nPart One combines quirky style and ultimate relaxation in one bouncy* package. Perfect for lounging, chatting, or sitting. Part One is sure to add a pop of personality to your space!\n\n*Does not support bouncing.</Text><Text Key="1D6686A8">The Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part One</Text><Text Key="B8042198">Full Body</Text><Text Key="53E6C847">Find this item in Create a Sim under Full Body, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="B12F3756">Does it protect the time traveler? Is it temporally insulated? Does it provide a quick dry in a rainstorm? No. But...\n\nA thousand years from now, this is the hottest thing in the megalopolis of Greater Sixam!</Text><Text Key="0DA88009">Be "The Emit"</Text><Text Key="BBB3BFC1">Activities and Skills</Text><Text Key="3AE6F8EE">Find this item in Build Mode under Activities and Skills, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="7F6B8C13">The Bigger Gatherings Banquet is your perfect choice for notching up your dinner parties, feasts, and shindigs to an eleven! This sturdy table ensures your gatherings always have a place for food, drinks, and socializing in style. Never ask, 'Where’s the food?' again.</Text><Text Key="41B508C2">Bigger Gatherings Banquet</Text><Text Key="1774940A">Accessories</Text><Text Key="2487DA0D">Find this item in Create a Sim under Accessories, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="890CF8FC">Emit often found time travel to be quite a head spin, until he discovered this handy neck stabilizer. Don't leave time without it!</Text><Text Key="B8065A53">The Relevart Neck Stabilizer</Text><Text Key="02EA18A3">Full Body</Text><Text Key="7898CF54">Find this item in Create a Sim under Full Body, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="428C49A9">The little black dress inspired by Dina Caliente, is a versatile essential to your wardrobe that can be worn dressed up or down, for any occasion.</Text><Text Key="AB5B818C">Dina Caliente's LBD</Text><Text Key="20F61291">Comfort</Text><Text Key="89A4571E">Find this item in Build Mode under Comfort, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="A95B7C83">Comfort meets convenience with the Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part Two!\n\nDesigned to foster a relaxed atmosphere. Its soft contours and light material make Part Two perfect for lounging, napping, or kicking back for a playful night of movies and popcorn!</Text><Text Key="C05840D2">The Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part Two</Text><Text Key="CBBCC5E8">Aspirations</Text><Text Key="DE1E2AF7">Find this in Create a Sim or Live Mode when choosing an Aspiration</Text><Text Key="AE48C1C6">Do you desire to climb the corporate ladder? Or swipe the ladder from beneath the feet of others?\n\nNimble fingers and a knack for mischief are the keys to a fortune in ill-gotten gains!</Text><Text Key="261C9459">Sticky Fingers</Text><Text Key="7DEEF4CF">Music - Retro</Text><Text Key="DB79CD38">Find these songs on any stereo on the Retro station, or in Game Options under Music - Retro.</Text><Text Key="C0171FED">Enjoy some new additions to the Retro music station! Whether it be a little 'naba neen naba neen' or 'tabwa ee' these throwback melodies are sure to hit that nostalgic note!</Text><Text Key="362E47B8">New Retro Station Songs</Text><Text Key="313CF546">Activities and Skills</Text><Text Key="9671BD61">Find this item in Build Mode under Activities and Skills, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="C56BAAF0">This colorful confection is sure to bring the ooh's and aah's, and maybe a little unexpected something surprising to the celebration!\n\nLight the Candles, Make a Wish, and be prepared for a little dancing!</Text><Text Key="A1122E9F">Surprise Birthday Cake</Text><Text Key="251D3752">Find this item in Build Mode under Activities and Skills, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="5CB4B617">The ElectroDance Floor is the perfect excuse for you to show off your "Get down and Boogie" moves!\n\nGather your friends, and turn those ordinary garden parties into a full-blown raves!</Text><Text Key="BC6C25EE">The ElectroDance Floor</Text><Text Key="D34BEF04">Find this item in Build Mode under Decorations, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="14F53859">The theory of the multiversal-disc, or digital depending upon your era of expertise, states "...any Sim that can be, has been in some way and at some time."\n\nThe Missing Sim Milk Carton collection attempts to make sense of the mind-bending multitude of Sim possibilities.</Text><Text Key="61477BDC">Missing Sim Milk Carton</Text><Text Key="06F0FEC2">Shoes</Text><Text Key="9AEDC115">Find this item in Create a Sim under Shoes, or use the Event Rewards filter.</Text><Text Key="D2D6D864">Walking the strands of time isn't easy.\n\nHaving a good pair of walking boots at hand really helps to keep you grounded as time is ripped apart beneath your feet.</Text><Text Key="B115CCAB">Relevart Time Walkers</Text><Text Key="5DE40314">Check your Sim's Inventory to find the reward!</Text><Text Key="3D345A75">Read this book to level up your Gardening skill!</Text><Text Key="E9840310">Gardening Vol 1: Water, Light and Dirt</Text><Text Key="424EE578">Read this book to level up your Cooking skill!</Text><Text Key="B0686777">Cooking Vol 1: Let's Cook!</Text><Text Key="05E012FE">Read this book to level up your Fishing skill!</Text><Text Key="777A8F81">Fishing Vol 2: Tackles and Techniques</Text><Text Key="35A6637B">Drink this potion to enter the Happy emotion!</Text><Text Key="07B621DA">Happy Potion</Text><Text Key="44AC6168">Drink this potion to instantly remove all negative Moodlets!</Text><Text Key="6A193687">Moodlet Solver</Text><Text Key="686E3665">Drink this potion to fill your Sim's Energy need!</Text><Text Key="793422E0">Sleep Replacement</Text><Text Key="A29E9E92">Because of its somber coloring Jet is commonly used in mourning jewelry, but it isn’t commonly known that Jet is actually fossilized wood!</Text><Text Key="DA96E8AD">Jet</Text><Text Key="5D16A78F">A plantable, strangely bovine fruit.</Text><Text Key="7C767056">Cowplant Berry</Text><Text Key="A6DBDDEC">Foul-smelling and inexplicably composed entirely of refuse.</Text><Text Key="D47D9823">Trash Fruit</Text><Text Key="FC0F1BD9">Drink this potion to refresh your Sim's Wants!</Text><Text Key="17C0CE5C">Want Refresher</Text><Text Key="214CF6C6">A spooky, yet elegant blossom. Roses just don't cut it for the Grim Reaper. Try this flower to calm his qualms and get out of a deadly situation.  </Text><Text Key="4E192359">Death Flower</Text><Text Key="1C5FB183">Drink this potion to change your Sim's personality traits!</Text><Text Key="E854CFD2">Re-Traiting Potion</Text><Text Key="BF55910B">Drink this potion to enter the Energized emotion!</Text><Text Key="A3BB4D8A">Energized Potion</Text><Text Key="0CB35E8E">Drink this potion to enter the Happy emotion!</Text><Text Key="2F129CB1">Happy Potion</Text><Text Key="B3A4E38C">Gardening Vol 2: Getting Your Thumbs Green</Text><Text Key="92380EFC">Drink this potion to fill your Sim's Hygiene Need!</Text><Text Key="C04FBC53">Instant Hygiene</Text><Text Key="4B6FD35F">Drink this potion to fill your Sim's Fun Need!</Text><Text Key="FD204106">Instant Fun</Text><Text Key="BB46BF62">Plant this rare flower and watch it bloom!</Text><Text Key="675C47DD">Bird of Paradise</Text><Text Key="FA2DE63D">The batfish doesn't sleep upside-down, but it has nice, leathery wings to make up for it.</Text><Text Key="25AFE8A8">Batfish</Text><Text Key="462BBC80">Drink this potion to enter the Inspired Emotion!</Text><Text Key="CBE5184F">Inspired Potion</Text><Text Key="47CE21B0">Household Funds</Text><Text Key="23D4A20F">Find these in your Household Funds available in Live Mode and Build Mode.</Text><Text Key="99A8655E">The sweet currency of all things good and bad! Use it to spruce up your home or simply stash it for a rainy day.</Text><Text Key="26A05A61">500 Simoleons</Text><Text Key="018C6159">Rewards Store</Text><Text Key="C9139616">Find these in the Rewards Store available in Live Mode.</Text><Text Key="FF00455B">Spend Satisfaction Points in the Reward Store.\n\nGrab a quick fix emotion potion or choose from a bevy of impactful traits for your Sims and discover new ways to play!</Text><Text Key="C037093A">25 Satisfaction Points</Text><Text Key="5F32FE48">Read this book to level up your Handiness skill!</Text><Text Key="04606EE7">Handiness Vol 1: Try Not to Die!</Text><Text Key="41B0D3F2">Read this book to level up your Logic skill!</Text><Text Key="2B98ED8D">Logic Vol 1: An Introduction to Reason</Text><Text Key="98446B6F">Read this book to level up your Programming skill!</Text><Text Key="CCEB96B6">Programming Vol 1: Turn It Off and On Again</Text><Text Key="D8C7BECC">Read this book to level up your Video Gaming skill!</Text><Text Key="276D2783">Video Gaming Vol 1: Trolling for n00bs</Text><Text Key="633F3AFB">(From Stargazing)</Text><Text Key="E39F4BDA">(From Cloudgazing)</Text><Text Key="59B8BCCB">(From Being Caught Sabotaging)</Text><Text Key="CC41C228">(From Enhanced Kleptomaniac Trait)</Text><Text Key="44EF00E8">(From Macabre Trait)</Text><Text Key="2A2D8522">(From Losing Party Frenzy)</Text><Text Key="91AC9E7A">(From Winning Party Frenzy)</Text><Text Key="E1FCF8B8">(From Losing MySims Racing)</Text><Text Key="795A6C40">(From Winning MySims Racing)</Text><Text Key="6806CD5C">(From Being a Sore Loser)</Text><Text Key="4396CE93">(From Winning Genie's Curse)</Text><Text Key="C38A13A5">(From Winning Density Effect)</Text><Text Key="437550A8">(From Sleeping in a Coffin)</Text><Text Key="A431A541">Since {0.SimFirstName} is Chased by Death, being more cautious around electrical objects would be prudent.</Text><Text Key="B0C7C8A1">(From Eating Death Frog Hot Pot)</Text><Text Key="EF022D42">Eating that tasty Death Frog Hot Pot has replenished {0.SimFirstName}'s Ghost Stamina!</Text><Text Key="AE45C105">(From Befriending Death)</Text><Text Key="6D145F62">Unfortunately {0.SimFirstName} was not able to cope with Grief in the most productive ways, resulting in a Personality Trait change.</Text><Text Key="070AD767">Congratulations! {0.SimFirstName} was able to cope with Grief in a healthy way, resulting in a Personality Trait change.</Text><Text Key="A80117C2">Personality Change</Text><Text Key="99CF599B">Beloved Mother and Wife\n\nAnn dedicated her life to the education of children, and she inspired so many. She was the one Sim everyone agreed on.</Text><Text Key="A16CC1CE">(From Exercise)</Text><Text Key="C9C0C427">I don't want to talk about Ambrosia...</Text><Text Key="4829B24F">Can't you just look Ambrosia up on a computer?</Text><Text Key="804F849E">Why are you asking me about Ambrosia? I haven't heard anything!</Text><Text Key="F571F21F">I've heard that you need to have mastered the Cooking and Gourmet cooking skills.</Text><Text Key="84F18BB7">If you want to make Ambrosia, you'll need to be willing to get your hands a bit dirty.</Text><Text Key="742FF1CE">Ambrosia?! I'm not sure how to make it, but I would love to learn and bring a ghost back to life.</Text><Text Key="DBA2A4D9">I seem to recall Ambrosia is a gourmet food.</Text><Text Key="9D4AD09C">Make sure you know how to fish. You'll need it if you want to make Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="186449C2">Thank you for your purchase! You can find your Death Flower in your Sim's inventory.</Text><Text Key="3B05DF1D">The Reaper's Rewards Event has ended. You can still claim any rewards that are unlocked in the Event UI.</Text><Text Key="A6DEE55F">Event Ended</Text><Text Key="D9C8C583">(From the Scare Seeker Lot Challenge)</Text><Text Key="6935B20C">Accused Sim</Text><Text Key="82F71078">If I could travel through time, do you think I would be here and not with the dinosaurs!?</Text><Text Key="02405C39">I wish I could time travel! Of course you have to worry about the re-entry. A building that wasn't there, that is there...it boggles the mind.</Text><Text Key="AC9425A1">A time traveler? Time doesn't exist beyond the present.</Text><Text Key="DC6F4E93">Is that even possible? I think you've been reading too much Wells.</Text><Text Key="D5D8E09F">Oh, if you find a time traveler, let me know. I have a lot of questions to ask.</Text><Text Key="2308410A">Emit's Location</Text><Text Key="28B06BF2">Emit? Nope, don't know an Emit. Knew a Skip once. I wonder whatever happened to him?</Text><Text Key="9009515A">No, haven't seen anyone like that. I'd try the park, everyone hangs out there.</Text><Text Key="CF167896">I was just out Sim watching and heard a loud bang. Maybe that's what you're looking for?</Text><Text Key="11D86023">I was just at the park and I think I saw someone matching that description.</Text><Text Key="F1997769">Someone told me they saw a flash of light while they were near the park.</Text><Text Key="7024F2B9">I haven't noticed anything missing, but then again, I don't pay much attention. Sorry.</Text><Text Key="505C3E27">Come to think of it, I have an alarm clock I really love that's gone missing. I just thought I had misplaced it.</Text><Text Key="6D0CFB17">I planned this big surprise party for the neighborhood, but the cake I ordered never arrived!</Text><Text Key="5CA3C706">There was this old song that...how did it go? La la la la di da?</Text><Text Key="24F9577F">Missing Items</Text><Text Key="8D9E1A5E">My friend had this muy caliente dress that was perfect for dancing. But it's been missing for a while now.</Text><Text Key="F3A1B9D0">Time Traveler Clue</Text><Text Key="F76A9DB7">Whoever it is, I bet they are trying to not stand out. Maybe they wear  a mask?</Text><Text Key="56D2390F">I bet Emit is looking for some sort of time bandit. Someone has to be taking those items from previous games.</Text><Text Key="0ACDF3B6">If someone is actually taking items from previous Sims games, I have to wonder why.</Text><Text Key="76FA65B6">I heard about a time traveler, but how would you know when you saw one?</Text><Text Key="21C05FC8">A second explosion and flash of light has been reported. Local Sims are beginning to wonder if time travelers have been visiting...</Text><Text Key="E199B4EE">We're receiving reports of a potential time traveler in town.\n\nTheir identity, origin, and purpose remain unconfirmed. However, several Sims have noted the distinct blue hair of this new arrival that they believe to be Emit Relevart.\n\nOver to you, Ginny.</Text><Text Key="637F58A0">(From Grim's Right Hand Trait)</Text><Text Key="02119B65">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their High Metabolism Trait to {1.SimFirstName}! Somehow. It's best not to think about it.</Text><Text Key="DEC74167">Pass it Down!</Text><Text Key="7D93D2D0">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Muser Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="6450317E">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Dastardly Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="3651A734">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Domestic Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="05DF39D9">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Essence of Flavor Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="30395B16">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Business Savvy Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="E45BC920">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Quick Learner Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="EAD845C0">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Home Turf Trait to {1.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="57D5D301">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Alluring Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="0DA62E0A">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Collector Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="AD60380C">{0.SimFirstName} passed down their Gregarious Trait to {1.SimFirstName}!</Text><Text Key="3CA800FE">Welcome to life as a Ghost, {0.SimFirstName}! Explore newfound powers with &lt;b&gt;Ghost Mastery&lt;/b&gt; and level up to become the most formidable ghost! It's also never too late to embark on the &lt;b&gt;Soul's Journey&lt;/b&gt; to take care of any Unfinished Business.</Text><Text Key="0457D1D8">Ghostly Beginnings</Text><Text Key="1D25AF8C">(From Witnessing a Deathly Experience)</Text><Text Key="CD82C60F">(From Witnessing a Justified Death)</Text><Text Key="B142AAB9">Thanks for the scare! Here's a gift:\n{1.String}</Text><Text Key="7E2F45B7">Sticky Fingers</Text><Text Key="CAD0676C">Grouch Sims will claim that they aren't really grouchy, just misunderstood. Either way, they definitely get great joy from making those around them miserable with their pranks and approach to social interactions.</Text><Text Key="50878DCA">Grouch Lesson</Text><Text Key="63A5F978">(From Being an Elder)</Text><Text Key="1549AA57">(From Being an Adult)</Text><Text Key="48E812E1">(From Grouch Trait)</Text><Text Key="185BDFDE">With nimble fingers and a knack for mischief, {0.SimFirstName} successfully swiped {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} way to the top! {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent|xxUpper} cunning and stealth have earned {0.SimPronounObjective} a notorious reputation and a fortune in ill-gotten gains.\n\nTrait Earned: Enhanced Kleptomaniac\n\nAttempt to Swipe is easier to succeed!</Text><Text Key="2783016A">This Sim wants to become a master procurer and redistributor of goods and wealth to their own pocket.</Text><Text Key="E7190E33">Work on Goals</Text><Text Key="847400F7">(From Alarm Clock)</Text><Text Key="8EFD360C">(From Scented Candles)</Text><Text Key="E87D4647">Awakened by an alarm clock can be unpleasant, but necessary.</Text><Text Key="594569FE">Jolted Awake</Text><Text Key="456ACE0F">A new day, a new opportunity!</Text><Text Key="4BF51BD6">Awake and Ready to Go</Text><Text Key="493E522C">Eeeeck! Get out get out get out get out get out! *Whew* Sleeping inside of a sealed coffin is definitely not for the faint of heart.</Text><Text Key="265E8763">Claustrophobic Nightmare</Text><Text Key="846D8457">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't know what to do in a situation like this.</Text><Text Key="063CB015">Another chance for {0.SimFirstName} means that {0.SimPronounSubjective} can do everything that {0.SimPronounSubjective} ever wanted!</Text><Text Key="C6CCEF30">Given a Second Chance</Text><Text Key="149117EE">Now that {0.SimFirstName} has a new lease on life (or on afterlife), {0.SimPronounSubjective} can't help but feel inspired by the endless possibilities awaiting the rest of {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} days!</Text><Text Key="CFF0A391">The Possibilities Are Endless!</Text><Text Key="C4871D73">Although given another chance, {0.SimFirstName} can't help but regret the actions that brought {0.SimPronounObjective} to this ghostly outcome.</Text><Text Key="757DDEA2">Unexpected Unlife</Text><Text Key="C7012988">It was an interesting thought, but {0.SimFirstName} had not considered the &lt;i&gt;actual reality&lt;/i&gt; of WooHooing with Grim. Cold bony claws, the eerie sense of dread...</Text><Text Key="2251ED27">Deathly Performance</Text><Text Key="3D82B6D6">Grim has got it goin' on! Who knew that an undead being from the afterlife could move like that?!</Text><Text Key="8423E689">Grim Satisfaction</Text><Text Key="5A5D65FE">When you're as old as Grim, it's only natural to pick up a few impressive tricks over time. {0.SimFirstName} had an experience that {0.SimPronounSubjective} will never forget!</Text><Text Key="75BC1881">Out of this Life</Text><Text Key="53BED2DE">How disappointing... Not even one good scare!</Text><Text Key="83752AE1">Never Scared</Text><Text Key="F32FEFE0">{0.SimFirstName} isn't sure...but did that painting just move?</Text><Text Key="5978562F">Did That Just Move?</Text><Text Key="FADAEF9D">This feels amazing!</Text><Text Key="24460988">Phantom</Text><Text Key="11E7C909">That was a good scare!</Text><Text Key="B215346C">Good one!</Text><Text Key="79DFF833">How terrifying! {0.SimFirstName} will have to calm down a bit after all this excitement.</Text><Text Key="90092162">Terrifically Terrifying </Text><Text Key="913B4A81">Looking at the vast sky brings inspiration that anything is possible.</Text><Text Key="13893CB4">Sparked by Clouds</Text><Text Key="4246E02D">{0.SimFirstName} loves {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} personal space more than others.</Text><Text Key="A3AFD3F8">Good Communication Is the Key</Text><Text Key="25C69F72">Sometimes, even the greatest mind can fail</Text><Text Key="38F1780D">Maybe that wasn't a good idea...</Text><Text Key="0CC839D4">No one can predict {0.SimFirstName} next move!</Text><Text Key="1392AEBB">Gotcha!</Text><Text Key="0B17CFDA">{0.SimFirstName} made the other Sim believe in {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} crazy story!</Text><Text Key="2D63AF05">Have You Heard This Gossip?</Text><Text Key="C47EF9A7">Someone is being nice to me? This is the worst!</Text><Text Key="4183D6DE">Is this... Kindness?</Text><Text Key="56D8EEBB">Someone near is not in their best mood, nice!</Text><Text Key="E76DE91A">What a Pleasant Environment</Text><Text Key="0884BFCD">There are a lot of Sims around... Maybe {0.SimFirstName} should leave.</Text><Text Key="4AA11418">Others Tire Me</Text><Text Key="4CE532B3">No one is around to talk with {0.SimFirstName}.</Text><Text Key="6CE6C8E2">Silence is Underrated</Text><Text Key="C16CDE7F">It's not so funny, as they say...</Text><Text Key="E524FCA6">Not Funny</Text><Text Key="11227DD3">Good game! {0.SimFirstName} didn't win, but {M0.he}{F0.she}'ll get them next time!</Text><Text Key="4C3A1482">Party Shenanigans</Text><Text Key="E5FDAF3B">{M0.King}{F0.Queen} of the virtual hill!</Text><Text Key="0D67429A">Party Game Pro!</Text><Text Key="EE07F751">{0.SimFirstName} is the champion of the short attention span!</Text><Text Key="62CD3BA4">Minigame Hero</Text><Text Key="2F02BB8D">At least {0.SimFirstName} didn't come in last!</Text><Text Key="F05E89D8">First Loser</Text><Text Key="E428D5E5">Way to leave the competition in the dust!</Text><Text Key="CCFAE960">Race Master!</Text><Text Key="355DD04F">Vroom vroom!</Text><Text Key="7921B116">Needed Some Speed</Text><Text Key="0BDFFFE3">If games are supposed to be fun, why do they make {0.SimFirstName} so mad?</Text><Text Key="2346ABB2">Rage Quit</Text><Text Key="A66FE78A">{0.SimFirstName} has dispelled the Genie's curse, but the princess is in another videogame.</Text><Text Key="FA8EFF95">Curse Reversed!</Text><Text Key="638D0DD0">Saving the galaxy requires some tough decision-making, but {0.SimFirstName} is more than up to the task!</Text><Text Key="2A5E2DFF">Commander's Shepherd</Text><Text Key="8831B19C">Life is so unfair! {0.SimFirstName}'s pain is manifesting itself as helplessness and frustration at the mortal injustice facing {0.SimPronounObjective}. </Text><Text Key="8120D873">How Can This Happen?!</Text><Text Key="E8995ACC">They were fine a moment ago... How did this happen? {0.SimFirstName} is having trouble grasping the reality of the situation.</Text><Text Key="2EFCBBE5">What's Going On?</Text><Text Key="00124CA9">&lt;i&gt;Eeeeerp!&lt;/i&gt; Is that {0.SimFirstName}'s stomach? Being around death is...disgusting! </Text><Text Key="DBF81A8C">Hard to Stomach</Text><Text Key="B63567C6">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't know what to do in a situation like this.</Text><Text Key="C8D5A659">Around Death</Text><Text Key="CACDAA44">It might be in bad taste to celebrate when someone dies, however, {0.SimFirstName} can't seem to contain {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} apparent joy!</Text><Text Key="29E8C60B">What an Experience!</Text><Text Key="513AECBB">You don't venture into the lion's den with the expectation of coming out unscathed. Sometimes death is the only logical ending for some actions. </Text><Text Key="E857831A">Serves Them Right!</Text><Text Key="AB922CBA">It's not often that we get a second chance at improving or mending relationships with those that we care about. {0.SimFirstName} would be wise to remember this moving forward.</Text><Text Key="40AEFA65">Second Chance</Text><Text Key="1F89381F">Looking at the vast sky brings inspiration that anything is possible.</Text><Text Key="2C2A88C6">Illuminated by Stars</Text><Text Key="D0F88028">Heirloom Eligible</Text><Text Key="7DB8165B">On Bereavement</Text><Text Key="BA467622">The Cozy Celebrations Event</Text><Text Key="4285798F">The Happy at Home Event</Text><Text Key="C17AEC44">The Blast from the Past Event</Text><Text Key="3D3EB15B">The Reaper's Rewards Event</Text><Text Key="4BC09FD5">Show Festival Info</Text><Text Key="11FEA845">The Festival Has Not Started Yet.</Text><Text Key="4B594EB4">A Festival Is Happening in This Neighborhood!</Text><Text Key="5FA5CEA8">Travel is unavailable from your current location.</Text><Text Key="9E174682">Sul sul! I need your help to spread joy and cheer this holiday season! I've received a special mission to discover the wonderful traditions that people around the world share with their loved ones. I thought you could lend me a hand.\nTry talking with others or cooking something unique to connect with these traditions.\n\nWarmest wishes,\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="391E199C">Learning about Traditions</Text><Text Key="E23E5E19">It looks like you've caught the spirit! The holiday season is all about sharing wonderful moments. Perhaps you could have a heartfelt conversation with Sims around the neighborhood. Oh, and don't forget to try making some delicious Brigadeiro—I know someone will enjoy this treat.\n\nWarmest wishes,\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="5084A14B">Exploring New Perspectives</Text><Text Key="C858A1AC">Sul sul!\nThe holiday season is special because of the cherished moments we share with those closest to us. For this part of our research, take some time to cook something special and share a meaningful moment with someone you care about.\n\nFestive regards,\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="261A770A">A Sweet Memory</Text><Text Key="B79DD9CB">The holidays are well underway, are you prepared for it? During these special days, Sims celebrate with unique cultural traditions. Try searching for something interesting online and explore different kinds of music for the season.\n\nSeasonal regards,\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="57210239">The Rhythm of the Festivities</Text><Text Key="B5C95366">Season's Greetings!\nI hope you're enjoying your research. This week, take some time to celebrate the holiday by sharing gifts, good memories, food, and happiness with the Sims you love and care about.\n\nHappy Holidays,\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="F8F95740">It’s Time to Celebrate</Text><Text Key="7137401D">Let's Celebrate!\nIt's time to embrace all the traditions you’ve been learning about—what do you think?\nTry making the place cozier, play games with Sims you care about, and enjoy a good, sweet hot chocolate to celebrate these last traditions. Oh, and don't forget to take notes on your experiences.\n\nReflecting on our newly researched Holiday traditions\n\n- Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="2B59AE5F">The Holiday Spirit</Text><Text Key="9257EF81">Pssttt… Hey, you…\n\nOver the centuries, my memory has started to grow foggy. I’ve heard rumblings about a special dish called "Ambrosia" that could jeopardize my job.\n\nComplete the &lt;i&gt;Assistant to the Grim Reaper&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;A Call Away&lt;/i&gt; quests to help me understand it!</Text><Text Key="514C3073">Reaper's Rewards: Week 1</Text><Text Key="7096B77F">It’s time to get your hands a little dirty. You’ll need to dig a hole or two for this next step, but I can’t help you. It’s time for me to take a (non) eternal nap.\n\nComplete the &lt;i&gt;Digging Holes&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Friends with Death&lt;/i&gt; quests, and good luck!</Text><Text Key="FDEC869D">Reaper's Rewards: Week 2</Text><Text Key="90553550">It seems as if Lady Mimsy was quite knowledgeable about Ambrosia. You'll need to keep honing your fishing skills if you want to put her knowledge to use.\n\nComplete the quests &lt;i&gt;The First Ingredient&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Learning from the Lady&lt;/i&gt;—don’t let me down now!</Text><Text Key="96AA85DE">Reaper's Rewards: Week 3</Text><Text Key="5245B753">It just so happens that the next ingredient is my favorite flower: The Death Flower!\n\nComplete the quests &lt;i&gt;Death's Favorite Flower&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Flirting with Death&lt;/i&gt;. It’s time for you to nurture a Death Flower to life!</Text><Text Key="5DB9A9E1">Reaper's Rewards: Week 4</Text><Text Key="7A246BE9">One ingredient remains—a Potion of Youth!\n\nYou’ll need Satisfaction Points in order to snag one, so complete the quests &lt;i&gt;An Inspiring Potion&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Skilled Chef&lt;/i&gt; to unlock the final secret of Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="3FD1ADDB">Reaper's Rewards: Week 5</Text><Text Key="3B32D406">This is the moment of truth…\n\nIt’s time to cook the Ambrosia. Complete the quests &lt;i&gt;The Moment of Truth&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Fruits of Your Labor&lt;/i&gt; and let's celebrate this monumental occasion!</Text><Text Key="8D6C7D60">Reaper's Rewards: Week 6</Text><Text Key="F77E6F72">Continue this Quest</Text><Text Key="91F56FA2">A brilliant flash and resounding boom echo through the town, sparking curiosity and rumors.\n\nA mysterious figure appears, both familiar and strikingly different. Could this enigmatic visitor be linked to the disturbance?\n\nUnravel the mystery in the "Strange Visitor" quest...</Text><Text Key="425159CC">As the mystery of missing items deepens, your Sim keeps searching for answers.\n\nWith each missing item, their anxiety grows. What could truly be happening?\n\nContinue the "Missing Clues" quest to uncover these mysteries and more...</Text><Text Key="2BE1BAB9">After discovering the IOU Note, you realize that understanding the secrets of time travel is crucial to stopping the thief.\n\nWith Emit's guidance, continue learning everything about this mysterious phenomenon.</Text><Text Key="268E8F86">Having discovered the secret element of time travel, Emit has challenged you to become a time traveler as well!\n\nContinue this quest to find out how to build a time travel component.</Text><Text Key="3F2976EB">Each part of the plan is falling into place. Although something still feels off, confidence is in the air.\n\nContinue this quest to see what happens next.</Text><Text Key="B3E5B2E0">Determined as ever, it's time for the final plan to be put into action.\n\nAll systems are in place. The time travel component based on Nikolai Volt's theoretical electronics work is installed and activated, and the computer is sufficiently overclocked.\n\nIt's time to catch a thief!</Text><Text Key="9EE9063D">With the thief caught in the act, Emit has one last order of business—to find out why they stole to begin with. Put the final pieces together so this never happens again.</Text><Text Key="AD9EC5FA">The thief had the right intentions but the wrong methods.\n\nAs a fan of time, they wanted to preserve the treasures of the past into the present and on to the future to keep forever.</Text><Text Key="5532ED93">Retro Edwardian Tile</Text><Text Key="6F57BB0C">Spiral Parquet</Text><Text Key="2A59B494">As impactful as its larger sibling, without the wooziness! Delight demands just as much admiration and awe with just as much stock!</Text><Text Key="1C157E7B">Delight</Text><Text Key="F7F8A1D0">The creator of The Sloop, Don B. Dumm, wanted a bar that fit his favorite surf shack. Enter The Sloop Jr! Enjoy the chill vibes and level your mixology skill at the same time. Hang ten!</Text><Text Key="DAE4A9FF">The Sloop Jr.</Text><Text Key="60A6B4CE">You loved the VAULT, but you wanted more! We heard you, and here we are with the extra long, extra stock, extra pro VAULT 2!</Text><Text Key="7938E4F1">VAULT 2 Pro-Er-Level Bar</Text><Text Key="39613C0E">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA traditional burial casket adorned with a floral skull inspired by the Grim Reaper himself. This model has been fitted with extra padding and sound proofing, guaranteeing a peaceful rest for the occupant.</Text><Text Key="A432BD31">Casket of Quiet Repose</Text><Text Key="A384130D">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nTravel the mortal realm in style with this faithful replica of the Grim Reaper's cruiser bike!</Text><Text Key="EFCBF858">Grim's Cruiser</Text><Text Key="39DF2632">Made from real stones gathered from a real field a long time ago. Don't ask when, it's not polite! Just ask it a very specific pop culture question that'll secretly give away how old it is.</Text><Text Key="7CA08DCD">Fieldstone Bonfire Pit</Text><Text Key="4CE84A33">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nOnce thought lost in the Von Haunt Estate fire of 1898, this treatise contains the secrets to making Ambrosia and appears to have been authored by Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot herself.</Text><Text Key="3FAD7762">The Green Lady's Lost Tome</Text><Text Key="8626DBC3">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nOnce thought lost in the Von Haunt Estate fire of 1898, this treatise contains the secrets to making Ambrosia and appears to have been authored Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot herself.</Text><Text Key="060ADE12">The Green Lady's Lost Tome</Text><Text Key="212C1873">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\n"Time waits for no Sim", but with the return of the classic Get Up! Alarm Clock you'll never be late because you lost track of time, again!\n\nSet it, forget it, and let this trusty gadget do the rest.</Text><Text Key="D8D5DFA2">Get Up! Alarm Clock</Text><Text Key="325A882C">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA supremely skeletal Freezer Boney. It would be much more terrifying to stumble upon one of these if they weren't so darn cute.</Text><Text Key="03714963">Original Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="4351BE79">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA Freezer Boney from beyond our solar system. Its plastic frame shimmers with the vastness of a distant galaxy.</Text><Text Key="3F61707C">Starborn Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="91D222CE">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA colorful Freezer Boney calavera, commemorating The Day of the Dead. This Freezer Boney is often placed upon the ofrendas of departed Sims.</Text><Text Key="E463CEF1">Sugar Skull Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="BE6DF4C3">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA Freezer Boney so shiny, you can see your reflection in it... assuming you have one.</Text><Text Key="93D2D912">Metallic Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="A5526458">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nAn exceptionally fluffy Freezer Boney for those cold nights when you want to curl up on the couch, wrap yourself in a cozy blanket, and ponder your own mortality.</Text><Text Key="D98996D7">Plush Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="9BD00CC5">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nSporting an eerie green glow, this Freezer Boney is the perfect companion for a late-night goth rave.</Text><Text Key="6E451BC0">Glow-in-the-Dark Freezer Boney</Text><Text Key="276D0358">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nMISSING?! What do you mean Bella is missing? Isn't she here? In her red dress? ...Where did this carton even come from? Is this a warning?</Text><Text Key="C34943D7">Bella Goth, Starry-Eyed Stargazer</Text><Text Key="1DEAABC5">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nPit of Judgement desperately seeking return of beloved tentacled beast known colloquially as Pit Beast, also answers to Steven.</Text><Text Key="5804C8C0">Pit Beast, Dweller in the Dark</Text><Text Key="BE935EFA">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nLast seen plundering...rustling cattle...writing tickets...extinguishing fires... Most likely to be found sailing the solar winds of space.</Text><Text Key="7479F9A5">Ginny, former Pirate and Sheriff</Text><Text Key="0C6933E7">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBlonde hair, blue eyes, kind of a neatnik. Last seen near the pool. His wife anxiously awaits his return but has offered no reward.</Text><Text Key="743EFD1E">Skip Broke, Prolific Father</Text><Text Key="B475272C">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nLast seen leaving the scene with a small sack of large furniture.</Text><Text Key="ED30F663">Some Sneaky Sim, Not a Raccoon</Text><Text Key="C56C5D79">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nKnown to pop in every now and then. Does not need roads. Answers to “Doctor” but doesn’t have a medical license.</Text><Text Key="29211D7C">Emit Relevart, Bow-Tied and Blue-Haired</Text><Text Key="B0144970">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThere is a reason why things become classics, they just stand the test of time. Put this festive wreath up and it'll bring that feeling of holiday nostalgia to your home.</Text><Text Key="B3F4C21F">Cozy Festive Wreath</Text><Text Key="11CB753D">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nLooking for something different while keeping it classy? This floral wreath not only looks good, but it also probably smells good too.</Text><Text Key="DDA565A8">Cozy Floral Wreath</Text><Text Key="A5341A92">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nBring that sense of playfulness the holidays bring to your decorations by putting up this Freezer Bunny adorned wreath.</Text><Text Key="72269CAD">Cozy Freezer Bunny Wreath</Text><Text Key="5BCF5CFF">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nNot quite ready to get into the full festive spirit? This wreath will give that autumn feeling, no matter the weather outside.</Text><Text Key="DC4F3026">Cozy Autumnal Wreath</Text><Text Key="4507EA8B">A time capsule left behind by a time traveling thief!</Text><Text Key="BA88220A">Special Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="ABE50622">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe ElectroDance Floor is the perfect excuse for you to show off your "Get down and Boogie" moves!\n\nGather your friends, and turn those ordinary garden parties into full-blown raves!</Text><Text Key="C78FA79D">The ElectroDance Floor</Text><Text Key="7F9FB4D4">If you needed a taller entryway with Prairie-style detailing, this is the perfect option.</Text><Text Key="45FA2FBB">Taller Prairie-Style Entry Frame</Text><Text Key="2E4E5243">Our tallest post-and-lintel frame fits just right in the loftiest of rooms.</Text><Text Key="CF027992">Tallest Prairie-Style Entry Frame</Text><Text Key="D1800C8E">This post-and-lintel entry frame is an extra half size wider and has the same Prairie-style detailing as our original frame.</Text><Text Key="A4DD46B1">Wider Prairie-Style Entry Frame</Text><Text Key="7B8CF493">Open up your space by adding this new entry frame, taller and wider than our original.</Text><Text Key="C933DA42">Taller and Wider Prairie-Style Entry Frame</Text><Text Key="5ABE5A64">The tallest and widest of our Prairie-style frames, the Tallest and Widest Prairie-style entry frame is taller and wider than the rest of the tall or wide Prairie-style frames. It's pretty tall and wide.</Text><Text Key="09D0B2AB">Tallest and Widest Prairie-Style Entry Frame</Text><Text Key="26D628B4">It took 241 doors to perfect our first addition to the Pointless Renovation line. Not to worry, 240 of those doors were repurposed to Plumbob Picture's next blockbuster: Day of the Doors! Where's door #241? We're guessing some starlet stole it.</Text><Text Key="D28AB51B">Door #242 by Pointless Renovation</Text><Text Key="5B51E73A">A group of kids won the opportunity to test this frame, and they took it to some kind of white sheet party. We're still finding leftover SugarFizz on it, but the good news is it holds up great.</Text><Text Key="E9B421E5">Door #118211 by Pointless Renovation</Text><Text Key="308C035C">Who needs a doggie door when this extra wide frame is perfect for bringing the outside in? At least that's what our fuzzy friends suggested in their testing feedback. Just be careful it doesn't let the smelly one in...</Text><Text Key="1E4DDE33">Door #51323 by Pointless Renovation</Text><Text Key="9A9655FF">Everyone loves an open concept floor plan, but when you're renting there's only so much you can change. We made this frame to slot right in and bring your rooms together. You know, your kitchen and living area, bedroom and bathroom, and even all four together! Who needs privacy!</Text><Text Key="EBD0CB26">Door #3125 by Pointless Renovation</Text><Text Key="8AAE358A">This door sorta just appeared one day. We don't know where it came from, and weird things have happened ever since, but we can't remove it so...Door #82728 it is.</Text><Text Key="12BC8995">Door #82728 by Pointless Renovation</Text><Text Key="742A2463">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This medium-height frame relies upon a load-bearing lintel to provide structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="A82AF132">Trabeated Entry Frame - Medium Height</Text><Text Key="495A1A81">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This extended-height frame utilizes a load-bearing lintel to maintain structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="850CACB4">Trabeated Entry Frame - Extended Height</Text><Text Key="245E2BEC">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This elevated-height frame depends upon a load-bearing lintel to ensure structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="2D372223">Trabeated Entry Frame - Elevated Height</Text><Text Key="48ECFEBF">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This wide, medium-height frame depends on a load-bearing lintel to ensure structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="3F8795E6">Trabeated Wide Entry Frame - Medium Height</Text><Text Key="ED80891C">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This wide, extended-height frame relies on a load-bearing lintel to provide structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="167EC6F3">Trabeated Wide Entry Frame - Extended Height</Text><Text Key="BE4D4171">A simple but effective example of a trabeated entryway. This wide, elevated-height frame uses a load-bearing lintel to provide structural integrity.</Text><Text Key="73DD8944">Trabeated Wide Entry Frame - Elevated Height</Text><Text Key="9BCE99BB">Can you bring it to the top?\nLike it never never stop?\nMove on through! Move on through!</Text><Text Key="C878FA1A">Cha Cha Mostly Tall Sliding Door</Text><Text Key="F42A3EDD">Our Facilities Door was so popular, we decided to expand your options. Place this anywhere you might need a door. It comes with kick protection!</Text><Text Key="FDB90EC8">Iconless Fiberglass Door</Text><Text Key="2A180810">Our perfect Iconless door, now without that flashy kick plate. Its plain and simple design allows it to be used almost anywhere!</Text><Text Key="FDCD133F">Kickless Fiberglass Door</Text><Text Key="0B874C66">Essence milked directly from Cowplants under the most humane conditions imaginable. Sometimes caretakers get eaten though. </Text><Text Key="98528EC1">Nothing's better on a cold night than a steaming mug of hot cocoa. Whether you cozy up with a blanket and a good book, or share a pot with a good group of friends, you're in for a particularly yummy treat.</Text><Text Key="481B8AF4">Cozy Hot Cocoa Tray</Text><Text Key="27C85B39">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA glass of Spectral Spritzer</Text><Text Key="FC97CB3C">Spectral Spritzer</Text><Text Key="64D69A2C">drinkTumblerShrt_SDX036GEN placeholder description</Text><Text Key="7BA4DF63">drinkTumblerShrt_SDX036GEN placeholder name</Text><Text Key="984DCDF2">A portion of Mucenici</Text><Text Key="0D0ABB8D">Mucenici</Text><Text Key="399E683B">Mămăligă</Text><Text Key="F94C23D7">Mucenici</Text><Text Key="91E4F2C4">Mămăligă</Text><Text Key="536629A8">Mucenici</Text><Text Key="73F07D8C">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThis colorful confection is sure to bring the ooh's and aah's, and maybe a little unexpected something surprising to the celebration!\n\nLight the Candles, Make a Wish, and be prepared for a little dancing!</Text><Text Key="1C23A843">Surprise Birthday Cake</Text><Text Key="6D365316">Surprise Birthday Cake</Text><Text Key="FE26C919">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe Super Dream Cube isn't trying to be the most powerful console on the market, but it definitely knows what it does best, retro games. With a game cartridge slot, a disc drive and a whole TWO controller ports for that couch gaming head-to-head you can be sure to relive some classic fun.</Text><Text Key="92B1209C">Super Dream Cube</Text><Text Key="5EC3C605">Game Console Controller</Text><Text Key="45A6FB00">Game Console Controller</Text><Text Key="E421F048">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA portrait of Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot enjoying an afternoon in the gardens of the Von Haunt estate. Some people say they've seen the painting move, but that's probably just an urban legend, right?</Text><Text Key="29B6A4E7">Portrait of Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot in the Garden</Text><Text Key="FABE3F84">Ambrosia Society Newsletter</Text><Text Key="7263C1DF">The Festive Hedge Row lets you form a seasonal barrier around your yard, perfect for keeping the grouches out and the festive feelings in. Go with one style for a standardized dignified look or mix it up a little with some color variations and let the neighbors look on in awe at your design choices.</Text><Text Key="6563C486">Festive Hedge Row</Text><Text Key="AF18523C">This festive topiary comes with all the benefits of the Starter Hedge with the added sparkle of that festive magic. Easy to maintain and lets everyone who comes by know that you are ready to celebrate the holiday season.</Text><Text Key="F83E8293">Festive Starter Hedge</Text><Text Key="8E693B4B">You helped the Grim Reaper research Ambrosia, and along the way you found six skeletal sidekicks. Grim sent along this plaque to help commemorate the completion of your Freezer Boney collection.</Text><Text Key="4C1090CA">"Freezer Boney Fanatic"</Text><Text Key="9C794DC2">Emit Relevart has taken note of your interest in the missing Sims from the past, and he has bestowed upon you this plaque so that they will not be forgotten.</Text><Text Key="4F29D3BD">"Missing not Forgotten"</Text><Text Key="5B4255ED">You helped Jasmine Holiday research festive traditions. While you were busy documenting and reporting what you discovered, you unlocked some festive decorations. Jasmine sent this plaque to recognize your achievement of completing the Cozy Wreaths collection.</Text><Text Key="1E3E09B8">"Festive Wreaths Aficionado"</Text><Text Key="6215C054">Shard of Time</Text><Text Key="FC155C95">A mysterious IOU note, left inside of a time capsule.</Text><Text Key="DC864CB0">IOU Note</Text><Text Key="C51547C0">Sent years ago, it's as though this letter has been waiting for just the right time.</Text><Text Key="B1C1499A">The past leaves echoes through time which manifest in these shards.</Text><Text Key="2859E4C6">The theoretical component needed to make time travel possible.</Text><Text Key="0A308D59">Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="892881DA">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nNothing prepares your guests for the Cozy Celebrations like the Festive Feeling Welcome Mat. Just make sure your guests use it before entering, no one likes cleaning muddy footprints.</Text><Text Key="BCF32505">Festive Feeling Welcome Mat</Text><Text Key="D14B1D46">Whether you're storing blankets for a chilly night, showing off your latest knitting pattern, or keeping heirloom quilts on display, the Comfy Blankets Quilt Stand is built to support your thickest blanket and bring an extra level of coziness to any comfy space.</Text><Text Key="B075CED9">Comfy Blankets Quilt Stand</Text><Text Key="865ED92E">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nRemember tangled chords, rotary dials, and tapping the receiver for a dial tone? The Retro-Deco Table Phone aims to bring you right back to that ancient era of pre-digital communications.\n\nExperience the memories of when busy signals were an everyday occurrence, the answering machine was still just a twinkle in the eye of a would be inventor, and call waiting meant waiting for your sibling to get off the phone so you could make a call.</Text><Text Key="C89125D1">Retro-Deco Table Phone</Text><Text Key="F09EF8AD">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe Retro-Deco Wall Phone is part of a two piece throw back set to when wireless meant stay near the phone base, phone screening was just in its infancy, and random Sims were calling to find out if your refrigerator was running.\n\nRelive those early days of carefree disconnection with the Retro-Deco Wall Phone.</Text><Text Key="F5B3B578">Retro-Deco Wall Phone</Text><Text Key="CF98810B">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nFeeling deflated? Inflate some fun with the Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part One!\n\nPart One combines quirky style and ultimate relaxation in one bouncy* package. Perfect for lounging, chatting, or sitting. Part One is sure to add a pop of personality to your space!\n\n*Does not support bouncing.</Text><Text Key="66311D8A">The Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part One</Text><Text Key="145C6EF8">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nComfort meets convenience with the Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part Two!\n\nDesigned to foster a relaxed atmosphere. Its soft contours and light material make Part Two perfect for lounging, napping, or kicking back for a playful night of movies and popcorn!</Text><Text Key="65FFCBF7">The Fun-Fun Inflatable Set, Part Two</Text><Text Key="6ACDF408">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Reaper's Rewards Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nA supernatural sound system with a direct line to Grim himself, allowing his mortal acquaintances to summon him day or night. It can also play your favorite tunes, if you're into that sort of thing.</Text><Text Key="44D144A7">The Grimophone</Text><Text Key="636B4308">&lt;font color= '#199C2C'&gt;From the Blast from the Past Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nThe Bigger Gatherings Banquet is your perfect choice for notching up your dinner parties, feasts, and shindigs to an eleven! This sturdy table ensures your gatherings always have a place for food, drinks, and socializing in style. Never ask, 'Where’s the food?' again.</Text><Text Key="3C3A01A7">Bigger Gatherings Banquet</Text><Text Key="F955CE0D">&lt;font color='#199C2C'&gt;From the Cozy Celebrations Event&lt;/font&gt;\n\nWith The Festive Frame TV you can impress your friends by showing how sophisticated you are by mounting this flat-screen TV, which doubles as a piece of art while it's off. When they are gone, turn it on and enjoy your shows or play console games on it.</Text><Text Key="198E3958">The Festive Frame TV</Text><Text Key="48714378">10 AM</Text><Text Key="12DEB3E7">10 PM</Text><Text Key="CB189F05">11 AM</Text><Text Key="C02CF7BE">12 AM</Text><Text Key="C6DBDB86">1 AM</Text><Text Key="57CABDED">2 AM</Text><Text Key="DF1D0EFE">2 PM</Text><Text Key="B15AFBC0">3 AM</Text><Text Key="35B490FF">4 AM</Text><Text Key="660DFCD0">4 PM</Text><Text Key="F253CD69">5 PM</Text><Text Key="642902A1">6 AM</Text><Text Key="1AAC4C03">7 PM</Text><Text Key="E8173CBE">9 AM</Text><Text Key="E4F6ABAD">9 PM</Text><Text Key="AF5AE16E">12 PM</Text><Text Key="AE6D5640">1 PM</Text><Text Key="B2F26272">3 PM</Text><Text Key="4A0764D3">5 AM</Text><Text Key="846789A5">7 AM</Text><Text Key="F07DE02A">8 AM</Text><Text Key="70C3A02F">11 PM</Text><Text Key="5831E919">6 PM</Text><Text Key="4F7ADF97">8 PM</Text><Text Key="2EB91F2C">Unsets all alarms on the alarm clock.</Text><Text Key="C8A37E9C">Unset Alarm Time</Text><Text Key="C8A6BB56">Sets the alarm for all Sims in the area.</Text><Text Key="A57F1ADF">Increases the effective range of the alarm.</Text><Text Key="69FF0BCD">Upgrade Speaker</Text><Text Key="0CC6A5AF">Upgrade complete!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has finished upgrading the alarm clock speaker.</Text><Text Key="968492B9">(From Viewing Portrait of Lady Mimsy Alcorn Shallot in the Garden)</Text><Text Key="3C73C61F">What's This?</Text><Text Key="8421F075">Serve Butter Chicken</Text><Text Key="CC54E118">Serve Challah</Text><Text Key="8A800261">Serve Minty Mocha Cupcakes</Text><Text Key="4962526E">Serve Vegetable Dumplings</Text><Text Key="AE5B5867">Bathe like a Ghostly Beast</Text><Text Key="5EE3C104">Bathe Ethereally</Text><Text Key="67458573">Hide in Cake</Text><Text Key="844D133B">Liberating Dance</Text><Text Key="ABCC6B7A">With The Green Lady's Tome, you can quickly gain the skills you need to cook Ambrosia! This book will build your Gardening, Cooking, and Gourmet Cooking skills.</Text><Text Key="95DFEE85">Read Book Intro</Text><Text Key="0D1B788A">Reading 'History of Time Travel'</Text><Text Key="22DBB556">Read "History of Time Travel"</Text><Text Key="E7A3738A">Reading Theoretical Electronics</Text><Text Key="2CBC6E56">Read Theoretical Electronics</Text><Text Key="2F951AC3">(From Being Naked at the Full Moon Revelry)</Text><Text Key="37C9F536">Only a vampire wants to start messing around in a coffin.</Text><Text Key="4E61450B">It can't be cleaned up while a Sim is hiding inside!</Text><Text Key="12BAF284">Death Frogs are not suitable for breeding.</Text><Text Key="8F1A6187">Dig for Special Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="484B2FE0">MISSING SIM\nName: Ginny, former Pirate and Sheriff\n\nLast seen plundering...rustling cattle...writing tickets...extinguishing fires... Most likely to be found sailing the solar winds.</Text><Text Key="FB0730F2">MISSING SIM\nName: Bella Goth, Starry-Eyed Stargazer\n\nMISSING?! What do you mean Bella is missing? Isn't she here?  In her red dress? ...Where did this carton even come from?</Text><Text Key="DA3951B9">MISSING SIM\nName: Skip Broke\n\nBlonde hair, blue eyes, kind of a neatnik. Last seen near the pool. His wife anxiously awaits his return but has offered no reward.</Text><Text Key="CAA993E2">MISSING SIM\nName: Some Sneaky Sim, Not a Raccoon\n\nLast seen leaving the scene with a small sack of large furniture.</Text><Text Key="C6FBF63B">MISSING SIM\nName: Emit Relevart\n\nKnown to pop in every now and then. Does not need roads. Answers to “Doctor” but doesn’t have a medical license.</Text><Text Key="8C7BB072">MISSING SIM\nName: Pit Beast, Dweller in the Dark\n\nPit of Judgement desperately seeking return of beloved tentacled beast known colloquially as Pit Beast.</Text><Text Key="1B746F8A">Research Shards of Time</Text><Text Key="FEB63BA1">Document the Research</Text><Text Key="3FE0C55E">While different cultures have all formed their own traditions around celebrating the festive season, common themes have emerged: Gathering of close friends and family, traditional food and drink, and listening to festive music. All of which feature heavily although the specifics and significance of these vary according to each culture.</Text><Text Key="897C6BEF">Research Holiday Traditions</Text><Text Key="A0808B67">Share the Discoveries with Jasmine</Text><Text Key="25D8538C">Play The Sims Archives</Text><Text Key="C0E6FB57">Play The Sims Archives, vol. 2</Text><Text Key="1506C1E1">Play The Sims Archives, vol. 4</Text><Text Key="E96F5536">The Death Flower is the Grim Reaper's favorite flower. If you offer it when a Sim is dying, the Grim Reaper will allow the dying Sim to continue living.\n\nIt can be grown by grafting a Pomegranate to an Orchid.</Text><Text Key="6282E7A4">Ambrosia is a Gourmet dish that can bring a loved one back to life. It is difficult to make and requires 3 rare ingredients.\n\nIf you want to learn more, be sure to read the Ambrosia Society Newsletter!</Text><Text Key="BBFB48B0">Research Ambrosia</Text><Text Key="11CBD883">Activate Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="6D067529">Send Time Traveling Email </Text><Text Key="A22F1AE9">Check Emit's Profile</Text><Text Key="3F75AF4C">Ingest {1.ObjectName}</Text><Text Key="8C04485B">Wolfishly Ingest {1.ObjectName}</Text><Text Key="69B8E0CC">Music must be playing nearby to perform this interaction.</Text><Text Key="01B3325D">Begin a new chapter of Life by becoming a Ghost! Exciting Ghostly Powers await in the Afterlife. Perhaps {0.SimFirstName} has some Unfinished Business to attend to? You can also choose to relinquish control of {0.SimFirstName} and allow {0.SimPronounObjective} to stick around as a Freeroaming Ghost.</Text><Text Key="C35D9472">{0.SimFirstName} has passed away!</Text><Text Key="519CDC74">&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is your soul ready to embrace the next chapter?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;\n\nBy choosing to Rebirth, you will set forth on a new journey as a new Sim, leaving your current life behind with no chance of return. You will be taken to Manage Worlds to select the household where your new life will unfold and will have the opportunity to fully customize your reborn self in Create a Sim. While funds, relationships, and achievements from this life will be lost, if you have already unlocked the coveted &lt;b&gt;Burning Soul&lt;/b&gt; trait, you’ll be able to retain one personality trait with the &lt;b&gt;Recall Past Life&lt;/b&gt; self-interaction, along with certain others using the &lt;b&gt;Peer Into Soul&lt;/b&gt; interaction available on mirrors. If you choose to Rebirth as a younger Sim, certain developmental skills will be immediately unlocked!\n\nNow the threads of fate lie before you. The choice to weave a new destiny can be made when you are ready. &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Will you choose to Rebirth now?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="6A691CBE">Cancel the Rebirth flow.</Text><Text Key="7492D540">No, do not Rebirth now.</Text><Text Key="FCD61ECC">Yes, Rebirth now.</Text><Text Key="60B365F3">Become a Freeroaming Ghost</Text><Text Key="EA481D18">Become a Freeroaming Ghost\nThe Sim becomes a Ghostly presence around the Household and in the World. They will no longer be playable.\n&lt;font color='#FF0000'&gt;&lt;b&gt;Warning! This will lead to a Game Over state, as this Sim is the only Sim in this Household.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</Text><Text Key="1FA2902F">Become a Freeroaming Ghost\nThe Sim becomes a Ghostly presence around the Household and in the World. They will no longer be playable.</Text><Text Key="D8DC56C9">Become a Playable Ghost</Text><Text Key="C474A3AD">Remain a Playable Ghost\nThe Sim will stay in the Household and continue to be playable as a Ghostly presence in the current Household.</Text><Text Key="AC250BDC">{0.SimFirstName} is no longer playable. Do you want to...</Text><Text Key="B47403BA">{0.SimFirstName} Is No Longer Playable</Text><Text Key="74C1C862">Rummage</Text><Text Key="3D01E246">Ask to Start Playing Music</Text><Text Key="D146E5E6">Ask to Stop Playing Music</Text><Text Key="00FFA755">Perfect food cannot be spoiled!</Text><Text Key="2F082586">Spread Delicious Sauce</Text><Text Key="F39D4A30">Grafting requires a healthy plant to take a cutting from. Once you have that cutting, just graft it onto another healthy plant and watch it grow!\n\nBe sure to Research Grafting to see what grafting combinations you can get!</Text><Text Key="434C2452">Research Grafting</Text><Text Key="9AF1499A">{0.SimFirstName} is only temporarily a Ghost and can't consume Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="10D1505E">(From Spectral Spritzer)</Text><Text Key="4991B0B6">PLACEHOLDER TEXT: FAILURE. OBJECT BROKEN</Text><Text Key="100DAD59">(From Debug in the Baleful Bog)</Text><Text Key="6BA8C305">Sim cannot be a ghost already.</Text><Text Key="3A4449BB">Sim must be TYAE.</Text><Text Key="A11A61BD">This interaction will add interred Ghost to the current household.</Text><Text Key="F7BDF4C5">Reflect on Former Long Life</Text><Text Key="897EEAAD">Set Ghost Color</Text><Text Key="9DB046EC">{0.SimFirstName} needs level 2 Handiness skill to build this.</Text><Text Key="B7B28E14">{0.SimFirstName} needs level 2 Logic skill to build this.</Text><Text Key="5AE2271A">Build Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="78220465">Open</Text><Text Key="462EF041">Read IOU</Text><Text Key="FF610F1F">To {0.SimName},\n\nI didn't mean to worry anyone. I know I should have asked before I did what I did. I was really just trying to save stuff from the past for the future, and have some fun!\n\nI'm sure we'll run into each other...in time. Gotta run! I have some things to pickup.\n\n- Sincerely, the Thief</Text><Text Key="4218EAB3">Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="7AD3D7FA">Read Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="2AE8B69C">Turn On Auto-Switch</Text><Text Key="F98E705F">Toggles the automatic visual change for urns and gravestones. Turning this off allows gravestones to be placed indoors/urns to be placed outdoors without automatically switching.</Text><Text Key="33428C4D">Turn Off Auto-Switch</Text><Text Key="AFCD1DF1">Bare-Naked Moonbathe</Text><Text Key="D3B308A7">Request Replacement Ambrosia Society Newsletter</Text><Text Key="8B9F6046">Replace IOU</Text><Text Key="500E03B7">Get Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="46AB0C58">Replace Electronic Upgrade Part</Text><Text Key="B2D8870E">{0.SimFirstName} already has this item.</Text><Text Key="0C99ED8E">Replace Ironyum</Text><Text Key="521BCFDB">Replace Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="EA05F339">Replace Plathinum</Text><Text Key="53880FD3">Replace Shard of Time</Text><Text Key="6131311B">Replace Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="BEF16955">Replace or retrieve a quest item.</Text><Text Key="0B38218F">Replace Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="5A42EF25">Ask to Cloudgaze</Text><Text Key="C4ABA72C">Ask to Stargaze</Text><Text Key="21B722A5">Greet Familiar Face</Text><Text Key="AB3A1BFB">Accuse of Being a Time Traveler</Text><Text Key="EEA7A08D">Ask to Stay Married</Text><Text Key="40A35C45">Spread Rumor about Others</Text><Text Key="02A99E57">Try for New Pirates in Coffin</Text><Text Key="8E837398">Try For Baby in Coffin</Text><Text Key="8EE86A86">Good Sims don't want to coffin woohoo.</Text><Text Key="44A972CA">Heave Ho in Coffin</Text><Text Key="0CF1B17D">Who would want to do THAT in THERE?!</Text><Text Key="23FEFBCF">Mess Around in Coffin</Text><Text Key="E9215C19">WooHoo in Coffin</Text><Text Key="837B2370">Being Accused of Time Travel by {1.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="F206CC0D">{0.SimFirstName}'s search came up empty this time. {0.SimPronounSubjective} can try again, or search another Object for a Shard of Time.</Text><Text Key="E8AD536C">Nothing Found</Text><Text Key="9EAC9C85">{0.SimFirstName} found a Shard of Time!\n\nIt has been added to {0.SimPronounPossessiveDependent} inventory!</Text><Text Key="0B5E6F9A">Shard of Time Found</Text><Text Key="2620DDC0">Search for Shard of Time</Text><Text Key="636B9874">Select Gravestone</Text><Text Key="CFE5791D">Gravestone</Text><Text Key="A1A65F42">Select Urn</Text><Text Key="902F0DA7">Urn</Text><Text Key="5E6A820F">Display as</Text><Text Key="CB5CCDD7">Urn and Gravestone Inventory</Text><Text Key="14BA94CE">Inheritance Lawyer has already been hired.</Text><Text Key="9A36773B">Order a Death Flower</Text><Text Key="0205D5B2">Your mail will arrive shortly!</Text><Text Key="B91D560B">Expedite Mail Delivery</Text><Text Key="57B5CC17">Dear Buyer,\n\nThank you for embracing the natural benefits of crystals. By asking yourself what conscious lifestyle improvements you can make (and by buying our crystals), you're one step closer to true self-empowerment. We're proud to be part of your journey here at Celestial Prosperity. \n\nCeleste Moonglade\nCEO &amp; Founder\n\n&lt;i&gt;The crystals {0.SimFirstName} purchased can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="82285F25">Purchase Crystals</Text><Text Key="50DA11D4">The Grim Reaper is currently unavailable to be summoned through the Grimophone.</Text><Text Key="92BA8D43">Summon the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="059DB85D">Overclock</Text><Text Key="2659D079">Play Party Frenzy Together</Text><Text Key="1275211D">Play Genie's Curse Together</Text><Text Key="ECB11043">Play MySims Racing Together</Text><Text Key="B2B3901C">Play Density Effect Together</Text><Text Key="847C4550">Watch Game Together</Text><Text Key="0173DA1F">Yell Angrily</Text><Text Key="4FCA7677">Awkwardly View</Text><Text Key="281CE51C">Bawl Uncontrollably</Text><Text Key="37E069F5">Confusion</Text><Text Key="61A56C2C">Disgusted</Text><Text Key="DEBB3D90">Curiously Indifferent</Text><Text Key="93F940BB">React to Becoming a Ghost</Text><Text Key="90390DF3">(From Witnessing Ghost Resurrection)</Text><Text Key="49590E1B">Sadistic Glee</Text><Text Key="5BEF8F9E">Wry Smirk</Text><Text Key="D4938C0A">Sniffle Cry</Text><Text Key="BEB2C8FE">Stoic Face</Text><Text Key="D1A3D033">Weep</Text><Text Key="EFC2D909">React to Ghost</Text><Text Key="EE6AEACE">(From Becoming a Ghost)</Text><Text Key="32F759EA">What shall this coffin say of its owner?</Text><Text Key="188F0D98">Cannot restock when tray is full.</Text><Text Key="CB65A8C8">Restock with Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="510847E0">Restock with Hot Cocoa with Marshmallows</Text><Text Key="FD9DC06F">Restock with Peppermint Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="92E47951">Restock with Spiced Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="0FD966BC">Restock with Vegan Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="6996AF34">Restock with Vegan Hot Cocoa with Marshmallows</Text><Text Key="97B13873">Aww... No more hot beverages left...</Text><Text Key="23BAC297">Grab Drink</Text><Text Key="D2E08C64">Exchange your collectibles for Simoleons! Get a great price for your treasures!</Text><Text Key="53C58E78">Thanks a bunch for the trade! Pleasure doing business with you friend!</Text><Text Key="051F96EC">Sell Your Collectibles</Text><Text Key="60217935">Wildly Cleanse Apparition</Text><Text Key="0C9E8E55">Cleanse Apparition</Text><Text Key="B740ABFA">Ponder Time Travel</Text><Text Key="182D01DC">Extinguish flames of all kinds from being a Death by Fire Ghost.</Text><Text Key="F79E280C">Extinguish Flames</Text><Text Key="1AC99E9E">Create a snack in the inventory from being a Death by Hunger Ghost.</Text><Text Key="0FF2EDD2">Grab Snack from the Netherworld</Text><Text Key="31A3A529">Increase or decrease mood duration from being Death by Old Age Ghost.</Text><Text Key="E79800AC">Warn of Danger</Text><Text Key="DB411A2B">Just a friendly warning from beyond, water can be tricky! Swim with caution and stay safe. The Netherworld isn't calling for you just yet.\nStay vigilant,\n{0.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="2CD91D45">You're surrounded by crackling electricity now! As a ghost who knows a thing or two about that, I'd suggest stepping back before it gives you a jolt.\nStay Safe,\n{0.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="05B4FC1D">As a ghost, I must warn you of imminent danger. Elder exhaustion is creeping closer. Take heed and rest well, for the Netherworld calls not yet.\nYours in ghostly vigilance,\n{0.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="9CB569CA">(From Being Skeptical)</Text><Text Key="8AE012AA">Cloudgaze Together</Text><Text Key="5834C033">Stargaze Together</Text><Text Key="AB24924C">Welcome to the final edition of our newsletter! It's time for all your hard work to pay off. Cook Ambrosia from the Gourmet Cooking recipes.\n\nOnce it's cooked, you can bring a ghost back to life with this magical dish!</Text><Text Key="3D9C8AE6">Aspiration Lesson</Text><Text Key="0C5D8318">This week, the Death Flower should be just within reach.\n\nWhile you're waiting for it to grow, make sure you continue working on your Cooking and Gourmet Cooking skills! They will come in handy when you're eventually ready to cook Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="EC5E7CBC">Another week, another newsletter! This week it's time to catch the first ingredient, an Angelfish!\n\nAmbrosia is a gourmet dish, so it's time to learn the Gourmet Cooking skill.\n\nIs your garden blossoming? Ambrosia requires a Death Flower, so this week, you will also need to graft an Orchid and Pomegranate plant.</Text><Text Key="6B21D92A">This week we are getting the final details rounded out before we are ready to cook Ambrosia! You need to max out your Cooking and Gourmet Cooking skills before you attempt to cook up the dish next week.</Text><Text Key="4C8491AA">Fishing Lesson</Text><Text Key="3E4BC8C8">This week, we continue to work on Gardening. You'll also need to make sure you start getting Satisfaction Points, you'll need them later!\n\nAmbrosia requires some creative plant manipulation, so you should also grab a cutting of Lily and Snapdragon this week. Check out Magnolia Blossom Park in Willow Creek to find some wild Lily and Snapdragon.</Text><Text Key="C3DEA665">Cooking Lesson</Text><Text Key="4FC40C09">Ambrosia Society Newsletter</Text><Text Key="28569837">Welcome to our latest series, where we guide you through the process of cooking Ambrosia!\n\nIf you have your Snapdragon planted then the next step is to work on your Cooking and Gardening Skills. The best way to do this is to feed your garden and yourself!</Text><Text Key="2DE7D237">Aspiration Lesson</Text><Text Key="82BE095B">Gardening Lesson</Text><Text Key="51C90F98">Object is already in use.</Text><Text Key="7239015B">Listen to {1.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="1F3117DA">Hey there! I’m on the lookout for all things &lt;B&gt;Science and Nature&lt;/B&gt;! I’ll buy cool stuff like:\n• Frogs\n• Space Prints\n• Crystals\n• Fossils\n• Plants\n• Fish</Text><Text Key="9227DFEF">Ask about Collections</Text><Text Key="73DDE525">Sell Collectibles</Text><Text Key="9DB48568">{0.SimFirstName} must be in a better mood first.</Text><Text Key="DE56DD50">Proclaim Best Date Ever!</Text><Text Key="E44B9387">My tradition may seem a little boring to some but since this time of year can be so hectic I mainly look forward to just relaxing with others and watching TV!</Text><Text Key="69AE9AFD">In my home, you could tell it was that time of the season when all you heard playing on the stereo was the Winter Holiday Station. It was a magical time!</Text><Text Key="87EEAD53">What do I look forward to the most during the holidays? Definitely the food, and while I enjoy the classics, I like to try traditional foods from different cultures as well.</Text><Text Key="B3CA8CCA">My festive traditions? I guess the thing I most fondly remember and always look forward to is getting together and playing some retro video games. They don't make them like they used to!</Text><Text Key="B41BCAF3">For me, the festive season is about getting together with those that mean the most to me. A house full of singing festive songs and dancing together with friends and family is what the holidays have always been about!</Text><Text Key="4C726E36">Ask about Holiday Traditions</Text><Text Key="A8BB62E6">Have a Nice Chat about Holiday Traditions</Text><Text Key="9C6BF624">Talk about Holiday Songs</Text><Text Key="92F1C9DB">Ask about Ambrosia</Text><Text Key="8FED7BDC">Ask about Shard</Text><Text Key="F2FFF0A7">Report on Experiment</Text><Text Key="8C406D15">Ask about Missing Items</Text><Text Key="7E81AEAB">Ask about Malfunction</Text><Text Key="19E5447A">Report about Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="4AE84F68">Tell about Thief's True Intentions</Text><Text Key="A873617A">Say Goodbye</Text><Text Key="AFE65148">Introduce Yourself</Text><Text Key="52D05F80">Ask about Missing Items</Text><Text Key="A5710499">Show Shards of Time</Text><Text Key="97B4D1A3">Ask about Emit</Text><Text Key="3BFA8DBA">Commiserate About Losing Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="274AB4D2">Commiserate About Losing MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="89ECB637">Commiserate About Losing</Text><Text Key="8953E6D7">Congratulate on Winning Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="86489813">Congratulate on Winning MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="76DC8B74">Congratulate on Winning Game</Text><Text Key="5E0CC1CF">Brag About Winning Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="23F9D34B">Brag About Winning MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="6273636C">Brag About Winning Game</Text><Text Key="44F90E92">Enthuse About Winning Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="B1FA43EA">Enthuse About Winning MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="BB890B35">Enthuse About Winning Game</Text><Text Key="3776BA83">Emit Grouch Aura</Text><Text Key="ACF48D26">Cloudgaze</Text><Text Key="53CA522F">Stargaze</Text><Text Key="88B67D8B">Stargaze in the Buff</Text><Text Key="6D2FB445">Dance of the Dead</Text><Text Key="AC1F86F5">Deathly Beastie Boogie</Text><Text Key="F3C62945">Surprise!</Text><Text Key="80AB50B4">(From Sticky Fingers Aspiration)</Text><Text Key="B689BB62">Expel Ghostly Feral Waste</Text><Text Key="DFFB914B">Expel Goo Waste</Text><Text Key="85742BBF">This isn't high enough quality for the refined tastes {0.SimFirstName} possesses.</Text><Text Key="47F2E596">In order to declare such a thing, {0.SimFirstName} needs to max out the Skill used to craft it.</Text><Text Key="AD327061">Permanently remove {0.SimFirstName} by returning to the Netherworld. This interaction cannot be undone.</Text><Text Key="6181100E">This vending machine is stocked with an assortment of quick snacks and small meals.</Text><Text Key="A6F05942">Repair or Replace the {1.ObjectName}.</Text><Text Key="CC7F1016">{1.ObjectName} is Broken!</Text><Text Key="EC675154">Replace the {1.ObjectName}.</Text><Text Key="7E551B2A">{1.ObjectName} is Burnt!</Text><Text Key="4D96ECC6">{1.ObjectName} is Disconnected!</Text><Text Key="D6AE7298">Disable Wireless Display Override</Text><Text Key="67B8B54C">Enable Wireless Display Override</Text><Text Key="06279BAE">{0.SimFirstName} must finish the current game before starting a new one!</Text><Text Key="72BFC7C8">Already Playing {1.ObjectName}</Text><Text Key="AF25ECDE">Joining</Text><Text Key="E326D88F">Join a Game of MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="4CC71096">Join a Game of Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="A6CCC9E8">Cannot Join Density Effect</Text><Text Key="4E78941A">Join Game</Text><Text Key="E2602AE6">Waiting to Join Game</Text><Text Key="D84ADAAC">Playing Genie's Curse</Text><Text Key="40E7C6CC">Play Genie's Curse</Text><Text Key="00851DE1">Forcing Self to Play Genie's Curse</Text><Text Key="F78FAF4B">Force Self to Play Genie's Curse</Text><Text Key="B01642E2">Forcing Self to Play Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="70F7B52E">Force Self to Play Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="2115F4CE">Forcing Self to Play MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="6B2B370A">Force Self to Play MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="DD13FF81">Forcing Self to Play Density Effect</Text><Text Key="1E87C9EB">Force Self to Play Density Effect</Text><Text Key="3C81DE60">Playing Multiplayer Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="80A64344">Playing Multiplayer MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="F8426FC1">Everyone loses a game now and then. It happens! {0.SimFirstName} unfortunately lost at this game.</Text><Text Key="B305C518">The game isn't over! Did the servers just disconnect?</Text><Text Key="3C90CBF1">It was a tight competition, but {0.SimFirstName} saving that power-up for the last few seconds was a smart move. {M0.His}{F0.Her} opponents didn’t see it coming!</Text><Text Key="AF75C899">Wow, that was pretty pathetic. A group of annoying teenagers that joined the online match were laughing at how bad {0.SimFirstName} was the whole time!</Text><Text Key="0ADE1014">Zap! Vroom! Dag Dag! {0.SimFirstName} demolished the competition in a display of virtual mastery. No one will be calling {M0.him}{F0.her} a n00b anytime soon.</Text><Text Key="063A15FA">“ALL THE POINTS ARE BELONG TO {0.SimFirstName|xxAllCaps},” the game proclaims, in a big retro font, as the match ends. {0.SimFirstName} is a digital champion!</Text><Text Key="0B8842D0">At the end of a very close match, {0.SimFirstName} just couldn’t pull it together for the win. Better luck next time!</Text><Text Key="2D7DCFDB">Playing Online Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="8B414171">Playing Online MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="C335BBF3">Playing Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="E91C57E9">Play Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="99A33D89">Playing MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="6C7B8E33">Play MySims Racing</Text><Text Key="D543736C">Playing Density Effect</Text><Text Key="B885350C">Play Density Effect</Text><Text Key="96622597">The Tournament isn't over! Did the servers just disconnect?</Text><Text Key="2702B057">Playing in Novice Genie's Curse Tournament</Text><Text Key="7B011D4D">Novice Genie's Curse Tournament</Text><Text Key="B7FA2CA4">Playing in Novice Party Frenzy Tournament</Text><Text Key="83F10E04">Novice Party Frenzy Tournament</Text><Text Key="665C1DF3">Playing in Pro Genie's Curse Tournament</Text><Text Key="2DC02DE9">Pro Genie's Curse Tournament</Text><Text Key="37130E90">Playing in Pro Party Frenzy Tournament</Text><Text Key="F4D32950">Pro Party Frenzy Tournament</Text><Text Key="D0F96AB4">Playing in Pro MySims Racing Tournament</Text><Text Key="75C14D94">Pro MySims Racing Tournament</Text><Text Key="2A6D46D3">Playing in Pro Density Effect Tournament</Text><Text Key="9B692EC9">Pro Density Effect Tournament</Text><Text Key="19A6A478">Playing in Novice MySims Racing Tournament</Text><Text Key="2A5A4DD8">Novice MySims Racing Tournament</Text><Text Key="42985D37">Playing in Novice Density Effect Tournament</Text><Text Key="962FC02D">Novice Density Effect Tournament</Text><Text Key="0730C567">No one is around to play games with {0.SimFirstName}.</Text><Text Key="53134B0A">Play Party Frenzy With</Text><Text Key="C9C811A4">Play Party Frenzy With {3.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="F55D0746">Play MySims Racing With</Text><Text Key="D7CFF550">Play MySims Racing With {3.SimFirstName}</Text><Text Key="CA3D8B98">No one {0.SimFirstName} knows is online right now.</Text><Text Key="499C5ACF">Play Party Frenzy Online With</Text><Text Key="769DA599">Play MySims Racing Online With</Text><Text Key="566D5705">Things might need to be toned down for a bit.</Text><Text Key="2A7823AC">Turn Off {1.ObjectName}</Text><Text Key="EA68ACF2">Place the {1.ObjectName} closer to an unpaired Television.</Text><Text Key="739AE9EE">Allows this device to take control over the display of nearby video screens</Text><Text Key="FACD31E2">Install Wireless Display Override</Text><Text Key="FD80EF24">Wireless Display Override (Completed)</Text><Text Key="3B535396">Resume Installing Wireless Display Override</Text><Text Key="B0605B32">Don't forget to tighten up the graphics for more fun!</Text><Text Key="09934F3E">Tighten Up Graphics</Text><Text Key="96E84758">Tighten Up Graphics (Completed)</Text><Text Key="00654F32">Resume Tightening Up Graphics</Text><Text Key="A026EC07">No more rings of any color when your console is Unbreakable!</Text><Text Key="18F22235">Unbreakable Upgrade</Text><Text Key="80E9FA71">Unbreakable (Completed)</Text><Text Key="2F6CDCDF">Resume Unbreakable Upgrade</Text><Text Key="81C04CA7">Watching Game</Text><Text Key="030D305D">Watch Game</Text><Text Key="43F5392D">The original Affluista Mansion lot, home of the Landgraab Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="BF67FDF7">Affluista Mansion - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="1EFCB1BC">The updated Affluista Mansion lot, home of the Landgraab Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="83010556">Affluista Mansion</Text><Text Key="2E66873B">The original Cacti Casa lot, home of the Roomies Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="5AB0D5C1">Cacti Casa - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="35FC6272">The updated Cacti Casa lot, home of the Roomies Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="E1C55CE0">Cacti Casa</Text><Text Key="2D3D428E">The original Cypress Terrace lot, home of the Spencer-Kim-Lewis Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="D0F2A974">Cypress Terrace - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="97F92B4F">The updated Cypress Terrace lot, home of the Spencer-Kim-Lewis Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="1C87F98D">Cypress Terrace</Text><Text Key="EF92740C">The original Garden Essence lot, home of the BFF Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="7434CA86">Garden Essence - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="F46347DD">The updated Garden Essence lot, home of the BFF Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="90740F47">Garden Essence</Text><Text Key="8CF24A03">The original Ophelia Villa lot, home of the Goth Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="F9947B69">Ophelia Villa - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="CEBEDA9A">The updated Ophelia Villa lot, home of the Goth Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="7A3057A8">Ophelia Villa</Text><Text Key="49D5D48D">The original Pique Hearth lot, home of the Pancakes Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="C5489957">Pique Hearth - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="8148841C">The updated Pique Hearth lot, home of the Pancakes Household in Willow Creek!</Text><Text Key="E54B44B6">Pique Hearth</Text><Text Key="8DA3BF7C">The original Slipshod Mesquite lot, home of the Zest Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="F1A67F16">Slipshod Mesquite - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="F67DD4ED">The updated Slipshod Mesquite lot, home of the Zest Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="71EF05B7">Slipshod Mesquite</Text><Text Key="B15591F2">The original Sultry Springside lot, home of the Caliente Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="5D1E8C60">Sultry Springside - Legacy Version</Text><Text Key="D4E6A963">The updated Sultry Springside lot, home of the Caliente Household in Oasis Springs!</Text><Text Key="4188D9C9">Sultry Springside</Text><Text Key="00E155FF">Peel back the veil to uncover the secret to richer Sim lives and beyond in The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death Expansion Pack. Achieve your dreams in life by ticking items off your Bucket List or pursue them as a Ghost with Unfinished Business. There is a ghastly new world to haunt, a career that'll bring you closer to Grim, Wills to write, Crypts to explore, and even ghostly skills to master. There are no real endings — only transitions — as you move between life, afterlife, and even rebirth.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Expansion Pack Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;An Endless Journey&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Ghastly, Gorgeous Life&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goodbye (For Now)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Friendly or Fiendish?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Town Worth Haunting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="64D08E5D">The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death</Text><Text Key="0160E18C">Peel back the veil to uncover the secret to richer Sim lives and beyond in The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death Expansion Pack. Achieve your dreams in life by ticking items off your Bucket List or pursue them as a Ghost with Unfinished Business. There is a ghastly new world to haunt, a career that'll bring you closer to Grim, Wills to write, Crypts to explore, and even ghostly skills to master. There are no real endings — only transitions — as you move between life, afterlife, and even rebirth.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Macabre Mementos Digital Content:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lasting Legacy Family Portrait&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mournful Melodies Music Box&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plumed Elegance Mask&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;\n\nWonder at treasures that have endured time's passing, witnessing the come and go of generations with ghastly grace. Look upon those who came before in the Lasting Legacy Family Portrait, listen to the haunting lullaby of the Mournful Melodies Music Box, and masquerade in fowl finery with the Plumed Elegance Mask, available when you order through December 12.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Expansion Pack Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;An Endless Journey&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Ghastly, Gorgeous Life&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goodbye (For Now)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Friendly or Fiendish?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Town Worth Haunting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="86033806">The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death</Text><Text Key="FAEF46FE">Design an inspiring space for Sims to hone their creative skills with The Sims™ 4 Artist Studio Kit. Your easel is surrounded by the tools of your trade – brushes, paint cans, still life references and more all scattered artfully, just the way you like it. You know your studio – its clutter, its drawers and shelves, and every drop of splattered paint – because you’ve left your mark on it, just like your canvas.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;An Artist’s Tools – Give your Sims more ways to express their creativity. There’s a new easel, tablet, and woodworking table for Sims to use in their artistic endeavors. Place inspiring still-life references, a backdrop, and other props to really help your creativity flow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Artful Décor – Add an artistic flourish to your canvas and your studio. Add paint splatter to the ground and clutter items like palettes, cans, tubes, brushes, and stacked sketch books to every shelf and corner.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="0359EB81">The Sims™ 4 Artist Studio Kit</Text><Text Key="BF1CA9F6">Surround new additions to the family with the elegance they deserve in The Sims™ 4 Storybook Nursery Kit. This nursery is a refined space that instills a sense of sophistication, featuring ornate furniture as well as whimsical toys. Made in collaboration with creator SixamCC, this collection balances the joy of a new arrival with elevated charm. Some items even pay homage to the lore and legacy of The Sims.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Touch of Whimsy – Inspired by classic fairy tales and the elegance of ages past, this collection features delicately crafted toys, pleasant wallpaper, a dreamy mobile, and a dollhouse modeled after the traditional home of an old, prominent family.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Legacy of Elegance – Raise your little one among ornate furniture including shelves and a changing table. Some of these items, like the crib with the sweeping canopy and the tasteful chandelier, may have been passed down through the generations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="86BB5B29">The Sims™ 4 Storybook Nursery Kit</Text><Text Key="5F249DAF">Look stylish and cute even when the venue of your party is your own bedroom with The Sims™ 4 Sweet Slumber Party Kit. The pastel colors, fluffy fabrics, adorable designs and patterns will make you feel like you are in an actual dream. Complete your sleepwear attire with cute nail designs, fuzzy socks and slippers and fun skincare items. Created by Trillyke.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cozy and Stylish – Whether your Sim prefers comfy and soft loungewear or the most delicate silk attire, these dreamy looks make them feel cozy and stylish during an overnight stay with friends. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dreamy Nighttime Routine – Level up your skincare routine with pore strips, sparkly under eye masks and star shaped acne patches.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="3FEE65F6">The Sims™ 4 Sweet Slumber Party Kit</Text><Text Key="25A68507">Embrace vibrant colors and mid-century modern design with The Sims™ 4 Cozy Kitsch Kit. Inspired by the 60s and the 70s, this collection of living room items features bold color and pattern combinations, stylish surfaces, and cute décor with delightful character. Add subtle accents to your room, or make a statement with every piece. Created by myshunosun.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Play With Color – Show off trinkets on a chic faux fireplace, tune your vintage radio to your beloved station, and cozy up on your favorite corduroy sofa. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make A Statement – Decorate your room with bold artwork and a daring neon sign. Combine sleek mid-century surfaces with unique heirloom finds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="21E4EABE">The Sims™ 4 Cozy Kitsch Kit</Text><Text Key="1D51C76B">Settle in for a cozy time at the computer with The Sims™ 4 Comfy Gamer Kit. With this collection you’ll craft warm, inviting spaces that feel personal with a large desk, playful clutter items, and of course a comfy gaming chair. This kit was created in collaboration with lilsimsie to be fun and relaxing with subtle references to The Sims.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Personal Touch – Use the décor in this kit to make your computer area feel homey, relaxing, and completely yours with plants, clutter, and gaming accessories. There are even cubed cubbies for displaying knickknacks and other treasured items that make you happy!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Little Sims-y – Who wouldn’t want a mini cow plant hanging over their head? This kit has all kinds of callouts to The Sims, including a grilled cheese mini-library and an adorable alarm clock.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="F9AB786A">The Sims™ 4 Comfy Gamer Kit</Text><Text Key="15F58B60">Indulge in iconic fashion and enchanting décor with The Sims™ 4 Secret Sanctuary Kit. Create a luxurious space full of opulent furniture concealed behind a secret passage in a bookcase. When you’re inside your hideaway, let the world melt away as you relax on your chaise lounge or try on polished Italian-inspired fashions in your floor-length mirror.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;An Opulent Oasis – This is a private retreat featuring a mysterious hidden entrance, elegant antique vanity, charming tea set, and more high-end touches sure to delight Sims with a sense of refinement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flawlessly Fashionable – These finely-tailored Italian-inspired fashions are polished, sophisticated, and feature classic silhouettes. It’s a cohesive collection that feels curated, as if hand-picked by someone with exquisite taste.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="D53750AF">The Sims™ 4 Secret Sanctuary Kit</Text><Text Key="4E2EE181">Impress guests with a modern entertainment space and suave fits from The Sims™ 4 Casanova Cave Kit. This laid-back masculine fashion will have Sims looking confident, and the contemporary style of your den’s décor – a stylish bar, sleek coffee table, and more – will guarantee the right atmosphere, whether it’s game night or date night.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Elevated Evenings – A jumbo, state-of-the-art TV and stylish modern furniture will make your den an undeniable hotspot. Have friends over for a chill night at the card table – or have a date over for an exciting night on your stylish, well-loved leather sofa.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Effortless Style – Dress in high-quality, understated fashions made for the masculine Sim. These styles are relaxed, achieving a polished look that is still a bit rough around the edges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="E21251B4">The Sims™ 4 Casanova Cave Kit</Text><Text Key="4AEC5F00">Embrace elegance and sophistication with The Sims™ 4 Refined Living Room Kit. With a clever mix of modern and retro furniture you can create the perfect base. Add extra personality with unique and chic decor pieces. And voilà! You’ll have a living room worthy of a design magazine. Created by Pierisim.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Feature:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hand Picked – You’ve done your research and you’ve finally found the perfect items. Every time you step into your living room, you can feel that this space has been made by you and for you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="DAC877CF">The Sims™ 4 Refined Living Room Kit</Text><Text Key="FAA65317">Give your Sims a professional edge with chic and stylish outfits from The Sims™ 4 Business Chic Kit! From tailored suits to elegant dresses, Sims will feel confident and fashionable. Complete the look with sleek shoes and fancy accessories for an extra touch of class. The Business Chic Kit ensures Sims always look up to the task! Created by Madlen.\n\n&lt;font color="#1A81E1"&gt;Kit Feature:&lt;/font&gt;\n\n&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tailored for Success – It's time for your Sims to shine with outfits that showcase their career achievements! Elegant accessories and standout shoes are making sure they don't go unnoticed. Taking their fashion game to the next level!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text><Text Key="F7646CEE">The Sims™ 4 Business Chic Kit</Text><Text Key="2B29ED43">{1.SimName}'s {0.ObjectName}</Text><Text Key="C062DBC4">Special Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="6F6885DC">The time capsule seen in The Sims Archives, that was left behind for someone to uncover!</Text><Text Key="0E897DA3">Ambrosia Society Newsletter</Text><Text Key="F6C0F797">IOU Note</Text><Text Key="165CA576">A mysterious IOU note, left inside of a time capsule.</Text><Text Key="34B576E7">Sent years ago, it's as though this letter has been waiting for you the whole time.</Text><Text Key="A7D516AC">Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="E2ACA988">An echo through time found in items in the world and concentrated in a crystalline shard.</Text><Text Key="ACFB6AC2">Shard of Time</Text><Text Key="9D3E0908">The component made from a Shard of Time. It's needed to turn a computer into a time machine.</Text><Text Key="E1CFDD10">Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="DFE93B39">{0.Number} {S0.Serving}{P0.Servings} Left</Text><Text Key="8C5134D3">Swipe Items Worth {1.Money}</Text><Text Key="EF9F9C94">Travel away from your home lot by using the World Map, then Attempt to Swipe on valuables found there!</Text><Text Key="32A31B11">Evening</Text><Text Key="8C159659">Morning</Text><Text Key="CB0B3483">Night</Text><Text Key="2F7072E1">Set Alarm for Room</Text><Text Key="241C10C6">Daytime</Text><Text Key="D2FB1AF2">Mysterious Merchandise</Text><Text Key="8000C611">Play Game Together</Text><Text Key="6E6C0A9D">Enter Game Tournament</Text><Text Key="76DF3518">Enter Novice Tournament</Text><Text Key="44DEFC39">Enter Professional Tournament</Text><Text Key="4981EBC0">Force Self to Play Game</Text><Text Key="C6F5A0B2">Play Game</Text><Text Key="00555F21">Play Multiplayer Game</Text><Text Key="9DDE606C">Play Online Game</Text><Text Key="ADDAABD7">Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="E2C7CEEC">Hot Cocoa with Marshmallows</Text><Text Key="9634F6E3">Peppermint Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="B4E93959">Spiced Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="158A5864">Vegan Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="BF7C5F4C">Vegan Hot Cocoa with Marshmallows</Text><Text Key="BE6CA262">Spectral Spritzer</Text><Text Key="85EEB34D">Make Spectral Spritzer</Text><Text Key="8606DB3E">A cloying concoction that will give Sims a taste of the afterlife in one ghastly gulp.</Text><Text Key="B23FC693">Mămăligă</Text><Text Key="31C8A1AC">Serve Mămăligă</Text><Text Key="1ECA09DB">Mămăligă is a cherished traditional dish found in many Eastern European countries, and some hail it as the national dish of Romania. Originally made with millet flour, today it is a polenta crafted from yellow maize flour. It can be prepared to various consistencies, serving as a comforting porridge or a delightful bread substitute.\n\nMămăligă is incredibly versatile and pairs well with cheese and other toppings. Our own recipe includes cottage cheese, tomatoes, and basil. Rich in history and flavor, mămăligă continues to be a staple in Eastern European cuisine, celebrated for its simplicity and adaptability.</Text><Text Key="9E7B8F42">Make Mămăligă</Text><Text Key="E9E6554F">Mucenici</Text><Text Key="E38921B0">Serve Mucenici</Text><Text Key="716BAF3F">Mucenici is a traditional Romanian pastry prepared for the Christian feast of the 40 Martyrs of Sebaste on March 9th. They are created by rolling and shaping dough into figure eights, which represents eternity and remembrance of the soldiers who were persecuted. The pastries embody the cultural heritage of those who observe the day and celebrate culinary tradition, bringing families together to honor the past and welcome spring.\n\nThe preparation method of mucenici varies depending on the region. In Moldova, the famous Moldavian mucenici are made from sweet bread dough. They are baked in the oven, then coated with honey and sprinkled with walnuts. In Muntenia, Oltenia, and Dobrogea, the dough for mucenici is much simpler, with only three ingredients. These are boiled in water with sugar, walnuts, and cinnamon—the water symbolizing the lake where the soldiers were thrown. Although the preparation method differs, their shape has remained unchanged—the figure 8. The enjoyment of mucenici is a communal activity that strengthens family bonds and cultural identity, making it a cherished part of Romanian heritage.</Text><Text Key="5F7D73F6">Make Mucenici</Text><Text Key="0DEFC692">Chocolate Surprise Cake</Text><Text Key="0A3202CE">Vegetarian-Safe</Text><Text Key="EF51A4C7">Fruity Surprise Cake</Text><Text Key="16EE0F17">Vegetarian-Safe</Text><Text Key="B8CB12BD">Red Velvet Surprise Cake</Text><Text Key="18D65451">Vegetarian-Safe</Text><Text Key="F11F5F31">Vanilla Surprise Cake</Text><Text Key="9D0126AD">Vegetarian-Safe</Text><Text Key="EDF6A01B">Enhanced Kleptomaniacs are less likely to be caught in the act of taking things right in front of the eyes of others.</Text><Text Key="25514FAC">Enhanced Kleptomaniac</Text><Text Key="FFB1F72B">Event Points are needed to unlock new Event rewards. You don't actually spend them, you just collect them. Select the Event button or the Event Tab to see more details.</Text><Text Key="DFB2B93C">Event Points!</Text><Text Key="B2C152B1">Goth</Text><Text Key="11394ABB">Emit Relevart</Text><Text Key="C9ED941C">This will end the Event Quest, but you will still receive Event Points!</Text><Text Key="562EB1D4">Different cultures all have their own festive traditions, ask other Sims about their Holiday Traditions to learn about them.</Text><Text Key="465BD889">You are off to a great start learning about different traditions and foods. Keep going and chat with Sims about the holidays, try some tasty new foods and then let me know what you discover!</Text><Text Key="25A1A442">Do you know what goes well with traditional foods? Traditional drinks! Let's make some of both to test my theory.</Text><Text Key="402872F7">You've heard what traditions others have in your local area but there is a whole world out there. I wonder what other traditions exist, use the Internet to see how else Sims celebrate and let's get some music going to really set the festive mood!</Text><Text Key="986C98F0">In the online research I saw that other Sims like to get together and dance. I think it's time to fill this place with Holiday Cheer and invite some friends over!</Text><Text Key="2FC5F035">Phew! The festive season seems really busy. Let's try the tradition of relaxing with some sweet drinks and some festive TV, I hear they play traditional movies at this time of year!</Text><Text Key="E3DB7488">Assistant to the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="70B9D074">The Grim Reaper is calling for your assistance! Help Grim research Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="BD031EA9">A Call Away</Text><Text Key="FC4660A9">Work on your skills to prepare to make Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="59EFD7BA">Digging Holes</Text><Text Key="578CFCE2">Start your garden and grow the ingredients needed for Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="A223B763">Friends with Death</Text><Text Key="D32EF717">Become Friends with the Grim Reaper and continue to work on skills.</Text><Text Key="8829DB34">The First Ingredient</Text><Text Key="8A96C210">Fish for the first ingredient needed for Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="8A0DBE35">Learning from the Lady</Text><Text Key="0D0E9655">Continue to grow your skills and your garden!</Text><Text Key="09271CE6">Death's Favorite Flower</Text><Text Key="8ED91E7E">It's time to harvest the rare Death Flower!</Text><Text Key="CE4CE1CF">Flirting with Death</Text><Text Key="D43E9003">Continue to build your skills and your relationship with the Grim Reaper!</Text><Text Key="9AE71450">An Inspiring Potion</Text><Text Key="9BE3091C">The second ingredient for Ambrosia is just in reach!</Text><Text Key="9C8E68EA">Skilled Chef</Text><Text Key="F0E57092">Put the final touches on the skills required for Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="16BCC519">The Moment of Truth</Text><Text Key="094EA719">All the work is done, now it's time to cook Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="F41A28B8">Fruits of Your Labor</Text><Text Key="D8DCA8E4">The mystery of Ambrosia has been uncovered! Time to relax and celebrate.</Text><Text Key="E13FF63F">A Strange Visitor</Text><Text Key="26E3CAF3">A Sim from the past arrives in town with a boom and flash of light. Meet them and find out what's going on.</Text><Text Key="D82DA772">Missing Clues</Text><Text Key="9602CF5A">Items have gone missing from the Sims timeline! Help Emit find more information on his hunt for who is responsible.</Text><Text Key="CF2406A1">Echoes of Time</Text><Text Key="0FBD5D81">In order to help Emit, you must discover the secrets of time travel if you ever expect to catch the time-traveling thief.</Text><Text Key="AD71306C">Inventing the Past</Text><Text Key="04B504A8">Now that you have discovered the secrets of time travel, you must build a time machine to catch the thief in the act!</Text><Text Key="93E7BDFB">The Setback</Text><Text Key="5AFDAE2F">With the component in hand, it's time to travel in time! But alas, sometimes when things are running smoothly, that's when it all falls apart.</Text><Text Key="248995DE">On the Hunt</Text><Text Key="06CC8216">Determined as ever, it's time for the final plan to be put into action.\n\nThe time travel component is installed and activated, and the computer is sufficiently overclocked. It's time to catch a thief!</Text><Text Key="FACF61AD">Hidden Motives</Text><Text Key="5716266D">Now that you found the thief, you should try to find out why he did it to begin with.</Text><Text Key="D3F57A78">The Good Thief</Text><Text Key="901872A4">Turns out that the thief had the best intentions. It's time to inform Emit of everything that has been uncovered, so that he can continue his own journey!</Text><Text Key="F6AEBA30">This event always has Goals and Rewards.</Text><Text Key="3FEF473A">Cook Japchae</Text><Text Key="49AE0662">Start a Sim's culinary journey and prepare Japchae by selecting Cook on a Fridge or Stove.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="6B7C7F4F">Cook some Chocolate Chip Cookies</Text><Text Key="DAEEC141">Raise a Sim's Cooking skill to level 3 by using a Fridge or Stove and then Cook some delicious Chocolate Chip Cookies.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="078E9348">Cook Brigadeiro</Text><Text Key="3FA78CE0">While a Sim has Cooking skill level 2 or higher, select a Fridge or Stove to whip up a batch of Brigadeiro.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="1E99CE8E">Cook Hallaca</Text><Text Key="815B64CE">While a Sim has Cooking skill level 3 or higher, select a Fridge or Storve to Cook up some Hallaca.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="20DFAEE3">Restock the Cozy Hot Cocoa Tray</Text><Text Key="32EC596D">Get a Cozy Hot Cocoa Tray from Kitchen Appliances in Build Mode and stock it with any choice of Hot Cocoa flavor. It'll really set the festive feeling!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F6B3B1D6">Prepare a traditional Coquito</Text><Text Key="D0A2AB26">Raise a Sim's Mixology skill to level 2 or higher by practicing on a Bar from the Dining Room category in Build Mode. Then, show it off and shake up some Coquito.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+60 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="78F079EC">Beats and a dance partner or group are required for this one! First, Form Group with any nearby Sim and interact with a Stereo to Listen To something with a beat. Then select the Stereo to Dance Together. If you don't have a Stereo, there is a fine selection in Build Mode to suit the décor.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="B5E6E147">Ask other Sims about their Holiday Traditions</Text><Text Key="D7BB4029">Interact with other Sims and ask them about Holiday Traditions.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="C7921A00">Document the Research</Text><Text Key="87E5C0C8">Use a Computer to Document the Research for Jasmine.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F7C35EE8">Have a Nice Chat about Holiday Traditions</Text><Text Key="97715D00">Meet up with other Sims and Have a Nice Chat about Holidays and hear what they think about it.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="5198CC2A">Prepare a Hot Cocoa</Text><Text Key="27ACC8D2">Grab the Cozy Hot Cocoa Tray from Kitchen Appliances in Build Mode and use it to prepare a delicious comforting drink to celebrate the holiday.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="802A6664">Invite Sims over to Current Lot</Text><Text Key="B8421674">Invite three Sims over to Current Lot using the Social app on the Phone. Maybe offer them some good food and great company or just let them hang out.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="2A9EF177">Listen to Winter Holiday Station</Text><Text Key="5EF9EA19">Change Station to the Winter Holiday channel on a Stereo and let the festivities begin.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="ED602B33">Sing Songs with an Instrument</Text><Text Key="41B3E0BD">Play some music on an instrument and be inspired by the holiday spirit.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="8A153FCE">Research about Holiday Traditions on the Web</Text><Text Key="CFB7200E">Take a look at what Sims say about Holiday Traditions on a computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="94F62823">Share the Discoveries with Jasmine Holiday</Text><Text Key="5FC004AD">Use a Computer to Share the Discoveries about the Holidays with Jasmine Holiday.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="5060D775">Cloudgaze or Stargaze</Text><Text Key="F9E3721F">Have a Sim take a moment and just look up to take it all in by selecting a Sim then Cloudgaze during the day or Stargaze during the night.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="65BBDC1D">Talk about Holiday Songs</Text><Text Key="47984937">Talk with two Sims about Holiday Songs.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="D2761D79">Watch Channels on the Festive Frame TV</Text><Text Key="7EBDA7AB">Place the Festive Frame TV from Build Mode and take it for a spin by watching some channels alone or with friends.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+30 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="A961D870">Have Sims Play Multiplayer Game Together</Text><Text Key="BE02A938">Using Play Multiplayer Game by selecting a console from Build Mode, go head-to-head against another Sim in an epic gaming battle and may the best Sim win!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F54E5854">Have Sims watch TV together</Text><Text Key="93944EE4">Sit down with friends or family and just Watch TV together.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="9313EEB9">Catch an Angelfish</Text><Text Key="D04663EB">Fish for Angelfish in the Crawdad Quarter in Willow Creek.\n\n(+65 Event Points)</Text><Text Key="6F01E81B">Obtain a Death Flower</Text><Text Key="CF7C7B35">Take a cutting of the Orchid and graft it to your Pomegranate plant to create a Death Flower plant, then harvest it! Or Order a Death Flower from the Home app on the phone.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+65 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="EF93B355">Order a Starter Flower Seed Packet</Text><Text Key="3D1F4B88">Order a Starter Fruit Seed Packet</Text><Text Key="2F288520">Continue growing your garden!\n\nPurchase a Starter Fruits seed packet from the Activities and Skills section in Build Mode, or use the Order interaction on a Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F6B349AD">Graft a Shoot to a Plant or Research Grafting</Text><Text Key="17F07F47">Grafting can seem like a mystery! Graft a shoot to a plant or "Research Grafting" on a plant.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+55 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="84EA90F4">Buy The Grimophone</Text><Text Key="CB41B204">Claim The Grimophone reward from the Event and buy it from Build Mode in the Electronics category.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="B3DFB866">Purchase a Potion of Youth</Text><Text Key="23C4B0F6">A Potion of Youth is needed to make Ambrosia! Open the Rewards Store from the Aspiration Panel and Purchase a Potion of Youth.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="A09BBCBA">Introduce Yourself to Emit Relevart</Text><Text Key="C35CF2E2">You arrived at Magnolia Blossom Park in Willow Creek. Now, find Emit!\n\nWith his bright blue hair, he shouldn't be too hard to spot.\n\nSelect Emit and choose an Introduction.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="298AF07D">Report to Emit on the Experiment</Text><Text Key="0F1B0017">There is a lot to report back to Emit about the time travel experiment and the thief's email.\n\nSelect Report on Experiment on Emit.\n\nEmit can be found at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Emit Over.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="61AC4DE9">Great Scott, it worked!\n\nI wonder if you can use the same technology to actually send an email through time and find out why any of this happened to begin with.</Text><Text Key="BC415FDB">Emit's Response</Text><Text Key="3937608C">Report Back to Emit</Text><Text Key="3F98D1AC">The discovery in the archives of the capsule and the note—someone is clearly leaping through time and taking items!\n\nSelect Report about Time Capsule on Emit.\n\nYou can find him at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Over Emit.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="495E5EBA">I see! Yes, it's starting to make all sense now.\n\nA thief is taking the missing items! But why and who?\n\nI can't help but wonder if that time-traveling thief is here and in this time right now...</Text><Text Key="131631B4">Emit's Response</Text><Text Key="4F55242A">Tell Emit about the Thief's True Intentions</Text><Text Key="3F6290D2">Find Emit and let him know what you have learned about the thief's intentions.\n\nSelect Tell about Thief's True Intentions on Emit.\n\nEmit can be found at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Emit Over.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="1AD0FE24">Well, I can't blame a fellow time traveler for wanting to preserve the past.\n\nI can't say I agree with the thief's methods, but nobody was hurt other than a few who overslept a bit.\n\nThank you {0.SimFirstName} for all of our help!</Text><Text Key="94EA6003">Show Emit the Shards of Time</Text><Text Key="F51C200D">Emit absolutely must see the Shards! Maybe he knows something more.\n\nSelect Show Shards of Time on Emit.\n\nEmit can be found at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Emit Over.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="E069E186">Say Goodbye to Emit</Text><Text Key="CAFDC016">The mystery is solved, the thief has been...not caught, but uncovered, sort of...actually who is the thief? Maybe a question for another day...\n\nFor now, it's time to say a fond farewell to Emit.\n\nSelect Say Goodbye on Emit.\n\nEmit can be found at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Emit Over.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="D2DDA6B8">Thank you {0.SimFirstName} for all of your help!\n\nI have to be heading back...or forward... I'm so confused now about when I came from and when I'm going!\n\nWhenever that is though, I think I'll get a grilled cheese sandwich.\n\nTa-ta, and thanks {0.SimFirstName}! I couldn't have done it without your help.</Text><Text Key="BE52C9A6">Emit's Fond Farewell</Text><Text Key="6B4AB9F4">Hey {0.SimFirstName}, great to meet you! Why yes, I am Emit Relevart! Technology expert and time traveler extraordinaire!\n\nI've been jumping around through time on a bit of mystery, and I'm kind of stuck. Have you noticed any unexplained missing items around here? I'm trying to figure out what's going on.</Text><Text Key="A9B952F2">Emit's Introduction</Text><Text Key="D22294A2">Ask Emit Relevart about the Missing Items</Text><Text Key="A71D287A">Emit's been found! And he mentioned something about missing items. That sounds intriguing!\n\nSelect Ask about Missing Items on Emit.\n\nYou can find him at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Over Emit.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="DBDCE2EC">I've been exploring the past, where we come from... It's been quite an adventure in simulation!\n\nHowever, I have noticed some ripples in my travels and have suspicions that items through time might have gone missing.\n\nHave you or anyone else noticed any things out of place?</Text><Text Key="3881354A">Items Missing in Time</Text><Text Key="FBF46798">Ask Emit about the Malfunction</Text><Text Key="86E943F0">Emit has built time machines before, and he might know where things went wrong.\n\nSelect Ask about Malfunction on Emit.\n\nEmit can be found at Magnolia Blossom Park, or select the Social category on the Phone to Invite Emit Over.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="C05BEE0E">Here's the thing {0.SimFirstName}, you installed a powerful new component and didn't give it enough processing power! That's why the computer fried.\n\nIt doesn't need too much more power. It just wasn't enough.</Text><Text Key="0A6A7D68">About the Malfunction</Text><Text Key="9FBAAE74">Where did you find these? I thought I was the only one who knew about them.\n\nThese little echoes of the past can be used to build a time machine. Which, hey, you know what? Yea...yea!\n\nYou're going to build one of your own!</Text><Text Key="6F299B72">Emit's Response about the Shards</Text><Text Key="743DD63D">Catch {0.Number} Fish</Text><Text Key="980B8FD7">Select a nearby fishing sign post to go Fishing.\n\nIf the fish aren't biting, try going to another fishing location!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="3139EEBE">Fulfill an Aspiration Goal</Text><Text Key="CB6B4DFE">Complete any Aspiration Goal. Open the Aspiration Panel to see your Sim's goals or pick a new Aspiration!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="B59400D9">You'll need to know how to cook to make Ambrosia! Level up your cooking skill at the Fridge, Stove, or even a TV...then cook a recipe!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="0137D07A">Fish with Bait</Text><Text Key="AA6A97A2">Fishing with bait increases your chances of catching fish! Reach level 3 or higher in the Fishing skill and select Fish with Bait.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="89E2A494">Getting the ingredients needed requires a green thumb. Reach level 2 in Gardening, select a plant, and Research it.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="1F608B62">Ambrosia is considered gourmet! Level up your gourmet cooking skill by using the Fridge or Stove.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="BF8CD481">Complete a Want</Text><Text Key="51943FE3">Wants are a great way to earn Satisfaction Points for the Potion of Youth!\n\nWants can be viewed on the bottom left above your Sim's head. Hover over the bubble to see more details!\n\nIf you don't see any Wants, open your Game Options and make sure Show Wants &amp; Fears is enabled under Gameplay.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="97BA9AAE">Host a Social Event</Text><Text Key="3FE90F6E">It's time to celebrate all your hard work! Host a Social Event by selecting "Plan a Social Event" from the Social App on your phone and pick any Event with "Goals and Rewards" selected.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="D28358E8">Apply the Scare Seeker Lot Challenge to your Lot</Text><Text Key="857D9B00">The Scare Seeker Lot Challenge can really help your Sim gain skills faster! Claim the Lot Challenge and apply it by entering Build Mode and selecting Venue Info.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="A322DD6B">Get a Silver or Better Result From the Party</Text><Text Key="E7407405">Don't host a dud of a party! Complete the goals for the party and get silver or better.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+45 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="218FF923">Wait for the Ambrosia Society Newsletter</Text><Text Key="E3F33FAD">It's coming! Wait for the mail to get delivered or you can Expedite your mail from the Home app on your Phone.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="396D619C">Ask {0.Number} Sims about Ambrosia</Text><Text Key="42CB283C">Someone must know something about Ambrosia! Socialize with a Sim and select Ask about Ambrosia. Just make sure to introduce yourself first.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="42FFFB47">Summon the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="1743DE29">It's time to meet the Grim Reaper. Select Summon the Grim Reaper from the Grimophone.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="C061B834">Fertilize 2 Plants</Text><Text Key="EE57D944">Fertilize your plants to increase their quality!\n\nReach Gardening level 3, select a plant, and Fertilize it with a fish or fruit.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="3427560A">Plant an Apple</Text><Text Key="44E73B32">Plant the Apple from the Starter Fruit Seed packet.\n\nHint: Plant it under a roof to ensure they are in season.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="98759A2B">Plant a Cherry</Text><Text Key="E9C8C0C5">Plant the Cherry fruit from the Starter Fruit Seed packet.\n\nHint: Plant it under a roof to ensure they are in season.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="EAA5BAB2">Plant a Lily</Text><Text Key="8B724F0A">Plant the Lily from the Starter Flower seed packet.\n\nHint: Plant it under a roof to ensure they are in season.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="71A9E635">Plant a Snapdragon</Text><Text Key="DDCFBFDF">Plant the Snapdragon from the Starter Flower seed packet.\n\nHint: Plant it under a roof to ensure they are in season.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="894CE11F">Take a Cutting of a Plant</Text><Text Key="F0727091">Reach Level 5 in Gardening and take a cutting of your Snapdragon or Lily.\n\nYour plant must grow to the mature stage for the Take Cutting interaction to be available.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="3D95130D">Read the Intro in The Green Lady's Tome</Text><Text Key="4D049CA7">Claim The Green Lady's Tome from the Event, purchase it from Build Mode, and read the intro.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="979A0C67">Read the Ambrosia Society's Newsletter</Text><Text Key="70502449">It's here! Select your mailbox and Get Mail, then Select the Ambrosia Society's Newsletter from your Sim's inventory and read it.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="098E09AF">Research Ambrosia on your Phone, a Tablet, or a Computer</Text><Text Key="3F03B4A1">There must be more information somewhere out there...\n\nResearch Ambrosia from the Home app on the Phone, or select the Research Ambrosia interaction on a Computer or Tablet.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="FE09F0BE">Research a plant</Text><Text Key="03434BB4">Talk to {0.Number} Plants</Text><Text Key="C5908FC4">Select a plant in your garden and talk to it!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F00E5F47">Cook Ambrosia</Text><Text Key="B2672A29">It's time! Cook Ambrosia by reaching level 10 in the Cooking and Gourmet Cooking Skills, then selecting Cook a Gourmet Meal on the Fridge or Stove.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+100 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="E4902937">Cook a recipe while level 10</Text><Text Key="AF9D1C40">Cook a recipe while level 3 or higher</Text><Text Key="7DA3D846">Cook a recipe while level 4 or higher</Text><Text Key="7D873334">Cook a recipe while level 5 or higher</Text><Text Key="5F2EFF9A">Cook a recipe while level 7 or higher</Text><Text Key="9E79529A">Cook a Gourmet Cooking recipe while level 7</Text><Text Key="D2F26EF3">Cook a Gourmet Cooking recipe</Text><Text Key="AAD432E9">Cook a Gourmet Cooking recipe while level 4 or higher</Text><Text Key="9F6BB34F">Obtain an Electronic Upgrade Part</Text><Text Key="0B5EFD41">Electronic Upgrade Parts can be obtained in a couple of ways.\n\nRepairing a broken electronic object may yield an upgrade part. Be careful, as a fire can easily be the outcome of the unskilled.\n\nOr Select Order and then Purchase Upgrade Parts... from a Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F7981FC7">{0.SimFirstName} has an Electronic Upgrade Part!\n\nThis is a core component for all theoretical high tech devices...including coffee makers, and it's used for building a time travel component.</Text><Text Key="2F0E8B45">Electronic Upgrade Part Obtained!</Text><Text Key="F47F5F59">{0.SimFirstName} has a piece of Ironyum!\n\nIronyum forms the base of all matter, past and present, and it is used for building a time travel component.</Text><Text Key="DE55848B">Ironyum Obtained!</Text><Text Key="3F54E0E8">Collect Plathinum</Text><Text Key="18F87300">To find Plathinum, search for rocks or dirt mounds ready to be dug up. Look closely for when they appear, or speed up the process of rock formation by using Ultra Speed from the time controls.\n\nExplore areas like parks, and seek out rocks with crystals or dirt mounds, and select Dig.\n\nA great place to look is Desert Bloom Park in Oasis Springs!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="94132ADE">{0.SimFirstName} has a piece of Plathinum!\n\nPlathinum forms magic and splendor in energy, and it's one of the needed parts used to build a time travel component.</Text><Text Key="9102BFB8">Plathinum Obtained!</Text><Text Key="12394EDD">Accuse 3 Sims of Being a Time Traveler</Text><Text Key="3225EFF7">Maybe you can uncover the time traveling thief hiding in plain sight by pretending that you already know their identity!\n\nSelect Accuse of Being a Time Traveler on 3 different Sims.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="EFDE88C9">No luck!\n\nMaking baseless accusations of your fellow Sims might be complicating things.\n\nIt might be best to cool off and reflect on this further.</Text><Text Key="731D4466">Activate the Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="FBB0B4F6">The time travel component has been successfully completed. Now it's time to find a computer, and turn it into a time machine!\n\nSelect Activate Time Travel Component on a Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="2EAFDC98">Oh no! What happened?!\n\nIt looks like the component may still be intact, but the computer itself is fried!\n\nAs setbacks go, this is bad, but it could have been far far worse.</Text><Text Key="D9B8BE86">Activation Failed!</Text><Text Key="089F2D20">Ask other Sims about Emit</Text><Text Key="1673C4E8">Blue hair, believer in time travel...who else could it be but Emit Relevart? Maybe others might know more.\n\nSelect Ask about Emit on other Sims.\n\n(Make sure to introduce yourself first, if you haven't already)\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="405E1606">Despite being mere gossip, the information from the news and your own inquiries suggest Emit might be found at Magnolia Blossom Park in Willow Creek.\n\nSurely, he's there!</Text><Text Key="5E8537E6">Ask Other Sims about Missing Items</Text><Text Key="67678B76">If there are items missing, someone else must have noticed!\n\nSelect Ask about Missing Items on other Sims to learn if they've seen or heard anything.\n\n(Make sure to introduce yourself first if you haven't already)\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="401C0718">It appears Sims are missing various items from around town with no explanation, just like Emit suspected!\n\nPerhaps Emit was right—something mysterious is indeed happening!</Text><Text Key="D9D9393D">Ask an Elder about the Shard</Text><Text Key="F4CA90D7">Maybe someone who has been around for a while knows something about the Shard.\n\nFind an elder Sim, and select Ask about Shard.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F3B7AAA9">I never thought they were real!\n\nI remember stories from when I was a youngster about something like this. People believed it was an echo from the past which could be used for time travel.\n\nBut, I always thought they were just that, stories.</Text><Text Key="2203879B">Elder Story</Text><Text Key="F4D19C3B">Burn Off Steam by Exercising for an Hour</Text><Text Key="C57F4B55">After having nearly destroyed everything, maybe it's time to burn off some steam.\n\nFind an exercise to do, such as Workout on a treadmill or Practice Punching on the punching bag, and exercise for at least an hour. Or visit a Gym Venue and use the equipment there.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="123858EB">Exercise really helps relieve stress and clear the head, which {0.SimFirstName} desperately needed.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} feels refreshed and should be ready to tackle the time travel component installation again.</Text><Text Key="8E8C5CD9">Steam Burned Off</Text><Text Key="22995898">Collect Ironyum</Text><Text Key="B3BEDEF0">To find Ironyum, search for rocks or dirt mounds ready to be dug up. Look closely for when they appear, or speed up the process of rock formation by using Ultra Speed from the time controls.\n\nExplore areas like parks, and seek out rocks with crystals or dirt mounds, and select Dig.\n\nA great place to look is Desert Bloom Park in Oasis Springs!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="8D721D35">Find the Special Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="69ECDCDF">To uncover a time capsule, search for rocks or dirt mounds ready to be dug up. Remember to look closely for when and where they appear.\n\nExplore areas like parks, and seek out rocks with crystals or dirt mounds, and select Dig for Special Time Capsule.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="CC5F119F">Get Something to Eat</Text><Text Key="E1B02611">No plan can be executed well on an empty stomach.\n\nFind something to eat!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="4AE3A717">It's hard to think straight on an empty stomach.\n\nNow that that's solved {0.SimFirstName} is ready to continue!</Text><Text Key="5A6BECD5">Full Belly Clear Mind</Text><Text Key="53222BD9">Check Emit's Social Media Profile</Text><Text Key="FC8F180B">Could it really be Emit?\n\nChecking his social media profile on a Computer might confirm it. Did he have blue hair, after all?\n\nYou can check his profile under Social Networking from any Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="20F1717D">Loves science, technology, believes in time travel, and has blue hair.\n\nThe description on the news definitely bears a strong similarity to Emit...\n\nIt must be him, right?</Text><Text Key="D24C1FBF">Emit's Social Media Profile</Text><Text Key="374F7455">Retrieve the Thief's Letter from the Mailbox</Text><Text Key="1991477F">The thief's response is in the mailbox? And it has been waiting all this time—that's the mystery of time!\n\nSelect Retrieve Thief's Letter from a Mailbox.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="EBFBA4D1">How wild and weaving time is! From now, to then, and back to here instantly in the future—it boggles the mind!\n\nThe Thief's Letter can now be found in {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory.</Text><Text Key="E36253C3">Thief's Letter Found</Text><Text Key="5E59862D">Repair Something while Handiness Level 2 or Higher</Text><Text Key="0CF1B8C7">Build Handiness skill by fixing broken items, upgrading objects such as Sinks or Toilets, or reading books on Handiness.\n\nWith a skill level of 2 or higher, select Repair on a broken object.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="30A4A599">{0.SimFirstName}'s handiness will be very handy when it comes to building a time travel component.\n\nIt's better to be prepared then to be rusty.</Text><Text Key="C58AF4CB">Handiness Skill Ready</Text><Text Key="B77C3756">Give Yourself a Pep Talk</Text><Text Key="71BA47A6">With everything in place, it might be the right time to pep oneself up before taking a time traveling experience.\n\nFind a mirror, and select Give Yourself a Pep Talk.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="0979B188">{0.SimFirstName} is feeling better about the upcoming time traveling experience!\n\nStay away from butterflies and everything should be fine!</Text><Text Key="E6838776">Pep Talk Before Time Travel</Text><Text Key="94D9BB5E">Exercise Your Mind while Level 2 or Higher in Logic</Text><Text Key="DD4F531E">Spend some time preparing to expand your mind by performing any logic activity.\n\nLogic is built on things like Playing Chess, Using the Telescope or Microscope, or Reading a Book on logic.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="401E7E40">{0.SimFirstName}'s logic skill is just what {0.SimFirstName} needs to piece together Nikolai's theoretical vision.\n\nUse this skill to help build the time travel component.</Text><Text Key="C296E78E">Logic Skill Ready</Text><Text Key="FF2EE937">Overclock a Computer</Text><Text Key="3AC9B7D9">Emit said it wasn't too much power that fried the computer, but rather not enough power!\n\nFind a Computer, and select Overclock.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="2722449F">Time travel component: check!\n\nComputer overclocked: check!\n\nEverything is in place for a time traveling experience!</Text><Text Key="5076F93D">Overclocking Complete</Text><Text Key="9F4211E5">Refresh Your memory in The Sims Archives</Text><Text Key="A1C0C04F">Some of those items mentioned sound familiar, like they might be found in the archives of Sims.\n\nSelect Play Game and then Play The Sims Archives on a Computer to refresh your memory.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="546C7461">While in The Sims Archives, your attention was caught by an oddly dressed Sim burying a time capsule.\n\nIt seemed to glow in an unfamiliar manner, and a strange feeling came over you. Almost like...the time capsule may still exist.\n\nYou can't shake that feeling, and now you have to find it!</Text><Text Key="48AE92D3">The Sims Archive</Text><Text Key="94E90F5C">Experience the Past by Playing The Sims Archives vol. 2</Text><Text Key="9DD49EFC">The book at the library had some interesting theories about time travel and video games.\n\nSelect Play Game and then Play The Sims Archives, vol. 2 on a Computer to explore the past.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="2A4EAB8A">{0.SimFirstName} saw a strange glowing crystalline object being held by a hidden figure. That same uneasy feeling {0.SimPronounSubjective} experienced last time happened again.\n\nThat's the time thief! {0.SimFirstName} must be on the right track!</Text><Text Key="0D04DFC4">The Sims Archives, vol. 2</Text><Text Key="4D0521FA">Look for the Thief by Playing in the Archives</Text><Text Key="A88DF822">Time travel is on the table! Play in the echoes of the past of the archives once more to find the thief in time!\n\nUse a Computer, and select Play Game... and then Play The Sims Archives, vol. 4.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="E1941AF4">While playing through the archives, {0.SimFirstName} had that same uneasy feeling as when simulating the various events and was able to catch the thief in the act!\n\nIn doing so, {0.SimFirstName} was able to discover the thief's email address!</Text><Text Key="E80C1BF2">Thief Found</Text><Text Key="5B378A3A">Ponder Time Travel</Text><Text Key="00B2A762">There has been a lot going on today. Hidden time capsules, a cryptic note, random accusations towards your neighbors of the near-impossible. That's a lot to ponder.\n\nFind a Shower, and select Ponder Time Travel. (You can also use a Bathtub or Toilet!)\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="8464C234">That helped put things into perspective!\n\nMaybe it's best to take some time, and continue the search for clues after regrouping.</Text><Text Key="A8D5C232">Post Ponder Thoughts</Text><Text Key="B498C796">Read the History of Time Travel at a Library</Text><Text Key="ECC768E6">A little knowledge of time travel might help on where to begin!\n\nGo to a Library Venue, and select Read History of Time Travel from a bookshelf.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="115E8CC8">It is both now and ever, long and short, and started when someone tried to fix past mistakes. In doing so, the fabric of time itself crystalized and became something material.\n\nIt goes on to say that while some believe books, movies, or even video games are merely windows into the past, others believe they may be a form of time travel itself.</Text><Text Key="488FCFB6">The History of Time Travel</Text><Text Key="60187C40">Read the IOU</Text><Text Key="F3A35908">Why was the note in a time capsule, and what is this all about?\n\nOpen your inventory and find the IOU Note, then select Read IOU.\n\n(If you no longer have the IOU Note, it can be replaced at a mailbox)\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="1A9D3AA6">If you're reading this, I don't have time to explain everything.\n\nLet's just say I needed to borrow some things for now. Catch you later...or earlier.</Text><Text Key="CA48DA80">IOU Note</Text><Text Key="ECE1F281">Read the Thief's Letter</Text><Text Key="117E09E3">The thief has responded to the email with a letter.\n\nSelect Read Thief's Letter from the letter in your inventory to find out their motive!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="5760A6A4">Read Theoretical Electronics at a Library</Text><Text Key="F2D553B4">Nikolai Volt was a genius in the field of theoretical electronics before his time.\n\nHis book is kept at the library for historical preservation.\n\nGo to a Library Venue and select Read Theoretical Electronics from a Bookshelf.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="0FA14FC2">Nikolai theorized that a time travel component could be built with:\n\n• A piece of Ironyum\n• A piece of Plathinum\n• A common electronic component\n\nAnd one other item which must contain the essence of time...but he was unable to discover what held time!</Text><Text Key="C06EC4DC">Theoretical Electronics by Nikolai Volt</Text><Text Key="E4E994D5">Repair or Replace the Computer</Text><Text Key="ED724CFF">What a setback! Going to have to fix up the computer if there is any chance of moving forward.\n\nSelect Repair or Replace on a broken computer. Or from the Phone, select Home and then Hire a Service to hire a repair service.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="F5353651">Whew! That was indeed close. The computer is available again, and the Time Travel Component is intact and back in place.\n\nMaybe next time {0.SimFirstName} shouldn't just rush into things. Perhaps {0.SimPronounSubjective} might want to talk to Emit before proceeding.</Text><Text Key="3E560143">Computer Back Online</Text><Text Key="AAB86825">Research Shards of Time</Text><Text Key="9300708F">The internet has the answers to everything! There must be more information on the Shards of Time there!\n\nSelect Web... and then Research... and then Research Shards of Time on a Computer to do one last search.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="811293A1">It's true! It's right there on the internet!\n\nThe shards are echoes form the past and exist everywhere in the world. If {0.SimFirstName} looks hard enough for that faint glow the shards have...\n\n...Maybe {0.SimPronounSubjective} can find some more. This is an amazing development!</Text><Text Key="4CE7E013">Shards of Time Research</Text><Text Key="1E063B51">Search Objects for Shards of Time</Text><Text Key="62706B73">Even everyday items can contain echoes of the past.\n\nSelect Search for Shard of Time on items such as Sofas, Bookshelves, Computers, Refrigerators or maybe other objects.\n\nIf you're observant, you will find one...or three!\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="61C13285">Through research, discovery and a diligent eye {0.SimFirstName} has found more Shards of Time!\n\n{0.SimPronounSubjective} has found not one, but many. Now what? There must be some way to activate them.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} should return to Emit and show him what {0.SimPronounSubjective} uncovered!</Text><Text Key="7F092F87">All Shards Found</Text><Text Key="9085D52D">{0.SimFirstName} discovered the time capsule and can't wait to open it!\n\nThat unfamiliar feeling was just too strong to ignore and not discover the source!</Text><Text Key="A1E49FEF">Special Time Capsule Discovered</Text><Text Key="96DBC10F">Open the Special Time Capsule</Text><Text Key="10123801">Now that the Special Time Capsule has been found, it's time to open it!\n\nGo to your inventory, find the Special Time Capsule, and select Open.\n\n(If you no longer have the Special Time Capsule, it can be replaced at a mailbox)\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="BE286687">The time capsule was empty except for a single item—an IOU Note!\n\nWhat could be so significant about this note?</Text><Text Key="5B977605">Time Capsule Contents</Text><Text Key="2B77D21B">Build the Time Travel Component</Text><Text Key="B4A60935">To build a time travel component, first make sure you have:\n\n• Level 2 in both Handiness and Logic\n• A piece of Ironyum and Plathinum\n• An Electronic Upgrade Part\n• A Shard of Time\n\nIf any of the components are missing, select Replace on a Mailbox to recover the needed parts.\n\nFrom your inventory, select Build Time Travel Component on a Shard of Time.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="0C93D04B">With the time travel component in hand, {0.SimFirstName} is feeling very proud of {0.SimPronounReflexive}. {0.SimPronounSubjective} solved the missing time piece from Nikolais theoretical work!\n\nWhat could be next, other than to activate it?!</Text><Text Key="547C1CB9">Time Travel Component Complete!</Text><Text Key="3BA29AA8">Study a Historical Display at a Museum</Text><Text Key="5825C7C0">A museum might help to find additional clues. After all, that's where the past comes to life!\n\nTravel to a Museum Venue, select Study Historical Display on any work of art or sculpture.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="6DF6919E">After studying the historical display at the museum, {0.SimFirstName} noticed a glowing object emanating from it!\n\nTaking care to go unnoticed, {0.SimFirstName} plucked the object free from the display and put it in {0.SimPronounSubjective} pocket.\n\nA Shard of Time has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory!</Text><Text Key="3F246B78">The Historical Display</Text><Text Key="3FB5189B">Tune In to the News for 15 Minutes</Text><Text Key="D1E530B5">You might find more details about the situation on the news.\n\nSelect Watch Channel then Watch News on any TV for breaking updates.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="524FCC39">Local News Report</Text><Text Key="4F30FE3C">Send a Time Traveling Email to the Thief</Text><Text Key="53318EDC">As odd as it may seem, Emit believes that the time travel component infused computer can send an email to the thief, whenever they may be, to get some answers as to why the theft.\n\nSelect Send Time Traveling Email on a Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="C3F3C66A">{0.SimFirstName} got an automatic reply:\n\nI am sorry, I am currently AFK, so to speak, and find it best to respond to all correspondence via snail mail.\n\nThere's a good chance the response to your inquiry is already there with you.\n\nDoes that make it really snail mail...or, best to not worry about it.</Text><Text Key="98388B24">Email Auto-Reply</Text><Text Key="D1D48EDF">Meet Someone New</Text><Text Key="188E7DA3">Travel to Magnolia Blossom Park in Willow Creek</Text><Text Key="4229912D">It certainly seems Emit is here, with the sightings reported pointing to Magnolia Blossom Park in Willow Creek.\n\nUse the Phone menu to select Travel and go there.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+15 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="7D4DC665">Become Friends and Socialize with the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="096421CF">The Grim Reaper could really use a friend. Use friendly interactions to improve your friendship with Grim.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+35 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="2252937F">It's time to get this garden started!\n\nPurchase a Starter Flowers seed packet from the Activities and Skills section in Build Mode, or use the Order interaction on a Computer.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="29B88DEA">Flirt or Socialize with the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="9ADAD992">Summon the Grim Reaper by using The Grimophone and Flirt or Socialize with the Grim Reaper.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="44830B93">Meet or Socialize with the Grim Reaper</Text><Text Key="0D67649D">The Grim Reaper looks fairly friendly...Select the Grim Reaper and select an introduction or any social.\n\n&lt;i&gt;(+25 Event Points)&lt;/i&gt;</Text><Text Key="90463FE2">Have Deep Conversation</Text><Text Key="5C8905BA">Socialize with another Sim and select Deep Conversation which appears under Deep Thoughts in the Friendly pie menu.</Text><Text Key="D8A2E349">Express Admiration</Text><Text Key="C11017BB">Select a Sim and Express Admiration.</Text><Text Key="24BDAE7F">When Can I Have Fun Again?</Text><Text Key="9DBBF5F1">Attend an Event that could be made more &lt;i&gt;fun&lt;/i&gt;...the {1.SimFirstName} way.</Text><Text Key="4545D220">Buy a Kids Object Worth {0.Money}</Text><Text Key="9EA51BE8">Buy an Object from the Kids category in Build Mode worth at least {0.Money}.</Text><Text Key="21E34D06">Do an Athletic Activity</Text><Text Key="74BABE96">Use exercise equipment anywhere or select {1.SimFirstName} then find the Go Jogging interaction in the pie menu.</Text><Text Key="B5297132">Read Any Skill Book</Text><Text Key="EFA4468A">Select a Bookshelf to find a Skill Book under the Purchase Books interaction.</Text><Text Key="2A55EBD8">I Need More Ideas!</Text><Text Key="31294130">Go on a Research Binge on the Web using any Computer.</Text><Text Key="66B3633E">A Little Peace and Quiet Would be Nice</Text><Text Key="0D75EF7E">Be introverted, avoid coming into close proximity with other Sims, and definitely don't socialize with others for 4 hours.</Text><Text Key="729AD008">Enter a Game Tournament on the Video Game Console</Text><Text Key="42FDD6A0">Click on a gaming console and select Enter Game Tournament.</Text><Text Key="E7778B0A">Play Video Games on a Gaming Console</Text><Text Key="4CBC005E">Click on a gaming console to select a game to play.</Text><Text Key="20E6F685">Play Party Frenzy</Text><Text Key="D1D9C409">Play MySims Racing Game</Text><Text Key="95526D5A">Play Density Effect</Text><Text Key="7C69D1CD">Win a Multiplayer Game on the Video Game Console</Text><Text Key="93B06A67">Win a game after selecting Play Multiplayer or Join Game on a gaming console.</Text><Text Key="692935D6">Junior Collector Extraordinaire</Text><Text Key="4C24CA7A">Jogger</Text><Text Key="CCB1A59B">Jasmine needs help, she wants to know about festive traditions!</Text><Text Key="8436B79E">Nice work! It looks like you're embracing the holiday spirit. Soon, I'll bring you more exciting news as we continue our research.</Text><Text Key="87D46BD9">Keep Cooking or reading about it to increase the skill.</Text><Text Key="3DF85F72">Chat with others about the Holidays, then report the findings to Jasmine.</Text><Text Key="CC8202D1">Great job embracing the holiday spirit! Keep spreading joy and warmth.</Text><Text Key="8095AF14">Keep working on that Cooking skill and maybe give Mixology a try to create some traditional festive drinks.</Text><Text Key="9C873566">Traditional food and drink set the festive mood, try some more out!</Text><Text Key="D059DA55">You did amazing! I always get emotional at the end of films! These moments help us create strong connections and enjoy the holidays to the fullest.</Text><Text Key="959A2048">Bring the music of the season to Current Lot with a Stereo and pick up a musical instrument to really impress the guests.</Text><Text Key="C0292A1B">There's a whole world of traditions to research online, let's do it!</Text><Text Key="57DFD91E">It looks like we can always learn something new from people, right? Music is the soul of many special and sweet moments. Learning about it enriches our research. Great work! Next week is the final part of our study, so let's do our best to spread the holiday spirit and celebrate!</Text><Text Key="8621B459">Venture out and meet other Sims. The more friends a Sim has, the bigger the celebrations!</Text><Text Key="0D0AA739">Being with those that mean the most makes the holidays special!</Text><Text Key="CCBABFBC">This celebration was so beautiful. I'm sure you brought joy to those people with the presents and by sharing these sweet moments. The last part of our research is approaching, and I can't wait to see all you've documented.</Text><Text Key="2F2A6FCF">Get ready to celebrate the holidays the right way, with close friends and family, video games and hot cocoa. If only there were the Cozy Hot Cocoa Tray.</Text><Text Key="6A054EDC">Celebrating can get really draining. Take time to unwind and watch some TV.</Text><Text Key="0E58710B">You did it! Great work over these past weeks. You've shared amazing moments with others, created memories, and embraced the holiday spirit from different perspectives. Thank you for documenting experiences. I hope you enjoyed our research, and I can’t wait to collaborate with you again!</Text><Text Key="1E7F219E">Research has detailed lots of traditions from different cultures. Now it's time to enjoy existing traditions and make new ones.</Text><Text Key="1B1E4DCD">Grim needs your help! Start learning everything you can about Ambrosia!</Text><Text Key="9D9CAFF0">Great! You’ve scratched the surface about Ambrosia, but this is just the beginning… I need more details!</Text><Text Key="5FC74F33">Keep nurturing your garden!</Text><Text Key="73934380">Perhaps the Ambrosia Society Newsletter could get you closer to the truth...</Text><Text Key="5295D48F">With that Grimophone, you can summon me whenever you need. Just don't don't do it too often. Traveling to this realm can be exhausting.</Text><Text Key="BD754A62">Keep working on your Cooking and Gardening skills!</Text><Text Key="19DA9C56">You'll need a green thumb if you want to cheat death!</Text><Text Key="D911BDC5">Your garden is really coming together, and your fishing skills aren't too shabby either!</Text><Text Key="F6AEEE78">Keep nurturing your plants and catching fish!</Text><Text Key="CF1A450B">Grim doesn't just need an assistant, he needs a friend.</Text><Text Key="6924E8CE">The Grim Reaper can be so friendly!</Text><Text Key="C675CAC9">Keep working on your Aspiration!</Text><Text Key="541C4F67">Time to reel in the first ingredient for your Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="0D4BD91A">Amazing! You’ve lured in the elusive Angelfish!</Text><Text Key="9750FE95">Two more ingredients to go...</Text><Text Key="677841CE">It seems Lady Mimsy had compiled the secrets of Ambrosia many years ago... </Text><Text Key="998C9CCD">I wonder what other secrets this book may hold?</Text><Text Key="628B8FC0">Keep working on your Gourmet cooking!</Text><Text Key="0151FDF4">The next ingredient must bloom from your garden.</Text><Text Key="6DBD0973">Ah, the Death Flower! My absolute favorite.</Text><Text Key="DB29E6C6">One more ingredient to go...</Text><Text Key="6752CD8D">This research has brought you closer to Death than you ever expected...</Text><Text Key="D9102B30">Maybe after all this research is done, we can catch a movie or something?</Text><Text Key="C84C0273">Keep working on your aspiration to gain Satisfaction Points.</Text><Text Key="E7C43EC1">Just one more ingredient remains.</Text><Text Key="88296E34">That’s it! You have all the ingredients. Now you just need to hone your Cooking skills.</Text><Text Key="B54E2607">Keep working on your Cooking and Gourmet Cooking skills.</Text><Text Key="A542EFDF">Hone your cooking skills in preparation for the final step.</Text><Text Key="31263CA2">You're becoming quite the culinarian! You've acquired all the skills and knowledge needed to make Ambrosia.</Text><Text Key="676F003D">I think you're ready for the final step...</Text><Text Key="26F681A5">Everything you've learned comes down to this. </Text><Text Key="0469B198">Incredible! You did it! It’s amazing that this stuff can bring Sims back to life. It’s time to make my own version of it! Thank you for your help!</Text><Text Key="1E13771B">Who should eat this Ambrosia?</Text><Text Key="4D5F4618">You did it! Now it's time to celebrate!</Text><Text Key="A4CF81B7">What a party! Everyone will be talking about that for months.</Text><Text Key="C00E5A8A">Is it too early to throw another party?</Text><Text Key="4BD075BD">Emit's appearance seems to have drawn you into a mystery of missing items from the past. And it became clear that other Sims had also noticed similar disappearances in the present.</Text><Text Key="884A2370">The quest continues as new clues appear.</Text><Text Key="D0F2DC79">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="7AF29F05">A Sim from the past arrives in town with a boom and flash of light. Meet them, and find out what's going on.</Text><Text Key="7173A5D7">The mystery of missing items continues as the search uncovers secrets long buried.</Text><Text Key="85D560CA">Intuition drove the discovery of the time capsule and note inside.\n\nEmit believes the missing items are because of a time-traveling thief...which is a lot to absorb!</Text><Text Key="8B1F6D85">If time travel is indeed real, there must be a way to uncover its secrets.</Text><Text Key="20CC19C2">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="8EB64CCD">The past leaves echoes in time which can be found once again. Discover them, and uncover their secrets. </Text><Text Key="7326C4F0">The discovery of the Shard of Time is a revelation that the past leaves echoes—ripples—that can be found in the future.</Text><Text Key="23F60633">With the Shard in hand, it's time to build a time travel component and become a time traveler like Emit.</Text><Text Key="BF63B93C">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="611A90DC">With the secrets of time travel unlocked, build the needed component and become your own time traveler!</Text><Text Key="5D16070B">Having put Nikolai Volt's theories into practice, the creation of a time traveling component has been invented... or reinvented!</Text><Text Key="8F20F39E">With the theoretical component brought to reality, it's time to put it to use.</Text><Text Key="9103CAEB">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="F458C270">With each part of the plan falling into place, hopefully nothing falls apart.</Text><Text Key="9E97751A">The time travel component has been installed, and a computer given sufficient power. Everything you've learned from Emit and the literature of Nikolai Volt is now in place!</Text><Text Key="B5887295">It's time to see if you can find the thief in action!</Text><Text Key="719BD652">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="1313A97D">Determined as ever, it's time for the final plan to be put into action.</Text><Text Key="328375ED">You've managed to catch the thief in action and get their personal email. Maybe you can use this to contact them directly!</Text><Text Key="9B31AAA0">Next up, find the reason this happened in the first place.</Text><Text Key="201D3629">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="3E37E4BB">Discover why this all happened to begin with.</Text><Text Key="006BE553">It turns out the thief was really just a super fan of the present and was trying to preserve items from the past for the future!</Text><Text Key="BF470F66">Time to resolve things with Emit.</Text><Text Key="67D2F073">Quest Complete!</Text><Text Key="168DF2C5">Emit can now return to his own time-traveling adventures.</Text><Text Key="48D30751">The Good Thief</Text><Text Key="72152038">The thief had the right intentions, but the wrong methods.\n\nAs a fan of time, they wanted to bring everything from the past to preserve in the present, and keep for the future.</Text><Text Key="17D10D7B">Who could blame the thief after all?</Text><Text Key="BC7C3204">Event Complete!</Text><Text Key="9C92F1F0">There is nothing to extinguish right now.</Text><Text Key="93E9FB48">(From the Scare Seeker Lot Challenge)</Text><Text Key="E3F57166">Goo Waste motive is locked because of the Ghost Mastery &lt;b&gt;Transcend Living Needs&lt;/b&gt;.</Text><Text Key="CC20EB5C">Ghosts need to expel Goo Waste. Send {0.SimFirstName} to use the toilet to prevent humiliating ectoplasmic leaks! </Text><Text Key="14B33583">Goo Waste</Text><Text Key="6B0072D1">Ghosts need sleep to recharge otherworldly energy to stay awake and active! </Text><Text Key="12E71F00">Otherworldly Slumber</Text><Text Key="A2B83CF6">Ghosts need to indulge in fun diversions to keep their ghostly spirits high. Find a TV, play some chess, or of course, play some music to dance!</Text><Text Key="B035C60D">Spooky Diversions</Text><Text Key="D4ED66E1">Ethereal Sustenance motive is locked because of the Ghost Mastery &lt;b&gt;Transcend Living Needs&lt;/b&gt;.</Text><Text Key="6116E753">Ghosts need to ingest ethereal energy from food to sustain themselves. Have a meal, order pizza, or grill something delicious!</Text><Text Key="558E377A">Ethereal Sustenance</Text><Text Key="A16CAF69">Apparition Cleansing motive is locked because of the Ghost Mastery &lt;b&gt;Transcend Living Needs&lt;/b&gt;.</Text><Text Key="6FDC662B">Ghost Sims need to use the shower or bathtub to Cleanse Apparition. This ritual purifies their form by refreshing their ghostly presence!</Text><Text Key="5B085822">Apparition Cleansing</Text><Text Key="15715AE1">Apparition Hydration</Text><Text Key="45E01040">Merfolk Ghosts can't stay dry for long! Going swimming, taking a bath, or even a nice drink of water will bring Apparition Hydration back up.</Text><Text Key="6E5D8DDB">Ghosts need to bond with other Ghosts or communicate with the living to maintain their connections to the world. Invite over a friend, chat someone up on the computer or phone, or just stop a neighbor walking by on the street.</Text><Text Key="D9199FF2">Ethereal Bonding</Text><Text Key="86F6A0E8">Life Event Activities</Text><Text Key="BCE5CE20">Ghost Full Body</Text><Text Key="3491E8A9">Enjoy this bright &amp; lively moss - perfect for wiggling your toes in.</Text><Text Key="7AEC2E8C">Bright Moss</Text><Text Key="B51D2CFE">Bursts of scruffy grass and bright, white flowers give life and character to every free-growing lawn.</Text><Text Key="8A92BD81">Weeds are Flowers Too</Text><Text Key="A49E500C">This murky, mottled moss is the perfect effect for any marshy environment.</Text><Text Key="CFE797C3">Murky Moss</Text><Text Key="5BD625A6">This rich moss thrives in moist environments and little light.</Text><Text Key="EE7092B9">Rich Moss</Text><Text Key="C198E6A8">A quick and easy solution for driveways, paths or just about anywhere - you'll have a "crush" in no time!</Text><Text Key="C9EBE9C7">Pebbles Please in Light</Text><Text Key="D9F09A13">A quick and easy solution for driveways, paths or just about anywhere - you'll have a "crush" in no time!</Text><Text Key="F87AD2C2">Pebbles Please in Lighter</Text><Text Key="2302C5DE">A quick and easy solution for driveways, paths or just about anywhere - you'll have a "crush" in no time!</Text><Text Key="3C0893E1">Pebbles Please in Clay</Text><Text Key="485A9709">A quick and easy solution for driveways, paths or just about anywhere - you'll have a "crush" in no time!</Text><Text Key="29B83E6C">Pebbles Please in White</Text><Text Key="AF9C13FC">A quick and easy solution for driveways, paths or just about anywhere - you'll have a "crush" in no time!</Text><Text Key="6AC2BB53">Pebbles Please in Grey</Text><Text Key="3D0BEDD4">Bits of grass break through the gravel between these pavers - showing they don't take themselves too seriously.</Text><Text Key="69E78ABB">Red Grassy Pavers</Text><Text Key="3B5A6FC1">Bits of grass break through the gravel between these pavers - showing they don't take themselves too seriously.</Text><Text Key="473B5DF4">Clay Grassy Pavers</Text><Text Key="7A426436">Bits of grass break through the gravel between these pavers - showing they don't take themselves too seriously.</Text><Text Key="B1F5E469">Grey Grassy Pavers</Text><Text Key="4615A36B">Bits of grass break through the gravel between these pavers - showing they don't take themselves too seriously.</Text><Text Key="8DB84C6A">Black Grassy Pavers</Text><Text Key="A02674C0">Bits of grass break through the gravel between these pavers - showing they don't take themselves too seriously.</Text><Text Key="4394878F">Light Grassy Pavers</Text><Text Key="AFDAE051">Neatly ordered but authentically placed pavers give character to a heat-struck backyard.</Text><Text Key="50CFA6A4">Red Gravel Pavers</Text><Text Key="449B8BA4">Neatly ordered but authentically placed pavers give character to a heat-struck backyard.</Text><Text Key="FBE7B4EB">Grey Gravel Pavers</Text><Text Key="F239E79F">Neatly ordered but authentically placed pavers give character to a heat-struck backyard.</Text><Text Key="ABD67F46">Clay Gravel Pavers</Text><Text Key="9512C7B2">Neatly ordered but authentically placed pavers give character to a heat-struck backyard.</Text><Text Key="F01EBA4D">Black Gravel Pavers</Text><Text Key="BE6B8ADD">Neatly ordered but authentically placed pavers give character to a heat-struck backyard.</Text><Text Key="15E332C8">Light Gravel Pavers</Text><Text Key="58934E62">We had extra pavers, so enjoy our brand new Fine Geometry Pavers as groundcover!</Text><Text Key="132EC4DD">A Fine Geometry Ground Pavers</Text><Text Key="84BD8140">{0.SimFirstName} needs to wait awhile before {0.SimPronounSubjective} can do this again!</Text><Text Key="B79061D7">These Sims can "borrow" things more easily from others with a swipe, but they will get Tense when they have not swiped anything in a while.</Text><Text Key="038FF7C6">No need for sorrow, this is the result of a long, long life.</Text><Text Key="FB20B746">Death by Murder of Crows</Text><Text Key="8DDF494E">Death by Murder of Crows</Text><Text Key="ABA03179">This Sim chose to tangle with the talons of the Crow Collective and came out a little less alive as a result.</Text><Text Key="DB7ACB03">Temporary Specter</Text><Text Key="A9338159">Temporary Specter</Text><Text Key="89BF4E9E">The Sim is temporary in the form of a ghost!</Text><Text Key="44269063">This Sim succumbed to Rabid Rodent Fever, and spreads fear of pestilence and disease in the afterlife.\n&lt;font color='#FF0000'&gt;In Live Mode, this Sim will be doomed to wear a giant, ghostly rat costume permanently!&lt;/font&gt;</Text><Text Key="AD9F0334">Grouch</Text><Text Key="0AA6C3A4">Grouch</Text><Text Key="8C3DC0FB">These Sims raise their Mischief skill faster by playing pranks and bothering others with their surprises.</Text><Text Key="59D604ED">Ghost</Text><Text Key="9A448CD3">Ghost</Text><Text Key="F6F4AB7F">Enhanced Kleptomaniac</Text><Text Key="22B643BB">(From Completing the Sticky Fingers Aspiration)</Text><Text Key="364B589D">Alien</Text><Text Key="41842089">Merfolk</Text><Text Key="E7F4A25C">Vampire</Text><Text Key="C01F532D">Werewolf</Text><Text Key="1417B1DB">Spellcaster</Text><Text Key="9C8CE258">Dying isn’t the end! When Sims meet their untimely (or timely) demise, a Sim can begin a new chapter by becoming a Ghost.\n\nBy choosing &lt;b&gt;Become a Playable Ghost&lt;/b&gt;, the Sim will remain in the Household and continue to be playable as a Ghostly presence.\nChoose &lt;b&gt;Become a Freeroaming Ghost&lt;/b&gt; if you would prefer this Sim &lt;i&gt;live on&lt;/i&gt; as a Ghost in an unplayed Household. These Sims will no longer be a played Sim but can still be found in the World.</Text><Text Key="68F05AE8">After selecting a death trait and transforming your Sim into a Ghost, it’s time to customize! Use the Ghost Overlay toggle to preview your Ghost Sim without the overlay for more detailed customization. You can switch the overlay back on at any time to view your Ghost Sim in the default view!</Text><Text Key="5375BFC0">In Create a Sim, you now have the option to create a Ghost! Next to the Aspiration trait icon, you'll find a new molecule that lets you choose from various death types. To revert your Sim back to a living state, simply select the 'X' on the cause of death icon. Please note that Toddler and Infant Sims cannot become Ghosts, and certain death types are restricted to specific age groups.</Text><Text Key="26699F75">Ghost Sims can be customized to wear any regular outfits available for living Sims, in addition to those exclusive to Ghosts! From casual wear to formal, the choice is yours to give your Ghost Sim a unique and personalized look that reflects their otherworldly style.</Text><Text Key="2C09EDB4">Create a Ghost</Text><Text Key="99215FD5">Dying isn’t the end! When Sims meet their untimely (or timely) demise, a Sim can begin a new chapter by becoming a Ghost.\n\nBy choosing &lt;b&gt;Become a Playable Ghost&lt;/b&gt;, the Sim will remain in the Household and continue to be playable as a Ghostly presence.\nChoose &lt;b&gt;Become a Freeroaming Ghost&lt;/b&gt; if you would prefer this Sim &lt;i&gt;live on&lt;/i&gt; as a Ghost in an unplayed Household. These Sims will no longer be a played Sim but can still be found in the World.</Text><Text Key="10511FE6">There's something in the air here that fills you with eldritch excitement, and attracts Sims looking for a ghoulishly good time.</Text><Text Key="06A5E1F9">Scare Seeker</Text><Text Key="50017390">This lot adds an exciting punch of terror to the otherwise daily mundane. Be it possessed TVs, netherworld treasures, or lowered bills—living or dead, there's something here for everybody!</Text><Text Key="630E7DBF">On Hallowed Grounds</Text><Text Key="B1430373">During an Event, spread joy by trying to Sabotage an Object or Plant, rot foods by Spreading Delicious Sauce, or just being Mean with others.</Text><Text Key="BF47CDC6">Look for an event that could be made funnier...in {1.SimFirstName}'s own away.</Text><Text Key="277D4421">{1.SimFirstName} can prepare for family expansion with some shopping!</Text><Text Key="7345FCAB">Time to get the blood pumping!</Text><Text Key="0B570052">Gaming can be very consoling...</Text><Text Key="304E30D1">Chaos. No such thing as a good party game without chaos.</Text><Text Key="05EB5E25">Have to make this jump!</Text><Text Key="04D800DF">{1.SimFirstName} has a Need for digital Speed.</Text><Text Key="0C5A5A12">New game! New world with dragons!</Text><Text Key="6A6F4536">Win or lose it'll be a GG.</Text><Text Key="C342A893">Sometimes it helps to read about a thing instead of doing it.</Text><Text Key="9189AE4D">Search for new pranks on the Web to increase {1.SimFirstName}'s Mischief skill.</Text><Text Key="CD1B843F">Sometimes {1.SimFirstName} just wants some &lt;i&gt;me time&lt;/i&gt; to feel better about {1.SimPronounReflexive}. What's so great about socializing anyway?</Text><Text Key="564920E7">Time to show who is the best!</Text><Text Key="273234E5">Life Event Activities</Text><Text Key="9AC94881">Show Lesson</Text><Text Key="5BC06D81">You have the freedom to customize your newly reborn Sim and can create new Sims to join the household. However, if there are existing household members, some customization restrictions may apply.</Text><Text Key="BB19A506">Path to Rebirth</Text><Text Key="F0C4C12C">Romance relationship is unavailable for Sim during Rebirth.</Text><Text Key="E8E5D05D">Ghosts can only be a child or older.</Text><Text Key="15063E09">Must have at least one other living Sim in household to enable Genetics. </Text><Text Key="C28CA441">Play with Sim's Genetics</Text><Text Key="512BB42E">Reset Sim to Resemble Past Life</Text><Text Key="8797AA08">Select Cause of Death</Text><Text Key="0E7C79CD">Select Occult</Text><Text Key="DBB7B208">Hey, nice to meet you! Feel free to assign my gender, adjust my appearance, and select my clothing. Thanks to my Sim Story, I already have aspirations, traits, and skills that you can update. Don't forget to give me a name!</Text><Text Key="21CD139A">The Sims™ 4 Artist Studio Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="21CD139B">The Sims™ 4 Storybook Nursery Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="21CD1398">The Sims™ 4 Sweet Slumber Party Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="21CD1399">The Sims™ 4 Cozy Kitsch Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="21CD1396">The Sims™ 4 Comfy Gamer Kit © 2025 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="21CD1397">The Sims™ 4 Secret Sanctuary Kit © 2025 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="20CD122B">The Sims™ 4 Casanova Cave Kit © 2025 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="20CD122A">The Sims™ 4 Refined Living Room Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="20CD1229">The Sims™ 4 Business Chic Kit © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="537FBE08">Lead XDev Object Artists - Cozy Kitsch</Text><Text Key="547FBFE3">Lead XDev Object Artists - Refined Living Room</Text><Text Key="85F2325E">Business Affairs, 1st Party Platform Partnerships</Text><Text Key="569877C9">Studios Data and Insights (DnA)</Text><Text Key="CB26A5C0">EAX Partner Excellence</Text><Text Key="C85D3175">EAX Quality Verification</Text><Text Key="E41DD975">“Wooflay”\nWritten, produced and recorded by Raney Shockne</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C4">"Conceited"\nPerformed by Lola Young\nWritten by Conor Dickinson (PRS), Jared Solomon (ASCAP), Lola Young (PRS), William Brown (PRS)\nPublished by Sony Music Publishing LLC, Day One Songs Limited, and Solomon Gouda\nRecording courtesy of Island Records Ltd. under license from Universal Music Enterprises</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C5">"Far Out"\nPerformed by Gretel\nWritten by Madeleine Haenlein (PRS), Alexander Crossan (PRS)\nPublished by Concord Sounds (ASCAP) c/o Concord Music Group, Inc. BMG Platinum Songs US (BMI) obo BMG Rights Management (UK) Limited (PRS / MCPS)\nRecording courtesy of Breadcrumb Records by arrangement with AWAL Recordings Ltd</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C2">"Ghost"\nPerformed by Saint Mesa\nWritten by Daniel Jeremiah McCook, Michael William Freesh\nPublished by BMG Platinum Songs US (BMI) obo Homeschool Bad Boys (BMI) and BMG Gold Songs (ASCAP) obo itself and Mastafader (ASCAP)\nAll rights administered by BMG Rights Management (US) LLC\nRecording courtesy of Saint Mesa Music</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C3">"Halloweenie VI: Possess Me"\nPerformed by Ashnikko\nWritten by Ashton Nicole Casey, Micah Jasper, Oscar Scheller, Galen Tipton\nPublished by WARNER CHAPPELL MUSIC LTD (PRS) All rights on behalf of WARNER CHAPPELL MUSIC LTD administered by WC Music Corp., Micah Jasper Copyright Control, BMG Gold Songs (ASCAP) obo BMG Rights Management (UK) Limited (PRS / MCPS), Galen Tipton Copyright Control\nRecording courtesy of Warner Music UK, Ltd.</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C0">"Nack Nostalgia"\nPerformed by Royel Otis\nWritten by Otis Daniel Pavlovic (ASCAP), Leroy Francis Bressington (ASCAP), Chris Collins\nPublished by Ourness Songs Pty Ltd (ASCAP) Admin by Kobalt Songs Music Publishing, Sony Music Publishing (Australia) Pty Limited\nRecording courtesy of Believe/Ourness</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0C1">"Nothing Matters"\nPerformed by The Last Dinner Party\nWritten by Rhys Downing (ASCAP), Abigail Morris (ASCAP), Georgia Davies (ASCAP), Aurora Nischevci (ASCAP), Emily Roberts (ASCAP), Elizabeth Mayland (ASCAP)\nPublished by Kobalt Music Services Ltd (KMS) (ASCAP)\nRecording courtesy of Island Records Ltd./Island Records under license from Universal Music Enterprises</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0CE">"Persuasion"\nPerformed by Wishy\nWritten by Kevin Paul Krauter (BMI)\nPublished by Winspear Publishing\nRecording courtesy of Winspear by arrangement with Local Rep. NYC</Text><Text Key="BAD4E0CF">“Zumbrie Gumbroe”\nWritten, produced and recorded by Charlton Pettus</Text><Text Key="F3AD7825">Lead Object Artist</Text><Text Key="2C316FF6">Lead, Research Operations</Text><Text Key="CC64136C">Lead XDev Character Artist</Text><Text Key="F241B889">Lead XDev Object Artist</Text><Text Key="B0A18233">Maxis would like to thank Alexandra Nistor "Create4sims," Monika Dugić "Simsphony,"  Sofia Sandvik "sofythesim," and Katharina Bruchmann "Kate Emerald" for their amazing talent and for helping us create the spooky and spectacular lots in Ravenwood.</Text><Text Key="023C1CBC">"CAPS LOCK"\nPerformed by CHINCHILLA\nWritten by Daisy Matilda Bertenshaw, Morten ‘Mört’ Jepsen\nPublished by Daisy Bertenshaw Chinchilla Music Ltd - Copyright Control (PRS), Morten ‘Mört’ Jepsen Copyright Control (KODA)\nRecording courtesy of Republic Records Ltd./Island Records under license from Universal Music Enterprises</Text><Text Key="1639EE9F">Object Artists</Text><Text Key="F615B650">Player &amp; Quality Insights: Quality Support &amp; Partnership</Text><Text Key="C6CE32DD">Project Development Director</Text><Text Key="2BEFFE7C">The Sims™ 4 Life &amp; Death Expansion Pack © 2024 Electronic Arts Inc.</Text><Text Key="5D3CE0A6">XDev Character Artist</Text><Text Key="6CD5A521">XDev Character Artists</Text><Text Key="52FA803A">XDev Object Artists</Text><Text Key="3045D1C7">Sweet Slumber Party Created By</Text><Text Key="3045D1C6">Cozy Kitsch Created By</Text><Text Key="2D45CD09">Refined Living Room Created By</Text><Text Key="2D45CD0A">Business Chic Created By</Text><Text Key="6108BDB7">Lead Concept Artist - Artist Studio</Text><Text Key="6108BDB6">Lead Concept Artist - Storybook Nursery</Text><Text Key="6108BDBB">Lead Concept Artist - Comfy Gamer</Text><Text Key="6108BDBA">Lead Concept Artist - Secret Sanctuary</Text><Text Key="6208BF26">Lead Concept Artist - Casanova Cave</Text><Text Key="B1DE8886">Lead Outsource Object Modeler - Artist Studio</Text><Text Key="B1DE8887">Lead Outsource Object Modeler - Storybook Nursery</Text><Text Key="23DB2F0D">Lead XDev Character Artist - Sweet Slumber Party</Text><Text Key="24DB30FC">Lead XDev Character Artists - Business Chic</Text><Text Key="BEE7E502">Lead Producer - Artist Studio</Text><Text Key="BEE7E503">Lead Producer - Storybook Nursery</Text><Text Key="BEE7E500">Lead Producer - Sweet Slumber Party</Text><Text Key="BEE7E501">Lead Producer - Cozy Kitsch</Text><Text Key="BEE7E50E">Lead Producer - Comfy Gamer</Text><Text Key="BEE7E50F">Lead Producer - Secret Sanctuary</Text><Text Key="BDE7E393">Lead Producer - Casanova Cave</Text><Text Key="BDE7E392">Lead Producer - Refined Living Room</Text><Text Key="BDE7E391">Lead Producer - Business Chic</Text><Text Key="0D944720">Maxis would like to thank SIXAMCC for collaborating with us on Storybook Nursery.</Text><Text Key="0D94472D">Maxis would like to thank lilsimsie for collaborating with us on Comfy Gamer.</Text><Text Key="0891935B">Technical Artist</Text><Text Key="FCACB061">Edit world is disabled during Rebirth</Text><Text Key="2944CEBA">Unable to exit to main menu during Rebirth.</Text><Text Key="D8E7E4AB">Unable to exit the game during Rebirth. Progress will not be saved. </Text><Text Key="9D5EDA7B">Save is unavailable during Rebirth</Text><Text Key="55D914BA">Rebirth {0.SimFirstName} {0.SimLastName} Into...</Text><Text Key="CE6DA0D4">Watch Now</Text><Text Key="610DF7E5">Buy now for bonus content!</Text><Text Key="A0A3C468">Owned</Text><Text Key="909A9B2B">Owned Expansion Packs</Text><Text Key="FEFC0550">Owned Game Packs</Text><Text Key="3AA3782F">Owned Kits</Text><Text Key="AFB5C290">Owned Stuff Packs</Text><Text Key="36E84CA7">EVENTS</Text><Text Key="BB414CE0">HOME</Text><Text Key="B63E5045">STORE</Text><Text Key="4F6AB02E">Question {0.Number} of {1.Number}</Text><Text Key="3E81E4E2">Unleash your\nImagination!</Text><Text Key="3362D6D0">Welcome to The Sims 4!</Text><Text Key="072A588F">Unavailable during Rebirth</Text><Text Key="DB531AAF">You must be a ghost to unlock the rest of the Soul's Journey.</Text><Text Key="460EBC69">Add Funeral Event</Text><Text Key="B5026B06">Funeral Event</Text><Text Key="5A40D320">Funeral Event:</Text><Text Key="65A3288C">&lt;font color="#8080FF"&gt;{0.String}&lt;/font&gt;</Text><Text Key="CD25E216">Ghost Mastery</Text><Text Key="3B06C4E7">Explore the Ghost Mastery panel to track progress, stamina, and access the perks panel. Ghost Mastery is categorized into Evil, Neutral, and Good, shaping the type of ghost a Sim can become. Hover over each ability in the perks panel to learn more.\n\nGhosts use stamina when performing abilities. As stamina depletes, ghosts will appear more faded, which can be monitored using the stamina meter.\n\nTo reset unlocked abilities, visit the the Well of Longing and Regret in Crow's Crossing neighborhood of Ravenwood at anytime.
</Text><Text Key="A6A5FCDA">Total days lived and in Afterlife: {0.Number}</Text><Text Key="26562CD3">&lt;b&gt;Rewards&lt;/b&gt;\nRewards will be given upon completion of the Quest.</Text><Text Key="D2C5B90E">Open '{0.String}'</Text><Text Key="FACA898D">Ended</Text><Text Key="78B427EC">Ends In:</Text><Text Key="80DCED2D">{0.Number}d {1.Number}h</Text><Text Key="33E2F689">{0.Number}h {1.Number}m</Text><Text Key="55D563A3">Ending Soon</Text><Text Key="4C75A49D">{0.GhostPowersPoints}</Text><Text Key="07A4B7F0">Resume Game</Text><Text Key="81F0543C">Rebirth</Text><Text Key="05550EEE">Rebirth into this household to join this family.</Text><Text Key="F2AEC572">Would you like to Rebirth into the {0.String} family?</Text><Text Key="821158EC">Rebirth into this household to join this family.</Text><Text Key="92E4D7BE">Automatic Death Inventory Handling:</Text><Text Key="61B2DEBB">If enabled, the Inventory of a previously played Sim will remain with the Ghost upon death. If disabled, a dialog will show at the Sim's Moment of Death with the various options available for their Inventory.</Text><Text Key="AF61A3A5">Enable Heirloom Creation:</Text><Text Key="CE0DF88A">When disabled, the &lt;b&gt;Make Heirloom&lt;/b&gt; interaction will be hidden from heirloom eligible objects.</Text><Text Key="3F484C9E">&lt;font color='#B755E1'&gt;(Blast from the Past Event reward)&lt;/font&gt;</Text><Text Key="EB47C321">View</Text></STBLKeyStringList>