<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="42406D2D">(From Reading Conspiracy Theories)</Text>
  <Text Key="DD3426DA">You have received Fan Mail. It is addressed to StrangerVille Hero. Check {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory to see what they got.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBA3C3D4">StrangerVille Fan Mail Received</Text>
  <Text Key="EF6ADEAF">The Vaccine has stopped the infection from taking hold. It seems {0.SimName} is immune to infection, for now...</Text>
  <Text Key="40370262">The Vaccine has stopped the Infection from taking hold. It seems {1.SimName} is immune to Infection, for now...</Text>
  <Text Key="D9FA9C8C">(From Drinking Infected Plasma)</Text>
  <Text Key="8EF87FD1">{1.SimFirstName} is Vaccinated and is temporarily protected from the infection. Recruit them to help fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="558DD872">The Vaccine seemed to caused some kind of reaction, but did not completely isolate the Infection. Keep testing on other Possessed Sims to see how it will react.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB319AE">Eureka! The Vaccine seems to be isolating the Infection. Head back to the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to create the &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; on the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D52F0AA">{0.SimFirstName} has successfully crafted an &lt;b&gt;Experimental Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;! Test this on Possessed Sims to learn how to craft the true Vaccine.\nReceived: \n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="2CB0B3CA">{0.SimFirstName} has successfully crafted an &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;! Use this on other Sims to Vaccinate and Recruit them to help you fight the Mother Plant.\nReceived: \n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="91669D7C">{0.SimFirstName}'s diligent analysis of the collected &lt;b&gt;Spore Cluster&lt;/b&gt; has paid off. Take this &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt; to a &lt;b&gt;StrangerVille Scientist&lt;/b&gt; to see if they have any helpful information.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC822319">You have successfully compiled a &lt;b&gt;Secret Dossier&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nThe Dossier can be used to Request a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;. I bet &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt;, or that &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop Owner&lt;/b&gt; would be very interested in seeing this. </Text>
  <Text Key="10ECB986">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Aerial Surveillance Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="27F83832">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Hastily-scrawled Note</Text>
  <Text Key="E74DFC01">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Infrared Microfilm</Text>
  <Text Key="A63A722F">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Partially Redacted Report</Text>
  <Text Key="95018DE0">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Strange Blueprints</Text>
  <Text Key="19688EF3">As {0.SimFirstName} leafs through the book, something interesting falls out:\n• Suspiciously Blurry Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="158BD04B">{0.SimFirstName} did not find anything useful on this computer. Maybe one of the others will have something.</Text>
  <Text Key="E7BB6EE5">{0.SimFirstName} hacked the computer and found:\n• Aerial Surveillance Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="DABD3C82">{0.SimFirstName} hacked the computer and found:\n• Infrared Microfilm</Text>
  <Text Key="21F5DEE2">{0.SimFirstName} hacked the computer and found:\n• Partially Redacted Report</Text>
  <Text Key="C09C6CEF">{0.SimFirstName} hacked the computer and found:\n• Strange Blueprints</Text>
  <Text Key="E0D55636">{0.SimFirstName} hacked the computer and found:\n• Suspiciously Blurry Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="8BA624F1">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Aerial Surveillance Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="134A9768">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Clandestine Dongle</Text>
  <Text Key="0853C311">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Encrypted USB Device\n\nA skilled Programmer might be able to decrypt it. It can be found in your Sim's inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AC7B4B8">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Glitched Hologram Readout</Text>
  <Text Key="A4A183EB">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Hastily-scrawled Note</Text>
  <Text Key="DEA262DE">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Infrared Microfilm</Text>
  <Text Key="4E76173B">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Packet of Mysterious Seeds</Text>
  <Text Key="2906FE46">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Partially Redacted Report</Text>
  <Text Key="B2205BFB">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Strange Blueprints</Text>
  <Text Key="29236AAA">{0.SimFirstName} found StrangerVille evidence:\n• Suspiciously Blurry Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="0824B675">This door is locked. Looks like it requires a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;. Someone around town might know how to get one. Before leaving, poke around the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to gather more information.\n\n&lt;b&gt;New Notebook Entry Added&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="B5F5599B">(From Being Exposed to Spores)</Text>
  <Text Key="BD3FD8AA">These &lt;b&gt;Spores&lt;/b&gt; are too toxic to pass without protection. &lt;b&gt;Question about Spores&lt;/b&gt; around town to see if there is some way to protect yourself.\n\n&lt;b&gt;New Notebook Entry Added&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="70F706CD">The &lt;b&gt;Local Library&lt;/b&gt; is known to have &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; researching the &lt;b&gt;StrangerVille Archives&lt;/b&gt;. I wonder what they are looking for...</Text>
  <Text Key="E4081520">Have you checked out the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop&lt;/b&gt; near the trailer park? I hear they have a &lt;b&gt;Secret Inventory&lt;/b&gt; that might be worth checking out.</Text>
  <Text Key="386E12F6">I heard there are strange things going on at that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. The &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; around here can probably shed some light on the situation.</Text>
  <Text Key="03D1981C">Check out the &lt;b&gt;Local Bar&lt;/b&gt;. There are always &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; unwinding after a long day on the base.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC2ED5AC">I have noticed those &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Plants&lt;/b&gt; have grown double in size, as if something is growing inside them.</Text>
  <Text Key="E422D296">That strange cloud that is building over the crater does not look normal. I bet something is trying to get out...</Text>
  <Text Key="5EA1CCF0">I overheard some &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; talking about an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; at the &lt;b&gt;Local Bar&lt;/b&gt;. they use it to uncover &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. You may want to convince one of them to give it to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="49276611">I overheard some &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; talking about &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;. Talk to them about spores and they may share some information.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0FD3702">The &lt;b&gt;Conspiracy Theorists&lt;/b&gt; around here believe the &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; is behind some kind of cover-up.</Text>
  <Text Key="E29A0CFD">I’ve heard there’s some kind of &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater outside town.</Text>
  <Text Key="65702BB2">I have noticed a lot more &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; at the &lt;b&gt;Local Library&lt;/b&gt;. You should check it out.</Text>
  <Text Key="78EC8AC0">The &lt;b&gt;Local Library&lt;/b&gt; holds tons of history about StrangerVille. There are always &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; browsing the &lt;b&gt;StrangerVille Archives&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0895ABC">Have you been noticing those &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Plants&lt;/b&gt; popping up around town? You best keep your distance from them. The local &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; have been running tests on them.</Text>
  <Text Key="A47B6536">I am always curious what goes on in that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. After that explosion a few weeks back I have not seen anyone go in or out.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD239832">You should really check out that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. I hear there are strange things going on there. You should be able to sneak in through the back gate.</Text>
  <Text Key="3115FC3C">The &lt;b&gt;Local Bar&lt;/b&gt; is known to have &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; winding down after a long day on the base.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F46E2E">Wow, you did it! Let me analyze this &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt; and I will send you a &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt; in the mail soon. Keep digging and you might find a &lt;b&gt;Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; for this Infection after all.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AE836B4">Did you really think that you could beat me up and take my scanner? Think again!</Text>
  <Text Key="47AF50AB">I yield! Take my &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. You've earned it. Just stop hurting me!</Text>
  <Text Key="EDF4744B">You have got to be joking... You think that is "Impressive." You are going to have to get stronger if you are going to impress me.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E818C53">Wow! that was an impressive display of strength. Look... I really should not be doing this but I think you should have this &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. You can use this to reveal &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; that are otherwise invisible to the naked eye.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C3FE7E7">I have some information about what is going on in that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;, but I will only share that with close friends.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF04F7D4">I am not sure if I can trust you. We barely even know each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="17C5C79F">I can't really say what's going on. My CO plays things pretty close to the chest. We're always kept on high alert in case something happens at the nearby lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="292315EA">There is something shady about that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. I think there is a major cover up brewing.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA118DEE">That &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; is cursed. Everyone that works there is cursed!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7A7CD38">Look...I really should not be saying this, but there are some strange things going on at that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. There was some big explosion and now everything is sealed shut.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8BDB94D">I know something is going on at that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. No one ever goes in and out of it. They must be holding something in there...</Text>
  <Text Key="C260AC26">I hear that the &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; is hiding something in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. They have doubled security ever since that big explosion.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F3A7061">I have a few theories about what is going on in that lab, but I am not going to share that with just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA3FE4E3">We are instructed to keep quiet about all information regarding the Secret Lab. I can't share that information with just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="5DDF2322">I used to work in that lab, but ever since the explosion... I have said too much. I can't share that information with strangers.</Text>
  <Text Key="726FEA54">I have been noticing a lot more of these &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; around town. I bet anything if you can get close to one of them they would be willing to give you a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; for that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="31DE0B25">There is much more to that &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; than you know. You should keep digging. </Text>
  <Text Key="7CFA37C0">&lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; are always hanging out at the local bar. I bet they have heightened security because something went wrong at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;!</Text>
  <Text Key="81316441">Secret Lab... are you kidding me!? Why would I put my life on the line for you? I hardly know you.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD433E50">I barely even know you! What makes you think I would risk my life to help defeat this "&lt;b&gt;Mother Plant&lt;/b&gt;" you speak of. That is nothing but a bunch of mumbo jumbo.</Text>
  <Text Key="B7280F30">You want me to go down there with YOU!? What do you know about fighting giant alien plants? We hardly even know each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="635822F9">Of course I'll help you destroy the Mother Plant. I am all for clearing StrangerVille of this vile infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="949A9300">I think I have a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; in my &lt;b&gt;Secret Inventory&lt;/b&gt;. I will only sell this to you if you can prove you are committed to this StrangerVille Investigation. Maybe if you have a &lt;b&gt;Secret Dossier&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="1827F238">Look... I really should not be doing this, but you seem like you can help with this terrible situation. Take this &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;. This will give you access to all the doors in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. Just be careful, no one has been down there since we sealed the doors.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CBA649F">I hear the &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; have access to a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;. Try asking them.</Text>
  <Text Key="D257D9A2">I'm just an old retired fighter pilot. Do you really think I would have access to some fancy &lt;b&gt;Key Card&lt;/b&gt;? I bet one of those &lt;b&gt;Scientist&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; would have something for you. I doubt they are just handing those things out tho.</Text>
  <Text Key="640E5823">I am not sure what you're talking about. I bet the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop&lt;/b&gt; near the trailer park might be able to help you out.</Text>
  <Text Key="F44E2505">Wow! Thanks, but no thanks. I'm keeping my Infection scanner.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE340212">Wow... that was amazing! I really should not be doing this but take this &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E04245">Those &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Plants&lt;/b&gt; around town are part of something much bigger. I'm not saying that they're controlling people, but I have seen some very strange behavior from people recently.</Text>
  <Text Key="8F2EC6C6">These dust particles in the sky are loaded with strange bacteria! The Military is putting it there on purpose. They are running test on us like we are some kind of test subject!</Text>
  <Text Key="CB63F7A6">That &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt; that has been popping up around town is the cause of all this! DO NOT EAT IT! I don't even know where people are getting it from.</Text>
  <Text Key="F802F305">Look... there are some really strange things going on in this town. It all started a couple weeks ago. There was a large explosion inside that crater and things have not quite been the same since!</Text>
  <Text Key="59CEF3A0">I just got this new &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. It is really cool, it can.... I mean... That is classified information! But if you can convince me maybe I can give you one...</Text>
  <Text Key="59CEF3A3">There is something big going on here! The &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop&lt;/b&gt; owner has started selling &lt;b&gt;Hazmat Suits&lt;/b&gt;. I noticed everyone has been stocking up, but I fear that may not be enough...</Text>
  <Text Key="59CEF3A5">I have a couple of those &lt;b&gt;Hazmat Suits&lt;/b&gt; in my &lt;b&gt;Secret Inventory&lt;/b&gt;. I doubt they will do much good without a &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;, but I would be willing to sell it to you if you are still interested.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C549977">I have the materials to craft a &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;, but I have not been able to analyze enough &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. Use the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt; at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to construct the &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;. Bring it to me and I can construct a &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="81ECB4DA">You already have the &lt;b&gt;Incomplete Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt;. Question about Spores with &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; to see if they can improve it.</Text>
  <Text Key="54AEEBD6">You already have the &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;. Question about Spores with the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop Owner&lt;/b&gt; to see if he can sell you something to combine it with.</Text>
  <Text Key="06A8CD08">You already have an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. You can use that to scan areas for &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. I bet there are a ton at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="470FE56E">The StrangerVille Hacker Forums thanks you for your upload. We will review your submission, and get back to you within &lt;b&gt;1 Day&lt;/b&gt;. We can't say much, but make sure to keep a close eye on your &lt;b&gt;Mail Box&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="5970A53F">(From Admiring Achievements and Accolades)</Text>
  <Text Key="E827CC40">(From Being Ordered To Clean)</Text>
  <Text Key="5C9E357E">(From Poring Over Case Files)</Text>
  <Text Key="8CF71850">(From Running Drills)</Text>
  <Text Key="E8D36529">Your &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; requisition form has been received. We will follow up in a few days when it has been processed.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9037663">(From Requesting Energy From the Mother Plant)</Text>
  <Text Key="16D87883">The Mother Plant won't go down easy. Recruit more Sims to help, or craft some extra Vaccines to throw at her!</Text>
  <Text Key="1AD88A87">The Mother Plant is extremely powerful. Best not fight her alone.\n\nYou can now create &lt;b&gt;Vaccines&lt;/b&gt; on the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt;.\n\nVaccinate and Recruit other Sims to fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="E849F5A9">(From Losing to The Mother Plant)</Text>
  <Text Key="35A0AF3B">(From Mother Plant)</Text>
  <Text Key="AF4A39BC">(From Requesting Success From the Mother Plant)</Text>
  <Text Key="21444296">ĴØIŇ UŞ IŇ ŦĦ€ ĆŘΔŦ€Ř</Text>
  <Text Key="6EAE895F">(From Training Bot)</Text>
  <Text Key="3C2123B2">&lt;b&gt;Newspaper Clipping:&lt;/b&gt; “After the incident, there have been reports of Bizarre Plants growing around town. No one has been able to figure out why they are spreading so quickly. Efforts to eradicate them have been fruitless; for each sprout removed, three grow back in its place.”</Text>
  <Text Key="4A946F9B">&lt;b&gt;Old Newspaper Clipping:&lt;/b&gt; “The Military Arrives in StrangerVille! Residents rejoice as a new base opens near the crater. The City Council welcomes the opportunity of new jobs for the struggling town.”</Text>
  <Text Key="14A7664A">&lt;b&gt;Letter to the Editor:&lt;/b&gt; “They say they’re here to help us, but there’s barbed-wire around the crater now! What are they trying to hide??? Doesn’t anyone see what’s going on here?!? Wake up, sheeple! Also, a quick shout out to the Curio Shop near the old mobile home park. They have some great shirts and posters for those of us in-the-know.”</Text>
  <Text Key="7D0F0883">&lt;b&gt;Unsolved Mysteries of StrangerVille:&lt;/b&gt; “A local resident claims that after he found his lost cat outside the crater, it became unreasonably afraid of his houseplants and wouldn’t stop hissing until they were all removed from the property.”</Text>
  <Text Key="86A70B80">&lt;b&gt;Promotional Flyer:&lt;/b&gt; “Clogged drains? Call Undercover Plumbers for a free inspection. We’re available at all hours, even when you’re not at home! Our state-of-the-art vans are equipped with the latest in satellite-uplink plumbing technology.”</Text>
  <Text Key="31E43064">&lt;b&gt;Recent Newspaper Clipping:&lt;/b&gt; “New Era for StrangerVille! A high-tech super-science facility is being constructed in the crater. While residents are eager to modernize the town, the amount of secrecy surrounding the project has some people on edge.”</Text>
  <Text Key="3901930B">&lt;b&gt;A History of StrangerVille:&lt;/b&gt; "Stories passed down by the indigenous people who lived in the region long ago speak of a blinding purple light in the sky followed by a massive explosion. It is believed that this is the source of the StrangerVille crater.”</Text>
  <Text Key="54FEBC6A">Nothing to see here. Move along.</Text>
  <Text Key="261F2516">Have you been to the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; yet, Soldier? If you’re rank 5 or above, you can use a computer to requisition a keycard to restricted areas.</Text>
  <Text Key="0196980B">I actually don’t know much about StrangerVille. Up until recently, I spent most of my time at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater.</Text>
  <Text Key="4513ED24">This has always been a military town, but it sure seems like there's a lot more of them around lately.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FF18711">There’s nothing interesting at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater. Especially not in the basement. Don’t bother going there.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBFF186F">People shouldn’t worry about the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater. We have top people working on it right now. Top. People.</Text>
  <Text Key="D42F096D">There’s some kind of cover-up going on. I’ve been listening in on the &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; people at the &lt;b&gt;local bar&lt;/b&gt; to see if I can figure anything out.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CC9862F">Those crackpot &lt;b&gt;Conspiracy Theorists&lt;/b&gt; think there’s a cover-up at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater, but they haven’t got a clue.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB8D3A6C">There’s some very interesting plant life around here. Have you seen any of it yet? I don’t advise messing with it too much.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0E1A3B7">The &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater outside town is off-limits to civilians. Under no circumstances should you go there.</Text>
  <Text Key="00C6017D">Have you heard of the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater? I wanna go see it.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFC14452">I’ve heard there’s some kind of &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater. I’m convinced it has something to do with the weird storm that caused my plane to crash.</Text>
  <Text Key="109C2E8A">You may have heard rumors about an explosion at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater. Totally false! There’s nothing interesting going on there at all. Move along.</Text>
  <Text Key="46F58AB6">Hello, Soldier. As you know, guarding the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater is our top priority.</Text>
  <Text Key="FC506E30">The implications of what we’ve discovered in the &lt;b&gt;crater&lt;/b&gt; are astounding! I mean… er… the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; is totally boring and not worth even thinking about.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F803ECD">It’s our job to protect these people from whatever it is those science geeks found in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. I wonder what’s in the restricted area…</Text>
  <Text Key="186251F0">Even though we’re Military, they won’t let us see all of the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater. Have you been there yet, soldier?</Text>
  <Text Key="E11AFCB7">StrangerVille is a lovely town. I hope you enjoy your time here, just stay away from the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC754EEC">I don’t have lots of time to talk, I’m busy studying some of the plants around town. Fascinating!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB52D122">I worked at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; in the crater until recently. Now my attention is on the town itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCDFEEE3">If someone got enough &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; they might be able to use it to get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the lower floors of the lab. Let’s all hope that doesn’t happen.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0EF0B19">There are ways to get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the basement of the Secret Lab if you get enough &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; of the strange stuff going on in town.</Text>
  <Text Key="44DC1962">I got a piece of &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; about the StrangerVille mystery from a &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; officer I befriended.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6FF8664">I bet if you get enough &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; of the weird stuff happening, you could convince a &lt;b&gt;Scientist&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Military officer&lt;/b&gt; to give you a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5A92544">I have some &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; of what’s been going on, but I’m not supposed to talk about it.</Text>
  <Text Key="E68007C3">Military ranked Warrant Officer (level 5) or above can get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the restricted area of the lab. Just use a computer to &lt;b&gt;Requisition a Keycard&lt;/b&gt; and they’ll mail one to you. I've heard civilians are finding ways to get them too though.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF40196E">I convinced one of the &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; to show me some &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; about the covert operations here in StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="25FB1892">I was told to be on the lookout for someone asking for &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; from the local &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt;. Do you know anything about that?</Text>
  <Text Key="7DB8E365">Some sinister stuff is going on around here. If I knew someone trustworthy enough, I might even show them the &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; I found.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE36D502">I’ve been told that if anyone asks me for &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt;, I should report them. But I’m starting to think the public should hear about what’s going on.</Text>
  <Text Key="B4F038F6">I heard someone has been poking around the Secret Lab. As long as they don’t get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the lower floors, things won’t get out of hand.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A7BAF4D">The &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; are the only ones who have access to the restricted area of the lab. Maybe you can get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; from one of them.</Text>
  <Text Key="5E88B493">You can get a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to the basement of the Secret Lab if you get enough &lt;b&gt;Evidence&lt;/b&gt; of the strange stuff going on in town.</Text>
  <Text Key="65090189">I bet there’s all kinds of weird stuff behind that locked door in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;, but you need a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to get in.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDB4E38D">My friend dared me to go into the basement of the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;, but I’m too freaked out! Plus, I don’t have a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to open the door.</Text>
  <Text Key="844B1D8A">Even if I had a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;, I don’t think I’d go through the locked door in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="1BA6DBAF">Hi, Soldier. Only people with a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; can get to the basement levels of the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. I’ve heard there’s some weird stuff down there.</Text>
  <Text Key="36CEC1BF">There are restricted areas in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;, but you need a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; to get in.</Text>
  <Text Key="689121A8">I know it can be tempting to see what’s in the &lt;b&gt;restricted area of the lab&lt;/b&gt;, Soldier, but I advise against going in there, even if you have a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD8F6C88">Only people with a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; can get to the basement levels of the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. I’ve heard there’s some weird stuff down there.</Text>
  <Text Key="993B9309">Someone has released spores from the lab! With enough &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; analyzed at the Lab, I could create a &lt;b&gt;breathing filter&lt;/b&gt; for them.</Text>
  <Text Key="96F820A7">Someone broke into the lab and released spores! We’re using our &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanners&lt;/b&gt; to find them.</Text>
  <Text Key="51115DAF">I heard a Scientist talking about &lt;b&gt;analyzing Spore clusters&lt;/b&gt; at the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="91F09140">I’ve been watching; the Military are using &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanners&lt;/b&gt; to find &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. Then they take them to the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F538D0A">Soldier, the Scientists need &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. Our orders are to use an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to find them.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C5045BD">I wonder if I could convince someone in the &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; to give me an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;…</Text>
  <Text Key="AD9FF369">The Military is gathering &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;, then we need to &lt;b&gt;analyze them at the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="8831A43D">It looks like the Scientists want &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and the Military is using &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanners&lt;/b&gt; to find them.</Text>
  <Text Key="589663EA">The Scientists want &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. We can use our &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to find them. Have you found any yet, Soldier?</Text>
  <Text Key="454F5FB7">With all these spores in the air, a &lt;b&gt;Breathing Filter&lt;/b&gt; would be useful. I could create one if I had &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt; from analyzing &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; at the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="EEF3FED7">Have you seen all the spores in the air? Something must’ve happened at the lab! I heard the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop&lt;/b&gt; has some kind of protective gear, maybe I should look into that.</Text>
  <Text Key="C07A76D4">Some Military officers were talking about gathering &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; to &lt;b&gt;analyze at the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="3DE14930">Hey, Soldier, have you been given an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; yet? You can use them to detect &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A0A0ECF">I saw some Military people gathering &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; with an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="03B17478">Move along, citizen, I need to use my &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to find &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; so we can &lt;b&gt;analyze them at the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="89A399ED">Oh my goodness! Something crazy is going on!</Text>
  <Text Key="BDDFC5F9">Everyone is acting super weird! My friend wouldn’t even talk with me, they just had this creepy look on their face.</Text>
  <Text Key="8CDC5F47">This is insane, right? I hope someone finds a cure for the spore infections!</Text>
  <Text Key="906E1810">I heard there was some kind of monster in the lab and it’s the source of all this!</Text>
  <Text Key="E413845F">I’m so glad things are back to normal!</Text>
  <Text Key="88778939">I wonder if the whole “Mother Plant” thing was a hoax. I mean, does anyone have any proof?</Text>
  <Text Key="B1974956">I wonder if they’ll reopen the science facility in the crater? Surely nothing bad could come of it.</Text>
  <Text Key="42291084">Now that those crazy plants are gone, maybe we can get back to things that matter like collecting rocks and cooking grilled cheese sandwiches.</Text>
  <Text Key="2DB2F79C">Don’t tell anyone but… I kinda miss those weird plants.</Text>
  <Text Key="03DB2E6E">I know we’re all safe now, but I can’t get the image of all those possessed weirdos’ faces out of my mind!</Text>
  <Text Key="620A295A">That was some weird, wild stuff, right?!? Luckily it all seemed to work out.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A6C06BF">Things seem like they’re back to normal… for now.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A1BA6B4">People are strange when you're in StrangerVille. Faces look shady when you're in town.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D579CB1">*KRRRRSSHHHHHZZZZTTTTHHZZZZ* (Something seems to be blocking the signal)</Text>
  <Text Key="004B9ABD">"I'm telling you, there is SOMETHING happening in the crater! I've seen the lights in the sky!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="5851B1BA">"Yeah, yeah, a 'weather balloon' crashed in the crater. That's what THEY want you to think."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="8CC78866">"Someone's gotta sneak into that lab and figure out what is going on!!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="CFA62C17">"I don't trust fruit anymore, and neither should you."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="E864DEB5">"If there's nothing in the lab, why aren't we allowed in?! Explain that!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="A71B138F">Some of this lab equipment is crazy advanced... I've never seen anything like it!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="D973F71A">Of course I could get you into the lab... for a price."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="FA0112A7">"No, General, I don't know where those seeds came from..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="8A370DC6">"I gotta keep moving... the military is on my tail!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="EDE14821">"Been finding a lot of weird stuff in that crater... gotta be worth something!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="DA1C3980">"They don't let me into that base anymore... not that I'd ever go back!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="258B7F05">"They think they have it under control. Psshh. More like it's got THEM under control."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="BC81B1C8">"They say it's some freak lightning storm, but I don't buy it. Ain't never seen a storm like that before..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="42803C6C">"Buncha cowards. Abandoned that lab as soon as things got rough."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="C816FA2E">"I feel safer away from town... can't trust anyone these days."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="4220C0A9">"I've seen some crazy stuff in my day, but that lab... still gives me the shivers thinking about it."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="9A51A030">"I know what the colonel said but... c'mon, the people have to know what's going on in that crater!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="BBD86440">"There's only one guard at the lab!? What if someone sneaks in!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="1F115FAC">"The order came from the very top... no one is allowed back in the lab."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="4153F40B">"No one knows where it came from... even the eggheads can't figure it out."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="B0119201">"... I told him my favorite color is blue... but it's not... it's yellow..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="B883291C">"I mean... everyone's got a secret child somewhere, right?"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="C1FD1F4D">"I mean, what's one... okay, ten... little lies?"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="D5ED0136">"...if this gets out, I could be in HUGE trouble..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="22A8725C">"...it's not stealing if I REALLY want it, right? They won't miss it anyways..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="63EF2015">"... don't tell anyone, okay?... no, not even your cat..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="2969564D">"... sure, some people have skeletons in their closet... I've got an entire GRAVEYARD in there..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="28A2FC57">"... of course I trust you with this information... you're the only friend I have!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="24DB2190">"...c'mon, you agree right? Her new haircut is awful!... just don't tell her I said that..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="1DAD4F89">"I may have committed some... light treason."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="A36D2C72">"You're sure no one is listening?... Okay, I'll tell you..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="DD54064E">"What he doesn't know, won't hurt... me... so, it's fine."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="63D0882D">"Don't worry where the money came from... it's fine... nobody is gonna find out!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="D408E913">"If the government knew what I was up to... well, let's just make sure they don't find out..."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="DEEFF6DB">"... but you gotta keep that secret. No one can know!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="E927E44B">"And they were like, 'Please, spare me! I have a family!'... Hilarious. Love this job."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="D79B6803">"All those gravestones? Cardboard and duct tape."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="46E8D376">"Oh, I much prefer cats... They're tastier AND less filling!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="FDD0E091">"Don't tell anyone, but I'm not wearing anything under this cloak."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="EE59C7D3">"Y'know, no one asks old Grim how he's feeling."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nBasic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="DB6B53EA">"Science can't explain what we found down there... it's... otherworldly."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="DC552AA9">"I'm just a botanist, I don't know anything about space rocks!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="8C125C1B">"That... thing... in the lab... the whole town is in danger!"\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="AD7F5734">"I'm never stepping foot in that lab again! I might as well burn my keycard."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="8C5ED91B">"The things they made us do in that lab... I still have nightmares."\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\nTop Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="9E368935">The hacker community has come through. {0.SimFirstName}'s &lt;b&gt;Key Card&lt;/b&gt; has been delivered to their mailbox.</Text>
  <Text Key="377C9232">The StrangerVille Hacker Forums really appreciates your "donation", {0.SimFirstName}'s keycard is out for delivery. Keep an eye on your mail for a special delivery.</Text>
  <Text Key="138CE9C3">Your &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; is out for delivery. Keep an eye on your &lt;b&gt;Mailbox&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="D79AF9DC">Your &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; requisition request has been approved. Please allow 1-2 days for delivery.</Text>
  <Text Key="7662768B">{0.SimFirstName} should check the mail. {M0.His}{F0.Her} &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt; has been delivered to {M0.his}{F0.her} mailbox.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B475BA8">{0.SimFirstName}, I ran some tests on that &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;. I constructed a &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt; that will attach to any &lt;b&gt;Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt;. This will give you everything you need to go deeper into the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. Keep an eye on your mailbox for a special delivery.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B857619">Some of the townsfolk have expressed some concerns about some incident that happened. It might be helpful to question people around town to see whats going on.</Text>
  <Text Key="80FDFF81">New Resident</Text>
  <Text Key="7D80ECFA">Seems as if some people in StrangerVille are hiding some rather valuable information. It might be worth digging a bit deeper to see whats really going on here.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4B2A4C2">Personal Spy</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB7E113">The Secret Lab is containing some viral outbreak. Try to equip yourself with the necessary tools to investigate a Vaccine.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3F22DCB">Pathogenic Investigator</Text>
  <Text Key="8F6AF634">You have found the source of the infection. It is time to recruit enough people to stop it.</Text>
  <Text Key="BECEACAC">StrangerVille Hero</Text>
  <Text Key="2A765B65">After much planning and investigation, and perhaps a bit of unconventional combat, {0.SimFirstName} has freed StrangerVille from the clutches of the Mother Plant. StrangerVille can now sleep safe and sound. \n\nTrait Earned: Hero of StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="04A05261">StrangerVille is holding some deep dark secret, and this Sim wants to uncover why all the townsfolk are acting a bit strange.</Text>
  <Text Key="9EB42F35">StrangerVille Mystery</Text>
  <Text Key="C00A4F8C">Pore Over Case Files</Text>
  <Text Key="6EFAA333">Pore Over Case Files</Text>
  <Text Key="ADEDD474">Builds Logic at the cost of a little stress.</Text>
  <Text Key="01D3FE62">Run Drills</Text>
  <Text Key="2DF8B671">Run Drills</Text>
  <Text Key="48737B5A">Builds Fitness at the cost of some fatigue.</Text>
  <Text Key="3EC64477">(From Being Scanned)</Text>
  <Text Key="B52E5D46">My superior told me to clean...Now I must clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="D43B8ED9">Ordered to Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="BEEBDD1D">What is going on here! These plants are getting out of control!</Text>
  <Text Key="D1025A08">Botanophobia</Text>
  <Text Key="4CCCEAA3">(From Plants in Plumbing)</Text>
  <Text Key="84E49B85">Admiring the amount of medals in the case can fill any Sim with a large amount of confidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="843E8380">Admiring Major Achievements</Text>
  <Text Key="F26734A3">Admiring the amount of medals in the case can fill any Sim with a small amount of confidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="C632D772">Admiring Minor Achievements</Text>
  <Text Key="36F4C73C">Admiring the amount of medals in the case can fill any Sim with a medium amount of confidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="AACFD193">Admiring Quality Achievements</Text>
  <Text Key="1B1E077F">Sometimes it's not worth looking at all of those old case files. It can be pretty stressful at time.</Text>
  <Text Key="4BEE27A6">Pored to the Breaking Point</Text>
  <Text Key="4CCAF245">Running extra drills has aggravated muscles that you didn't know you had.</Text>
  <Text Key="A72DD440">Tough Drills</Text>
  <Text Key="8BF05814">You are bursting with the Mother Plant's power!</Text>
  <Text Key="BBE910FB">Overwhelming Power</Text>
  <Text Key="8DF85580">The Mother Plant is extremely powerful. Best not fight her alone. Try vaccinating and recruiting allies to help defeat her.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E45934F">Overwhelmed by The Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="1E6735C9">The Mother Plant is extremely powerful. Regroup and reanalyze your strategy in order to achieve victory.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9964D2C">Destroyed by Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="12ED9900">The Mother Plant has granted your Sim ultimate career success.</Text>
  <Text Key="5EB305CF">Overwhelming Focus</Text>
  <Text Key="350BF558">Cannot do this while possessed!</Text>
  <Text Key="BFCCBC9A">You and your allies will deal more damage to the Mother Plant, but will also take on more Infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="63F77EC5">Charge!</Text>
  <Text Key="6924B912">You and your allies will take on less Infection but will deal less damage to the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="BE61302D">Be Careful!</Text>
  <Text Key="FF19FC5C">You and your allies are recovering from Infection and will deal no damage to the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="74747933">Taking a Breather</Text>
  <Text Key="8F2DA434">You and your allies cry out repelling the Mother Plant's Minions.</Text>
  <Text Key="DC994F9B">Warbling War Cry!</Text>
  <Text Key="C491FCD8">ŦĦ€ ΜØŦĦ€Ř ĆΔŁŁŞ ΔŇĐ I ΜUŞŦ Ř€ŞPØŇĐ</Text>
  <Text Key="32ABF857">Possessed</Text>
  <Text Key="4A27DD0F">The machines still remain our superior... for now.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA3118D6">Botted and Bruised</Text>
  <Text Key="E0F2A9E4">People just don't understand! When something happens, they will have wished they listened.</Text>
  <Text Key="2775892B">Surrounded by Skeptics</Text>
  <Text Key="F329E73F">Other people on the internet agreed with me so it must be true!</Text>
  <Text Key="D780E766">Theory Confirmed!</Text>
  <Text Key="654CD6E2">Danger lurks around every corner! Better stay inside to avoid any danger.</Text>
  <Text Key="02BBF65D">They're Out To Get Us!</Text>
  <Text Key="099214E6">Nothing beats being deep underground surrounded by concrete, shelter, and pure safety.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF3CB0F9">Safe and Secure</Text>
  <Text Key="0F0A725B">(From Paranoid Trait)</Text>
  <Text Key="B888AD09">Paranoid Sims don't like being around others that are whispering. What are they talking about? Are they talking about me!?</Text>
  <Text Key="A19AA06C">What are They Talking About?</Text>
  <Text Key="887B073E">Possessed</Text>
  <Text Key="68479682">Curios, Creations, and More!</Text>
  <Text Key="9E8CD5DB">The Bureau</Text>
  <Text Key="1A888BE2">StrangerVille National Base</Text>
  <Text Key="4A62BB2E">Curio Shop Owner</Text>
  <Text Key="8ED2F52C">Practice Chess ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="AD5184C9">Evidence Eraser</Text>
  <Text Key="91EEFF12">As an Evidence Eraser {0.SimFirstName} is required to clear all evidence of top secret case files. If any of that evidence slipped out into the public there would be mass panic.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BC39E7F">Monitor other Sims ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="2636F3B0">Conspiracy Squelcher</Text>
  <Text Key="51B1DEEB">Conspiracy Squelchers are the front lines in stopping all talks of conspiracies around town. If there is any talk of discussion of the strange phenomena it is {0.SimFirstName}'s duty to put a stop to it.</Text>
  <Text Key="2FAB9556">Search the Stars ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="CB82FA9B">Clandestine Investigator</Text>
  <Text Key="06C2FDB4">Clandestine Investigators have proven they are able to undergo secret covert missions. {0.SimFirstName} must investigate the strange happenings around town, and will be required to plant bugs to listen in on the unsuspecting.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E223A19">File Reports ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="7529485A">[REDACTED]</Text>
  <Text Key="EA8A51ED">[REDACTED]</Text>
  <Text Key="9F5BA318">Plan 10 Moves Ahead ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="7B161445">Sim-In-Black</Text>
  <Text Key="65CC126E">Sim-In-Black is the highest honor in the entire Covert Ops branch. There are only a few Sim-In-Blacks in the world and {0.SimFirstName} is now one of the few.</Text>
  <Text Key="05EE26B4">Work Out ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="A9A9E341">Raw Recruit</Text>
  <Text Key="5D25B99A">As a Raw Recruit {0.SimFirstName} will need to build their physical fitness in order to rise through the ranks of the Military Career.</Text>
  <Text Key="AFA9AD27">March Around ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="141C7828">Private Fourth Class</Text>
  <Text Key="483EDA73">Privates are the back bone of the day to day work around the base. {0.SimFirstName} must carry out any and all orders given to them.</Text>
  <Text Key="C9BF9F1E">Go Jogging  ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="CF0AC5F3">Lacking Corporal</Text>
  <Text Key="A988ACFC">Corporals are the key to base security. {0.SimFirstName} will begin to train and master sparring techniques in order to defend any threats to the base.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF7F6381">Spar With Others ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="6A55F612">Sergeant Minor</Text>
  <Text Key="BD117655">Sergeant Minors have mastered the art of Sparring. {0.SimFirstName} can demonstrate their mastery while competing with others in hand to hand combat.</Text>
  <Text Key="7E29AE40">Workout ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="14A9C85D">Warrant Officer</Text>
  <Text Key="175163B6">Warrant Officers have demonstrated they know their way around all combat drills and exercises. Keep improving your physical fitness and {0.SimFirstName} will soon be able to order platoons.</Text>
  <Text Key="ACCA5A95">Practice Speech ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="5A8CE196">Fourth Lieutenant</Text>
  <Text Key="DA593449">Lieutenants have proven they can master all physical challenges and are now fit to Order platoons and train them to the best of their ability.</Text>
  <Text Key="95185F8E">Give Orders ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="D63BC803">Courageous Captain</Text>
  <Text Key="BE34E62C">Captains are the most battle hardened veterans anyone could hope to be. {0.SimFirstName} is the focal point of any company and must do whatever it takes to make sure the company can succeed. If {0.SimFirstName} fails, their company can be in jeopardy.</Text>
  <Text Key="77306317">Practice Giving Orders ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="009A65F8">Lieutenant Colonel</Text>
  <Text Key="63083B63">Lieutenant Colonels are tasked with commanding battalions to ensure a safe and successful mission. The coordination and tactical mastery of each mission will fall to {0.SimFirstName}. If they fail the mission fails.</Text>
  <Text Key="0C8C7070">Share War Stories ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="54A3D0AD">Brigadier</Text>
  <Text Key="651A52E6">Brigadier is responsible for tasking missions out to the various platoons. {0.SimFirstName} is no longer tasked with field duty, but the role of Brigadier is to ensure the missions that platoons take on are safe and well planned out.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5FA0DF1">Recruit Sims ({0.String})</Text>
  <Text Key="6A400EA2">Grand Marshal</Text>
  <Text Key="27025D85">Grand Marshal is the highest position in the Military. {0.SimFirstName} has proven excellent field tactics and the ability to lead and order effectively. {0.SimFirstName} can wear their medals proudly knowing they are the highest ranking official in the entire Military.</Text>
  <Text Key="6BC9F2C4">Curio Shop Owner</Text>
  <Text Key="E21141D4">Curio Shop Owner</Text>
  <Text Key="0C7F732B">[REDACTED]</Text>
  <Text Key="14B4E8A4">StrangerVille Scientist</Text>
  <Text Key="D06B1017">Officer</Text>
  <Text Key="F28372F5">Officer</Text>
  <Text Key="FD75497C">The Covert Ops Branch is the part of the Military that no one talks about. You will be required to undergo secret tasks, by planting bugs and listening in on the unsuspecting. You will need to interrogate any and all suspicious individuals. No one can be trusted, and everyone is up to something. Are you up for the task?</Text>
  <Text Key="005563D3">Covert Operator</Text>
  <Text Key="D5184509">Covert Operator</Text>
  <Text Key="37ADDF34">Physical fitness and discipline will be the keys to success in the Military career. Rising through the ranks will not come easy unless you can demonstrate your physical prowess as well as your ability to recruit and be a leader. Will you pursue the path of a Grand Marshal, or will you follow a more secretive path to uncover what others might be hiding?</Text>
  <Text Key="AA1F109B">Military</Text>
  <Text Key="F3ABFB51">Military</Text>
  <Text Key="6481F863">In the Officer Branch you will continue to earn medals while you rise through the formal ranks of the Military. The Officer path will see you earning the highest rank possible and becoming a Grand Marshal. To build your leadership skills you will be tasked to order others and build to peak physical fitness. No Grand Marshal can be outdone by a Raw Recruit! </Text>
  <Text Key="5AFADFCB">Sleek and elegant the copious rounder is the perfect column to accent any classic home.</Text>
  <Text Key="9433564A">Copius Rounder</Text>
  <Text Key="A0E3C5DB">Hand crafted from the finest of used wood the Leafed Capping will add the perfect finishing touches on any ceiling.</Text>
  <Text Key="40B0A2BA">Leafed Capping</Text>
  <Text Key="8391CB8D">Strong and supportive this column will never fail. However if it feels betray you better not let your guard down.</Text>
  <Text Key="3FBEB9D8">Ridged Cornering</Text>
  <Text Key="40C9B8B9">Interior or exterior the Porch Break column will keep things standing strong.</Text>
  <Text Key="F75A6BBC">Porch Break</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC635">Those so-called &lt;b&gt;“scientists”&lt;/b&gt; have figured out a way to &lt;b&gt;filter the air&lt;/b&gt;, but they’re not sharing it! They want us to be sick!!</Text>
  <Text Key="2142055F">This is madness! They’re &lt;b&gt;testing experimental vaccines&lt;/b&gt; on anyone who is &lt;b&gt;possessed&lt;/b&gt;! I’m starting to wonder if this whole thing was planned from the start so they have an excuse to do this to us!</Text>
  <Text Key="2142055E">The Military are talking about “Operation Big Mama” and stopping “Subject B377-A”. If I could get some of that &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;, I’d be inclined to help them.</Text>
  <Text Key="2142055D">I knew it! I always knew there was something big going on in that lab!</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC636">Those &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; say they have a way to make a &lt;b&gt;breathing filter&lt;/b&gt; but, like, they’re only going to give it to their lackeys. What about us NORMAL people?!</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC637">That &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; is fighting the good fight. Always scrounging up secret government &lt;b&gt;equipment&lt;/b&gt; and exposing them for who they REALLY are!</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC630">You wanna know the truth?? Visit the &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; near the trailer park. They’ve got stuff that would BLOW YOUR MIND!</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC631">Whoa, cool &lt;b&gt;hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt;! You gotta use that to &lt;b&gt;get to the bottom&lt;/b&gt; of this whole conspiracy. I wish I could go with you!</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC632">I heard the Scientists were working on some kind of vaccine against this infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC633">The government doesn’t know what they’re doing! Someone needs to take the initiative and to &lt;b&gt;test a vaccine&lt;/b&gt;. I bet the &lt;b&gt;equipment at the lab&lt;/b&gt; could do something like that.</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC63C">I overheard the Scientists talking about needing to go to the lab to &lt;b&gt;craft a vaccine&lt;/b&gt; to stop the infection spreading from something they called “Subject B377-A”. I wonder what that means?</Text>
  <Text Key="F70EC63D">The Scientists and Military are &lt;b&gt;testing experimental vaccines&lt;/b&gt; on any &lt;b&gt;possessed&lt;/b&gt; people they find. I wouldn’t want to be possessed, but I’m not sure if I’d want to be a guinea pig for untested stuff like that!</Text>
  <Text Key="F8DB9F73">I have a &lt;b&gt;Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt; that can help protect you against all these &lt;b&gt;spores&lt;/b&gt;, but it’s missing a &lt;b&gt;breathing filter&lt;/b&gt;. I bet a &lt;b&gt;scientist&lt;/b&gt; could make you one.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8DB9F70">Nice &lt;b&gt;breathing filter&lt;/b&gt; you got there. I’ve actually got the &lt;b&gt;perfect thing&lt;/b&gt; to go with that in my &lt;b&gt;secret inventory&lt;/b&gt;... It’s a little pricey but I think you might be interested...</Text>
  <Text Key="F8DB9F71">I think you have everything you need to make a pretty stylish &lt;b&gt;hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt;, but you’re always welcome to spend more money here, if you want.</Text>
  <Text Key="513ECD9F">If my plane could still fly, I’d get the heck out of here ASAP!</Text>
  <Text Key="513ECD9E">I knew I was going to regret crashing in this town. Seems like our only hope is for someone to &lt;b&gt;find a vaccine&lt;/b&gt; that’ll stop this infection from spreading.</Text>
  <Text Key="513ECD99">If I can get some of that &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; they made, I’d be willing to head down into the lab and get revenge on that Mother Plant for causing the storm that crashed my plane!</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A0C">Sorry citizen, I leave the math-y mumbo jumbo to the &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt;. Maybe they can make sense of that &lt;b&gt;Spore Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A0F">Our orders are to turn over any &lt;b&gt;data&lt;/b&gt; to the &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; as soon as we get it. They’re working on some sort of &lt;b&gt;Breathing Filter&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A0E">We’ve been trying to shut down that &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; for weeks. It’s always selling restricted &lt;b&gt;equipment&lt;/b&gt;... that’s government property!</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A09">That &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; thinks it’s so sneaky with its &lt;b&gt;secret inventory&lt;/b&gt; but we know what they’re selling...</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A08">Citizen, I hope you’re not using that &lt;b&gt;hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt; to go anywhere “restricted”. I’d be required to report you to my CO.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A0B">Don’t worry, citizen, the Scientists are working on an Experimental Vaccine. They need &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzers&lt;/b&gt; at the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A0A">We need to &lt;b&gt;test the vaccine on possessed people&lt;/b&gt; as quickly as possible. If we can’t find something that works soon, things are really going to get out of hand.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A05">Now that we’ve figured out an &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;, we need to use it to stop the infection from spreading and &lt;b&gt;recruit the vaccinated&lt;/b&gt; to fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="9ACA2A04">We need to get this &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; to people. Once vaccinated, we can &lt;b&gt;recruit them&lt;/b&gt; to help take down that menace in the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A5B">The Scientists want &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. We can use our &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to find them. I’ve received intel that there is a large concentration &lt;b&gt;around the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A58">Soldier, the Scientists need &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;. Our orders are to use an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to find them. Check &lt;b&gt;around the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A59">Soldier! Get that &lt;b&gt;profile data&lt;/b&gt; to a &lt;b&gt;Scientist&lt;/b&gt; pronto! They need it to make a &lt;b&gt;Breathing Filter&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A5E">Way to go, soldier. I’m sure a &lt;b&gt;Scientist&lt;/b&gt; would love to see that &lt;b&gt;Spore Profile Data&lt;/b&gt; you got. They love that nerdy math stuff.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A5F">Soldier! Check out that &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; ASAP and see what kind of stolen &lt;b&gt;equipment&lt;/b&gt; they’re trying to sell now.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A5C">Well DONE, soldier! With that &lt;b&gt;hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt; you should be able to get even &lt;b&gt;deeper into the lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A5D">It’s go time, Soldier! The Scientists are working on an Experimental Vaccine. They need &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzers&lt;/b&gt; at the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A52">Soldier, keep an eye out for the &lt;b&gt;possessed&lt;/b&gt;. We need to &lt;b&gt;test the vaccine on them&lt;/b&gt; so we can put a stop to this madness!</Text>
  <Text Key="633C2A53">Operation Big Mama is under way, Soldier. We need to protect people with the &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; and then &lt;b&gt;recruit them&lt;/b&gt; to stop the Mother Plant at the bottom of the lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="E437444F">Oh good, you managed to get an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. There’s probably a high concentration of &lt;b&gt;spores around the lab&lt;/b&gt;. Come back to me after you’ve &lt;b&gt;collected and analyzed&lt;/b&gt; them!</Text>
  <Text Key="9200886D">By my calculations, if someone can &lt;b&gt;vaccinate and recruit&lt;/b&gt; three allies, they’d have enough to surround the Mother Plant from all sides and defeat her.</Text>
  <Text Key="E437444C">Once you’ve found enough &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and analyzed them &lt;b&gt;at the lab&lt;/b&gt;, I can make a &lt;b&gt;Breathing Filter&lt;/b&gt; for you. Surely there is a higher concentration near the &lt;b&gt;source of the infection&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="E437444D">If you can provide me with the &lt;b&gt;Spore Profile Data&lt;/b&gt; I can &lt;b&gt;craft a breathing filter&lt;/b&gt; to protect your lungs from this infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="E437444A">Unfortunately, that &lt;b&gt;breathing filter&lt;/b&gt; won’t do any good without the &lt;b&gt;rest of the suit&lt;/b&gt;. Luckily, I’ve heard that the &lt;b&gt;curio shop&lt;/b&gt; has one of our older models in their &lt;b&gt;secret inventory&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="E437444B">Excellent! Looks like you’ve got all the pieces you need to &lt;b&gt;craft a hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt;. It should provide enough protection to allow you to go &lt;b&gt;deeper into the lab&lt;b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4374448">If we can get some &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and a &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt; to the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt; at the lab, we can start working on a vaccine against the infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4374449">The &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzers&lt;/b&gt; at the lab could create a vaccine against the Mother Plant’s infection. We just need to gather some &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt; for testing purposes.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4374446">We need to find &lt;b&gt;possessed subjects&lt;/b&gt; so we can &lt;b&gt;test the experimental vaccine&lt;/b&gt; on them.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4374447">I hope the we can &lt;b&gt;test the vaccine&lt;/b&gt; quickly so we can help all those &lt;b&gt;possessed people&lt;/b&gt; around town.</Text>
  <Text Key="6896E83F">Denim Dreams</Text>
  <Text Key="D5EFA91E">Crocheted Explorer</Text>
  <Text Key="763D928D">Flowy Bouquet</Text>
  <Text Key="FD852F8A">Stud-ing Accents</Text>
  <Text Key="E592A1FA">Cool in the Desert</Text>
  <Text Key="7D0CC350">Dust Walker</Text>
  <Text Key="914ACBA4">Heart of the Pack</Text>
  <Text Key="B8B2C8BC">Is it real? Is it there?</Text>
  <Text Key="351F1E13">Illusion Of Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="7267A6B9">Cold and ridged, this fence will wined through out your home like rolling peaks of metal and iron. Gaze upon its beauty and never take it for granted.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C54D5BC">Twisting Peaks</Text>
  <Text Key="0C468952">In need of a tried and true barrier between you and your pesky neighbors? Fear not the Classic Picket has you covered.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B2E2F6D">Classic Picket</Text>
  <Text Key="DEBC617A">Worried about unwanteds finding their way into your yard? Keep everything out with this Almost Gapless yard fence.</Text>
  <Text Key="06687925">Almost Gapless</Text>
  <Text Key="9C2BB198">Decoder Tile</Text>
  <Text Key="70DCF10C">Dirtiest Pattern</Text>
  <Text Key="AD44854C">ArchGP07_Apartment_37x18_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="23C3B303">ArchGP07_Apartment_37x18_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="CB55790B">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="3066858A">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="7A096282">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_01_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="EB9FAF7D">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_01_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="FF57A0B4">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_02_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="76E59D1B">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_02_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="9FD242A1">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_02_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="81A43B54">ArchGP07_comStrip6x8_02_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="827A3F95">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="39C985B0">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_01_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="CA2BBA68">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_01_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="FD95F187">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_01_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="F1826D12">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_02_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="8DE40C2D">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_02_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="4EDBD49B">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_02_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="D030167A">ArchGP07_comStrip9x9_02_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="FF91B21A">ArchGP07_gasStation_35x20_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="80016745">ArchGP07_gasStation_35x20_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="789307E3">ArchGP07_gasStation_35x20_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="476143B2">ArchGP07_gasStation_35x20_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="FE247584">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_bar</Text>
  <Text Key="97F4054B">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_bar</Text>
  <Text Key="EE9EA520">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_bowlingAlley</Text>
  <Text Key="7A23926F">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_bowlingAlley</Text>
  <Text Key="2233F106">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_burgerJoint</Text>
  <Text Key="9214D499">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_burgerJoint</Text>
  <Text Key="924912BC">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_carWash</Text>
  <Text Key="849BDC13">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_carWash</Text>
  <Text Key="FF0C2CC1">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_diner</Text>
  <Text Key="513A04F4">ArchGP07_GoogieStrip_diner</Text>
  <Text Key="5E54ACDA">ArchGP07_Shack_01</Text>
  <Text Key="F3D9B605">ArchGP07_Shack_01</Text>
  <Text Key="F254EBF0">ArchGP07_Shotgun_Box_03</Text>
  <Text Key="0358219F">ArchGP07_Shotgun_Box_03</Text>
  <Text Key="6E10D5AD">ArchGP07_Shotgun1rm_7x14</Text>
  <Text Key="4AB8BC78">ArchGP07_Shotgun1rm_7x14</Text>
  <Text Key="8BF6B12D">ArchGP07_Shotgun1rm_7x14_03</Text>
  <Text Key="216476F8">ArchGP07_Shotgun1rm_7x14_03</Text>
  <Text Key="7CAAE995">Generic, but with a purpose.</Text>
  <Text Key="514763B0">Generic Ceiling Light</Text>
  <Text Key="C45C6468">For your enjoyment.</Text>
  <Text Key="1513CF87">Another Ceiling Area Light</Text>
  <Text Key="10CBC5C3">Ceiling light with a purpose.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0317C12">Area Ceiling Light</Text>
  <Text Key="98B871EB">Where Larry keeps his most prized mementos on display! That's right, the ones he won't sell he would tack on to this bar for safe keeping. Check weekly for new ones added!</Text>
  <Text Key="32126FEA">Larry's Knick Knack Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="831DB538">Perfect for all types of indoor use. Even though it has a sturdy and rigid structure, it provides the best comfort in a lightweight frame. Perfect for those who just want to be able to relax without much fuss.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF5BDF37">The Bunk</Text>
  <Text Key="11724295">101 tips on avoiding unwanted snoops and spies. Written By: [REDACTED]</Text>
  <Text Key="E01C1EB0">Avoiding the Watchful Eye</Text>
  <Text Key="BB2C5EA2">The answers to all of life's greatest mysteries. The true reason you are stuck in this canyon.</Text>
  <Text Key="CEBD491D">Why are We Here?</Text>
  <Text Key="8FEFC14D">A book containing plans for all of Crystal Vu's top secret diabolical inventions. Most of these are probably out of date by now, but still worth a read.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC676098">Crystal Vu's Top Secret Inventions</Text>
  <Text Key="3CBA6994">A compilation of all untold mysteries of StrangerVille. There are sure to be some we missed...</Text>
  <Text Key="327F8D7B">Untold Mysteries of StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="DE44E7CF">7000 Tips and tricks to truly believe you are an effective fortune teller.</Text>
  <Text Key="69545F96">Fortune Telling for Goofballs</Text>
  <Text Key="A1D579C4">Dignified bookcase, sturdy even in adversity. Holds your books, while holding your style together. Feel free to store any kind of literature, it won't judge you.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2B01C8B">Regal Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="2E8C9B62">The perfect machine for all your particle and chemical analysis needs. Well, maybe more than analysis...\n\nOk...Fine, it has a lot of buttons and makes some noise, but we are not entirely sure what it actually does, but looks cool right?</Text>
  <Text Key="6F4F1BDD">Ch3M1C4l 4n4l1z3r 9000</Text>
  <Text Key="C9B925F6">Made with authentic rustic materials. The worn look is also authentic.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9B00F29">Old Timey Chimney</Text>
  <Text Key="BF2F0723">
Traces of Infection has been detected in this refrigerator. We have confiscated it for further investigation. Please refrain from going near the Secret Lab and have a nice day.\n\nYour Friendly Neighborhood Secret Agents</Text>
  <Text Key="7F24C6F2">Strange Note From StrangerVille Secret Agents</Text>
  <Text Key="7F3B06FF">The Medal Display Case will allow your Sim to neatly display all their Military Medals as they rise through the ranks. Don't forget to admire all of your hard-work and dedication.</Text>
  <Text Key="248E0E26">Medal Display Case</Text>
  <Text Key="CA6DBB32">Unlock by reaching level 2 of the Military career.</Text>
  <Text Key="B609F1A9">Unlocked at level 2 of the Military career.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD096FC0">Awarded for excellent technical knowledge and performance in the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="D746888F">Tech Team Excellence Award</Text>
  <Text Key="79EBF118">The highest accolade one can receive in the Military. Awarded for demonstrating overall field knowledge, the ability to recruit individuals, and be a top notch leader.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB64F697">Medal of Courage</Text>
  <Text Key="50E8D46B">Awarded for acts of selflessness and courage in the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="8CB90F6A">Bravery Heart</Text>
  <Text Key="AAF9A5C0">Awarded for realizing that life is not always under your control and there is something larger at work.</Text>
  <Text Key="42954A8F">Medal of Questioning</Text>
  <Text Key="462DA0C1">Awarded for showing excellent engineering and construction skills in the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="463C20F4">Construction Engineering Award</Text>
  <Text Key="85159536">Awarded for demonstrating exceptional sight, and ability to spot minor details in the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0F6A769">Eagle Eye Award</Text>
  <Text Key="FDA2C60F">Awarded for demonstrating the ability to pilot a rocket with exceptional skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CAB83D6">Air Award</Text>
  <Text Key="47DF1ED4">Awarded for demonstrating bravery against chaos on the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="68E84DBB">Medal of Supreme Bravery</Text>
  <Text Key="86498065">Awarded for demonstrating commitment and perseverance to make it this far in the Military.</Text>
  <Text Key="686FE0E0">Medal of Discipline</Text>
  <Text Key="2CA34B1A">Awarded for displaying top notch tactical expertise out on the field.</Text>
  <Text Key="8520E245">Tactical Genius Medal</Text>
  <Text Key="3EFD45BB">Spore Clusters can be used on the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt; at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to construct useful items. You can find Spore Clusters by using the &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt; to scan areas with a high concentration of spores.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB2D3E1A">Spore Cluster</Text>
  <Text Key="6CCFB293">With all your favorite functionality from the Basic Portable Computer, but now in more fresh and fun colors. Yes you need to pay more for cool colors...</Text>
  <Text Key="F363B442">Customized Portable Computer</Text>
  <Text Key="16711D5D">Tired of sitting at home on a beautiful day, but you still need to get that report done for work! Fret not, the Portable Computer has you covered. This high tech piece of equipment is the perfect companion for any hard working individual. From your favorite bar to your aunt Sally's for Harvest Fest, the portable computer can be taken anywhere. It even comes with a battery. They usually charge extra for that.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCA26248">Standard Portable Computer</Text>
  <Text Key="0EFCD958">This portable computer looks like it has been completely abandoned. Who knows what secrets it could be hiding...</Text>
  <Text Key="4C24E5D7">Abandoned Portable Computer</Text>
  <Text Key="F3BF5572">Grunge is IN!\n\nThe designers at Nacar Marmalade wanted to focus on the raw look. They believe that the new Lot appearance is a thing of the past. With this decal, you can add that grungy, worn out effect to any wall to make it look edgy, vintage, and lived in without incurring in rent increase.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCF1BA0D">Grunged Splatcal #1</Text>
  <Text Key="B1056DFB">With the success of Grunged Splatcal #1, Nacar Marmalade decided to add a second version into their catalog. You can use them together for intensified grunge.</Text>
  <Text Key="2BD8395A">Grunged Splatcal #2</Text>
  <Text Key="8B7E6647">Modern and professional. Perfect for those who like for their workstations to be always tidy, or at least look that way from all angles. Comes with conveniently placed drawers for all that sensitive data you are hiding...yes, we know where they are...;)</Text>
  <Text Key="EA3EC9FE">The Tekxhnik</Text>
  <Text Key="994DEB62">When is a door not a door? When it’s a portal. A portal to another dimension. A dimension not just of things seen and heard but of things only in the mind. You’ve entered through the Zone Door and your next stop? StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="FA320BDD">The Notjustador Collection – The Zone Door</Text>
  <Text Key="91473FE1">When is a door not a door? When it’s a gateway - a gateway to supernatural realms whose doors may, in fact, swing both ways if one has mastered the keys. Things that go bump in the night will pass freely between our mortal plane and theirs….and you thought I was just gonna say, “ when it’s ajar.”</Text>
  <Text Key="416C6194">The Notjustador Collection – The Tully</Text>
  <Text Key="D9C0DEE8">Don't let the appearance fool you, come on in! This door might look like it has seen better days, but its construction is top of the line to widthstand any disaster scenario. Properly insulated! Hardware and installation not included.</Text>
  <Text Key="B06B3707">Inviting Swing Out Door</Text>
  <Text Key="70E3A197">Why did the chicken cross the threshold of the Aether Door in StangerVille? To get to “the other side”. Personally, I’m too chicken to open this door. What about you?</Text>
  <Text Key="C686106E">The Notjustador Collection – The Aether Door</Text>
  <Text Key="BAD2031D">What awaits beyond the stately antiquated threshold of the Bosch Door? Total enlightenment? Or Purgatory, perhaps? Do I really need to paint you a detailed picture?</Text>
  <Text Key="136FEC08">The Notjustador Collection – The Bosch Door</Text>
  <Text Key="2B42E559">When is a door not a door? When it’s got so much glass in it that it might as well be a window. Well, here it is….It’s a door, it’s a window – it’s a Windoor.</Text>
  <Text Key="8376F2DC">The Notjustador Collection – The Windoor</Text>
  <Text Key="F9AD9344">Looking to get more door for less Simoleons? Well, we’ve got just the door for you! The MoreDoor - I mean, just look at the size of this ominous entranceway It’s as big as a mountain! Don’t ring, just go on in…what’s the worst that could happen?</Text>
  <Text Key="C782310B">The Notjustador Collection – The MoreDoor</Text>
  <Text Key="A33DB9D1">Local lore has it that this old eliptical arch used to be a door. Until, one day, those doors just turned up gone. Folks ‘round here think it mighta been them door snatchin’ space travelers what took ‘em. I just say, “that’s business as usual here in StrangerVille”.</Text>
  <Text Key="08C5FB24">The Sansadoor Arch</Text>
  <Text Key="65D93BA7">The Experimental Vaccine needs to be tested &lt;b&gt;3 times&lt;/b&gt; before you are able to construct the Infection Vaccine on the Chemical Analyzer.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE29B8F4">Experimental Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="C87326D4">The Infection Vaccine can make Sims temporarily immune to the Infection. You will need to use the Vaccine on Sims in order to Recruit them to fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="10D5E5BB">Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="D671AAF8">Cost and attributes unknown.</Text>
  <Text Key="9082BFF7">Game Card</Text>
  <Text Key="88360F49">This Bizarre Fruit has an ominous glow to it. As if it contains some living spore... This thing should probably not be eaten.</Text>
  <Text Key="2110A1AC">Bizarre Fruit</Text>
  <Text Key="84E5BE03">Bizarre Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="8A7272BD">Bizarre Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="38835ED3">This Bizarre Plant has an odd glow about it, as if it is being controlled by some other entity. It looks as though there is something growing inside of it...</Text>
  <Text Key="F8630688">Bizarre Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="6E5D11DF">gardenPlantSprout_GP07GENinfected Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="EE6EB486">gardenPlantSprout_GP07GENinfected Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="483BBD7E">I don’t know about you, but when I can’t see through to the other side of a gate, I get very nosey. I start to question everything. What’s back there? Is this where half of all socks go? Is this where they store everyone’s two cents? If the gate is opened, will I be the person who let the dogs out? Why can’t I have my cake &amp; eat it too? Purchase the Gates of Quandry and become instantly omnipotent.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8B08701">The Gates of Quandary</Text>
  <Text Key="E282C467">Heck top quality wrought iron gates are drop forged in the sweltering furnaces of Heck by sweaty folks that know a thing or two about forgery. So, when anyone asks me where to get a great gate, I always tell them to go straight to Heck.</Text>
  <Text Key="B45DC69E">The Gates of Heck</Text>
  <Text Key="668E9C18">If I told you what awaits you on the other side of this otherwise innocuous looking gate, would you still go in? OK then, I’m not tellin’, but I will say this, I know for a fact that this object was built with a Para-Normal Map applied to it. Strange? Oh, I think so.</Text>
  <Text Key="C9E70797">The Gates of Conundrum</Text>
  <Text Key="2E88D8B6">This can be used to modify an &lt;/b&gt;Incomplete Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt;. Question the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop Owner&lt;/b&gt; about Spores. He might have an &lt;b&gt;Incomplete Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt; to sell.</Text>
  <Text Key="9A7E19E9">Spore Filter</Text>
  <Text Key="ECFE778E">The filtration system on this suit is not enough to filter through &lt;b&gt;Toxic Spores&lt;/b&gt;. Question &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; about Spores to see if they can improve it.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DA697B1">Incomplete Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="45E85836">This will allow passage through &lt;b&gt;Toxic Spores&lt;/b&gt; in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; as long as it is worn.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C5D8069">Modified Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="F7A003E9">&lt;b&gt;Number of Scans Before Recharge: 3&lt;/b&gt;\nThe Infection Scanner can be used to reveal &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; by clicking and scanning the ground. Try scanning areas with a high concentration of spores.</Text>
  <Text Key="203011CC">Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="36D57B2F">Collect 15 pieces of StrangerVille Evidence to compile a &lt;b&gt;Secret Dossier&lt;/b&gt;. Evidence can be found by questioning the locals or poking around the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A0D11F8">Aerial Surveillance Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="95310A72">Clandestine Dongle</Text>
  <Text Key="5D1DED41">Encrypted USB Device</Text>
  <Text Key="A976B680">Glitched Hologram Readout</Text>
  <Text Key="0A1D7154">Hastily Scrawled Note</Text>
  <Text Key="E7364F6C">Infrared Microfilm</Text>
  <Text Key="2AFF91E6">Pack of Bizarre Seeds</Text>
  <Text Key="4A890BF3">Partially Redacted Report</Text>
  <Text Key="6EB6FE18">Photo Of Sealed Door</Text>
  <Text Key="F1ECC9EB">Photo of Bizarre Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="4FB0B13B">Strange Blueprints</Text>
  <Text Key="763DD667">Suspiciously Blurry Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="85109D85">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_basement_hallway</Text>
  <Text Key="716B0968">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_longstairs</Text>
  <Text Key="2B9EA9AE">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_microscope_room</Text>
  <Text Key="BDD3A666">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_motherplant_room</Text>
  <Text Key="2BCDAD1A">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_officefloor</Text>
  <Text Key="EB302E7D">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_ominous_stairs</Text>
  <Text Key="9D0926FB">inviseractableModel_ENVgizmoNoFtpUseAudioVFX_sporefloor</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC13F87">Spore Hallway - Privacy Area</Text>
  <Text Key="E1F6B5D5">These top secret blueprints look like they are for some giant structure. It looks like they are trying to contain something massive!</Text>
  <Text Key="4A8687F0">Top Secret Blueprints and Plans</Text>
  <Text Key="3B8C672B">This Junk Pile totally does not contain any helpful information for the StrangerVille Investigation...</Text>
  <Text Key="4C6D052A">Inconspicuous Junk Pile?</Text>
  <Text Key="52026550">Some places of work like to be discreet and blend with their surroundings, not the ones using this door though!\n\nComplete with lighting and scrolling text enabled, this door wants to let you know where you are and what you are doing there.\n\nNote:You may use this in a secret lair, but it might stop being secret...</Text>
  <Text Key="CD679C7F">Not So Inconspicuous Door</Text>
  <Text Key="12FE7FC3">labDoor_GP07GENmotherPlant Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="00F88A12">Another Not So Inconspicuous Door</Text>
  <Text Key="F959CE47">Not for the discreet.\n\nComplete with lighting and scrolling text enabled, this door wants to let you know where you are and what you are doing there.\n\nNote:You may use this in a secret lair, but it might stop being secret...</Text>
  <Text Key="D6A481FE">Another Not So Inconspicuous Door</Text>
  <Text Key="A81FC45A">labDoor_GP07GENsporeHallway Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="69786485">labDoor_GP07GENsporeHallway Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="752D4AA8">This will grant access to all doors in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="7EF3D5C7">Secret Lab Keycard</Text>
  <Text Key="C471E609">Landmark_GP07_Pylon_01</Text>
  <Text Key="7E6EFB6C">Landmark_GP07_Pylon_01</Text>
  <Text Key="C2F9C32A">landmarkGP07_thunderhead_01 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="5751F7B5">landmarkGP07_thunderhead_01 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="3A4C89B3">landmarkGP07_thunderhead_02 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="A6FF1DE2">landmarkGP07_thunderhead_02 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="76239795">Is it a ship? Is it a dish? Is it a spacedish? Spaceship?\n\nFor the conspiracy theorist and fan of the unknown, this ceiling lamp adds playful flair to any Lot. It may not always look chic, even with chic being a personal thing, but it will definitely evoke questions...lots of questions.\n\nNote: No, it doesn't fly.</Text>
  <Text Key="AD560DB0">Unidentified Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="69FB92CB">A creation from Gr00vy Lights, Co. Part of a series they said. A modern take on the traditional lava lamp in a deceptively friendly glow. Its design screams space alien and minimalist modern design all at once. Give your room a hint of retro-cool with this floor illumination piece. People will swear it came from outer space.\n\nDid we say deceptively friendly glow? We mean...cool space alien glow!</Text>
  <Text Key="01E0FF4A">The Purple Lava Beacon</Text>
  <Text Key="5CECFA08">A creation from Gr00vy Lights, Co. Part of a series they said. Still giving your room a hint of retro-cool, still making people wonder where it came from.\n\nNOW IN GREEN! Super Green!</Text>
  <Text Key="28D376A7">The Green Lava Beacon</Text>
  <Text Key="B1BFDF73">A creation from Gr00vy Lights, Co. Part of a series they said - and they were not joking! Need more pink in your life? This Lava Beacon is the perfect solution for that!\n\nWhat? Who said that cool alien glow cannot be pink? Nonsense!</Text>
  <Text Key="3EE884A2">The Pink Lava Beacon</Text>
  <Text Key="B114213E">Gr00vy Lights, Co. wants you to explore the depths of the color yellow with this version of their unique series for the Lava Beacon. Yellow hues to relax and set the tone for groovy evening.</Text>
  <Text Key="F67BD0C1">The Yellow Lava Beacon</Text>
  <Text Key="88D5ABE9">The last installment (we think) of Gr00vy Lights, Co. Lava Beacon series.\n\nYou don't have to feel blue with this shade of blue. Enjoy the depths of space in this blue shade that will evoke your grooviest space fantasies, and maybe conspiracies.</Text>
  <Text Key="171089CC">The Blue Lava Beacon</Text>
  <Text Key="B5559179">DYI chic and functional, what this lamp puts in effort makes up with style.\n\nAlready assembled.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A6E797C">Industrialized DYI Lighting</Text>
  <Text Key="AB584F25">Almost too clinical for normal day to day use.\n\nWarning: If the light flickers...don't call us. Just Run!</Text>
  <Text Key="5A40F6A0">Laboratory Light Strip</Text>
  <Text Key="7639E9F9">Re-purposing at its finest! Authentic truck parts, polished for a fresh look for your walls. No junk here!</Text>
  <Text Key="59E31AFC">Not A Scrap</Text>
  <Text Key="D9FB0868">lightWall2x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="F1A67B87">lightWall2x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="FDF84213">lightWall3x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="2B314AC2">lightWall3x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="97957DDE">lightWall4x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="B9533BE1">lightWall4x1_GP07LABtileable Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="379060F9">This Spy Bug can be planted on other Sims. Once planted, Purchase a listening device from the Catalog to listen in on the bugged Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="685ECFFC">51M5 Spy Bug</Text>
  <Text Key="FCB18A0F">The Listening Device will allow your Sim to plant bugs on other Sims and listen in on them. You never know what juicy gossip you will find out.</Text>
  <Text Key="64548FD6">Listening Device</Text>
  <Text Key="FF895F18">A Listening Device Recording can be given peacefully given to other Sims or used against them as blackmail!</Text>
  <Text Key="C545E097">Listening Device Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="F0E3CBE2">Recording of: &lt;b&gt;{0.SimName}&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThis can be combined with other StrangerVille Evidence to compile a secret dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="4674C55D">Top Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="6CFD158A">What’s the point of going on vacation if you don’t bring back a plethora of precious plastic memories that you can cherish for several weeks then discard like an orphaned orange sock? Well, if that’s what you’re hankerin’ for, visit The Knick Knack, Bric-A-Brac Shack whilst in StrangerVille. If they ain’t got it - it don’t exist…or does it? Inquire within. Ask for Larry.</Text>
  <Text Key="70B32995">The Knick Knack, Bric-A-Brac Shack</Text>
  <Text Key="A852C9B8">The Mother Plant in all its glory!</Text>
  <Text Key="19BC8C69">The Mother</Text>
  <Text Key="97BC8C61">The Mother Plant Pit. To use this make sure the Mother Plant is placed directly in the center of this object. Enjoy your own personal Mother Plant Pet, but BE CAREFUL SHE BITES!</Text>
  <Text Key="1F199F14">The Mother Plant Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="9C9E1D2C">The Mother Plant Pit. To use this make sure the Mother Plant is placed directly in the center of this object. Enjoy your own personal Mother Plant Pet, but BE CAREFUL SHE BITES!</Text>
  <Text Key="FC4DF863">The Mother Plant Pit</Text>
  <Text Key="CD8A1A47">A collection of posters that are usually on display at the StrangerVille National Base. From scientific theorems to military promotional posters this collection has everything you need to make you feel right at home on the base.</Text>
  <Text Key="BB6BA5FE">StrangerVille National Base Posters</Text>
  <Text Key="84A795A1">Where will it take you? Where will you go?</Text>
  <Text Key="116DC454">Lone Road</Text>
  <Text Key="E42CF3B4">Well, it seems like it is definitely out there...</Text>
  <Text Key="06AF261B">Where Did It Go?</Text>
  <Text Key="A7D5D06F">Question everything!</Text>
  <Text Key="C9A8B5B6">Simmanatti</Text>
  <Text Key="670B4C42">Rawr!</Text>
  <Text Key="58CA873D">Emily!</Text>
  <Text Key="25D4546D">Still not able to be explained in plain terms. Moo!</Text>
  <Text Key="27DEBD38">Cowplant Dissected</Text>
  <Text Key="0B026617">A painting can tell a story, or we can use a painting to tell a story. Whatever your motivation, allow these paintings to tell a story for the ages.</Text>
  <Text Key="C18635EE">Storytelling Paintings</Text>
  <Text Key="26E30197">A barrier so impenetrable you would want to replicate across all your Lot. It is also a beautiful industrial look for any fan of that style.\n\nMade with actual cement.</Text>
  <Text Key="17A6306E">Not Quite The Parapet</Text>
  <Text Key="22F3511F">plantGP07_Cacti_01</Text>
  <Text Key="DBEB83C6">plantGP07_Cacti_01</Text>
  <Text Key="AB75B8C6">plantGP07_Cacti_02</Text>
  <Text Key="7B53C959">plantGP07_Cacti_02</Text>
  <Text Key="E09449D1">plantGP07_Cacti_03</Text>
  <Text Key="80E4AB24">plantGP07_Cacti_03</Text>
  <Text Key="2512BD90">plantGP07_Cacti_04</Text>
  <Text Key="460C3BBF">plantGP07_Cacti_04</Text>
  <Text Key="16DDEBBB">plantGP07_Cacti_05</Text>
  <Text Key="1382501A">plantGP07_Cacti_05</Text>
  <Text Key="C5CC3132">plantGP07_Cacti_06</Text>
  <Text Key="2033BECD">plantGP07_Cacti_06</Text>
  <Text Key="EF24F45D">plantGP07_Cacti_07</Text>
  <Text Key="45F83748">plantGP07_Cacti_07</Text>
  <Text Key="4F591CEF">plantGP07_Cacti_Lg_01</Text>
  <Text Key="011FF336">plantGP07_Cacti_Lg_01</Text>
  <Text Key="46AFDE16">plantGP07_Cacti_Lg_02</Text>
  <Text Key="F74D28C9">plantGP07_Cacti_Lg_02</Text>
  <Text Key="E3E3408F">plantGP07_DesertBloomBush_01</Text>
  <Text Key="5BD6EB56">plantGP07_DesertBloomBush_01</Text>
  <Text Key="1ADD2E92">plantGP07_DesertBush_Alive</Text>
  <Text Key="BEED98AD">plantGP07_DesertBush_Alive</Text>
  <Text Key="3464462D">plantGP07_DesertBush_Dead</Text>
  <Text Key="489F25F8">plantGP07_DesertBush_Dead</Text>
  <Text Key="6E559496">plantGP07_GrassClump</Text>
  <Text Key="1DEB8449">plantGP07_GrassClump</Text>
  <Text Key="C2EDE022">plantGP07_infectedBushBloom Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="1CBF159D">plantGP07_infectedBushBloom Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="9AD39468">plantGP07_infectedBushDormant Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="BF725F87">plantGP07_infectedBushDormant Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="D7646552">This strange sprout looks a bit strange. It looks like something is living inside it...</Text>
  <Text Key="B329036D">Strange Sprout</Text>
  <Text Key="CAE17431">Give this to any StrangerVille &lt;b&gt;Scientist&lt;/b&gt; to construct an effective &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;. You can find them hanging out at the Local Library.</Text>
  <Text Key="0C1D7904">Infection Profile Data</Text>
  <Text Key="C8306B18">These Strange Floor Vines do not look very safe. WHY ARE THEY MOVING!</Text>
  <Text Key="0C354497">Strange Floor Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="0710B127">Looking for a planting DIY project, but without actually making it yourself?\n\nAre you a plant lover? Are you a lover of vintage and classy decor? Say no more!\n\nThe Clawfoot Fanciful Planter is the perfect balance of 'Do It Yourself' and classy chic that is the rage these days, turning any space into a beautiful and peaceful space, and without breaking the bank! Plants are included for maximum efficiency.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B74655E">Clawfoot Fanciful Planter</Text>
  <Text Key="E5218DEC">This Plant Containment Cell can contain the peskiest of flora. It is also nice to display other things as well, I guess...</Text>
  <Text Key="17FFA823">Plant Containment Cell</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE95658">Bzzzz...\n\nBzzzzzzzzzzzzz...\n\nBZZZZZZZZZZ\n\nBZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ...POP!</Text>
  <Text Key="6C57CCD7">Not A Statellite Dish</Text>
  <Text Key="B97F6995">Add a personal touch with this custom crafted finial spire.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E9CE3B0">Semi-Custom Style Spire</Text>
  <Text Key="94D26D44">Customized, stylish tileable finials for any home. Blendable with modern and vintage styles.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6459F0B">Custom Style Tileables</Text>
  <Text Key="48F1B405">GENIUS from Nacar Marmalade!\n\nFor even smaller spaces and with no corners that will randomly curl up, how can it? It IS the corner of the rug! Who says you can't indulge?</Text>
  <Text Key="4F516500">Grunged Splatrug - 1/4</Text>
  <Text Key="04AAB556">We’ve collected the top ten conspiracy theories from around the world, reprinted them in all their redacted glory, and constructed a paper mache rug for you to spend countless hours pacing over how it’s all connected.</Text>
  <Text Key="93A69A09">The Redacted Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="E21B2E93">Nacar Marmalade believes that it is OK to not have a giant space for art and that art can be anywhere and it comes in every size. This half of a rug is for those that don't have enough space to place the Large version of this series, or want a rug on their terms.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9356842">Grunged Splatrug - Half</Text>
  <Text Key="58AE240B">Accented with details that mark a successful and honorable career in the Military.</Text>
  <Text Key="A72A968A">Ranking Rug</Text>
  <Text Key="150372C8">Deliciously vintage looking patterns for the lover of trends of old, and maybe not so old anymore. Bring some joy to your life with something that looks and feels expensive, but only you know it isn't.</Text>
  <Text Key="4766A467">Patterned Rugs</Text>
  <Text Key="134B3F3C">From Nacar Marmalade! Who believe that a worn and raw effect can create the perfect Lot.\n\nKeep your guests guessing, is it mold? Is is it dirt? Oh...it's a rug?</Text>
  <Text Key="F899B993">Grunged Splatrug - Large</Text>
  <Text Key="43773C62">It was the Summer of that year. We spent our days in the desert sun, combing the sands seeking to uncover The Truth. A novel Shelly had lost the previous year. We found The Truth, and she disappeared on a Tuesday. It was noon. I was relieving myself in a bush. I returned to our favorite sand dune, she was gone. The desert sand was scuffled, was it the wind or a struggle? I don’t know, but I have my photo. My photo of Shelly.</Text>
  <Text Key="B51B2EDD">Bar Back with Shelly’s Photo</Text>
  <Text Key="F8797194">sculptFloor_GP07GENcargoTruck Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="BDFE257B">sculptFloor_GP07GENcargoTruck Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="2946F1B9">Made with 100% military grade materials. Comes with all accessories you need, only to be used as shown. Assembly not required.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDAAC6BC">Military Grade Flagpole</Text>
  <Text Key="BDAA1784">Unlock by reaching level 6 of the Military career while in the Officer branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD79FB07">Unlocked at level 6 of the Military career while in the Officer branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4D1F67A">Just a non harmful sculpture version of the Bizarre Plant in its Dormant State.</Text>
  <Text Key="461B2825">Infected Dormant Plant Sculpture</Text>
  <Text Key="A988A46A">Just a non harmful Sculpture version of the Strange Sprout</Text>
  <Text Key="861DB0F5">Strange Sprout Sculpture</Text>
  <Text Key="2C2BC7C1">sculptFloor_GP07GENstreamlineRV Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="59BFE5F4">sculptFloor_GP07GENstreamlineRV Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="8D0A5FDC">What were they thinking! The 5000 prototype was too much for the world! The 5 mi… well it incinerated the first 17 people that tried to get purify their rooms. I’d never seen purification move so fast. They hit a button, and then… well there was a sound, a spray, and they… let’s just say I’m glad I was 18th in line. Why did they keep stepping up for a try? I’m not sure I… why would they… I need some fresh air to get my bearings.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2A94BB3">Purifier 5 Million Prototype</Text>
  <Text Key="CADE7AB1">With 3 sides of blinking lights, no blinking light display blinks more than the Blink O’matic.</Text>
  <Text Key="4680C484">Blink O'matic</Text>
  <Text Key="DE74B7A5">What secrets are contained within this obelisk? What strange language are these hieroglyphs upon its surface? Bob from accounting says it’s a broken server stack. He found a whole bunch of them in the basement. I don’t agree. I think it’s alien tech! I hear it humming in my sleep. I think it wants me to serve it goulash. I’m not sure I know how to make goulash.</Text>
  <Text Key="4FC0C820">Pillar of Opulence</Text>
  <Text Key="2FD8A87D">A part of Old Penelope. This Engine must have dislodged in some kind of crash.</Text>
  <Text Key="CD9E94E8">Plane Engine</Text>
  <Text Key="3F0ABD5C">A part of Old Penelope. This Cockpit must have dislodged in some kind of crash.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA38EC33">Plane Cockpit</Text>
  <Text Key="36E865B5">Old Penelope is the tried and true cargo plane of George Cahill. She has put in many long years shuttling goods back and forth across the world. Unfortunately a freak storm while flying over StrangerVille has put her out of commission. Hopefully one day George will muster up enough energy to put the old horse back together.</Text>
  <Text Key="A466F250">Plane Tail</Text>
  <Text Key="0FEE3520">A part of Old Penelope. This Wing must have dislodged in some kind of crash.</Text>
  <Text Key="3ADD426F">Plane Wing</Text>
  <Text Key="9381156D">A part of Old Penelope. This Wing must have dislodged in some kind of crash.</Text>
  <Text Key="02173038">Plane Wing</Text>
  <Text Key="79112E86">For all your creature containment needs. Made from almost unbreakable materials, this barrel will help contain the meanest of creatures.\n\nWarning: Contents vary, and they may or may not...bite.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DE51519">Containment Barrel</Text>
  <Text Key="500CC3F6">Scratched, bruised, and cold this lonely table has been through a lot. It will never falter it will never waiver. It will stand the test of time. Just don't place anything on it.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A7C8929">Experimental Aluminum Slate</Text>
  <Text Key="598E37CF">Complete with accessories. Live and relive the illusion of scientific work with this piece. Just beware of what can awaken...</Text>
  <Text Key="AF4F4F96">Careful Tinkering Table</Text>
  <Text Key="BB0D48EE">Super safe, we promise! Don't pay attention to the label, feel free to explore their contents.\n\nWarning: Contents vary, and they may or may not...bite.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9C6691">Containment Barrel Stack</Text>
  <Text Key="A6EEE272">With the destruction of the Mother Plant you take the time to carve out a small trophy to display in your home. Now everyone will know that you put an end to the Mother Plant's control over StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="5260D10D">Mother Plant Tendril</Text>
  <Text Key="782A39E1">Taken from [REDACTED], this [REDACTED] is [REDACTED], filled with [REDACTED] and will help decipher [REDACTED] with [REDACTED].</Text>
  <Text Key="34D02F94">[REDACTED] Tendril</Text>
  <Text Key="CCF75C39">That nook that no one dares to look into but can't avoid. That window you see in all houses that seems to hold many secrets, and that no one seems to inhabit. What is it hiding? What is it showing?\n\nWait...Is that something moving up there?!</Text>
  <Text Key="1542FE3C">The Not So Dormant Dormer</Text>
  <Text Key="4F505D45">This box of unassuming papers is probably not your grandmothers' box of old photos. Something about the redacted text on the side seems a bit off...</Text>
  <Text Key="985C2540">Not your Grandmothers' Old Photos</Text>
  <Text Key="BBB56A6B">This small cluster of beakers and burners is sure to fill out any small lab. We will not question what strange experiments these are being used for.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D2EF16A">Beakers and Burners</Text>
  <Text Key="976170F7">The Crabby Bottom Armadillo is always there to cheer you up. If you ever need to put a smile on your face, stare into this armadillo's confused little eyes. He never disapproves of you, and is always there to make you laugh. Everyone loves the Crabby Bottom Armadillo.</Text>
  <Text Key="70B4AF4E">Crabby Bottom Armadillo Yellow</Text>
  <Text Key="83080F04">The Crabby Bottom Armadillo is always there to cheer you up. If you ever need to put a smile on your face, stare into this armadillos confused little eyes. He never disproves, and is always there to make you laugh. Everyone loves the Crabby Bottom Armadillo.</Text>
  <Text Key="071099CB">Crabby Bottom Armadillo Blue</Text>
  <Text Key="6F6C5AFF">The Crabby Bottom Armadillo is always there to cheer you up. If you ever need to put a smile on your face, stare into this armadillos confused little eyes. He never disproves, and is always there to make you laugh. Everyone loves the Crabby Bottom Armadillo.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDF9CA26">Crabby Bottom Armadillo Red</Text>
  <Text Key="7BD8D083">Stacks on stacks on stacks... and not the good kind. Just looking at this stack of unorganized papers is overwhelming!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6E7FCD2">Unorganized Documents</Text>
  <Text Key="D7D0ACBA">People should really not be leaving such important documents lying around on the floor like this. Anyone can rummage through these to find important things.</Text>
  <Text Key="1C227A65">Important Paper Clutter</Text>
  <Text Key="AC2F7AEE">This can be used to obtain a &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;. Check the &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop Owner's&lt;/b&gt; Secret Inventory, or ask &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Military Personnel&lt;/b&gt; around town.</Text>
  <Text Key="20A85C91">Secret Dossier</Text>
  <Text Key="FFAB21AA">The Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock is the perfect decoration to tie together your eclectic arts home. Do you like collecting souvenirs from the many places you have been? What better than this creepy looking souvenir.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC72CB35">Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock Alien</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE62FE3">The Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock is the perfect decoration to tie together your eclectic arts home. Do you like collecting souvenirs from the many places you have been. What better than this creepy looking souvenir.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0223BB2">Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock Alien</Text>
  <Text Key="9B2729F8">The Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock is the perfect decoration to tie together your eclectic arts home. Do you like collecting souvenirs from the many places you have been. What better than this creepy looking souvenir.</Text>
  <Text Key="2F5D0CF7">Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock Cyclops</Text>
  <Text Key="56ADE399">The Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock is the perfect decoration to tie together your eclectic arts home. Do you like collecting souvenirs from the many places you have been. What better than this creepy looking souvenir.</Text>
  <Text Key="DAAE681C">Wacky Wonderful Carnival Sock Triclops</Text>
  <Text Key="438FAB3D">This stack of totally unassuming and not confidential papers should probably not get left out on any old table. Who knows who might be interested in this information.</Text>
  <Text Key="643027A8">Unassuming and Not Confidential Papers</Text>
  <Text Key="2AA25949">…for display purposes only.</Text>
  <Text Key="A72F5FAC">Non-functional Air Conditioner</Text>
  <Text Key="1EE1AFE0">Relax as the soothing vistas scroll by. Escape to another reality, and forget the time and all your troubles... IM LATE!</Text>
  <Text Key="B661962F">Scrolling Decal Clock</Text>
  <Text Key="62D52D9B">You may not be a world leader, but that doesn’t mean you can’t decorate like one!</Text>
  <Text Key="F1FAD17A">Over-sized Uniform Accoutrements</Text>
  <Text Key="CC1C3D0C">These monitors display top secret information about what could be hiding in the StrangerVille Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="9233CEC3">Top Secret Monitor Display</Text>
  <Text Key="07888A03">Unlock by reaching level 8 of the Military career while in the Covert Operator branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="E5AD746C">Unlocked at level 8 of the Military career while in the Covert Operator branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="DB128437">They may work...or not.\n\nBut don't they look like they belong there?</Text>
  <Text Key="21DF528E">Vertical Spray Nozzles</Text>
  <Text Key="891A215C">sculptWall_GP07GENwall01 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="13C1D833">sculptWall_GP07GENwall01 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="DDF976E9">sculptWall_GP07GENwall02 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="FF0BFACC">sculptWall_GP07GENwall02 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="0637EC3E">sculptWall_GP07GENwall03 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="DE7741C1">sculptWall_GP07GENwall03 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="550C9008">For fortresses, secret laboratories, and villain hideouts. Some may worry about the size of it, but trust us, it is so giant it will go unnoticed.</Text>
  <Text Key="4AD258A7">Inconspicuous Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="55E3FC3B">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag01 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="49BE999A">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag01 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="04D241B2">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag02 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="5670084D">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag02 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="2E2B04DD">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag03 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="7C3480C8">sculptWall_GP07GENwallDiag03 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="CE32CC0C">A revolution was waiting! Purification at the speed of sound… BOOM! A fresh smelling room without the hassle of gurgle, gurgle, shhhpeew, gurgle, blurp, pshooooooooo… finally my fresh aerated room, 10 minutes later. But the world wasn’t ready. Purification at that speed was too much to handle. People didn’t know how to handle that much power. The sheer pure-osity of it all was too much for people to control.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE444BC3">Purifier 5000 Prototype</Text>
  <Text Key="12769BCE">These Strange Wall Vines do not look that safe...WHY ARE THEY MOVING!</Text>
  <Text Key="9005E9F1">Strange Wall Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="F3315B71">We aren’t sure what it does, but the manufacturer said it was impressive just to look at, and it is! Plop this metal behemoth down in your home and wonder at its protrusive-ness!</Text>
  <Text Key="093AB744">Over-sized Metal Wall Bracket, self-illuminating</Text>
  <Text Key="B6911A5A">See all your stored items like a pro! Everything visible and accessible. Nothing to hide here, nothing to hide.</Text>
  <Text Key="66408685">Heavy Metal - Heavy Duty Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="1E916672">Resourceful enthusiasts will challenge themselves to create DIY projects safely and affordable. This shower project is not an exception and we might say, the bar has been elevated. A couple of canisters, water hose, and an old "gently" used bathtub can become the bath of your dreams with a few adjustments. Assembly not required, use at your own risk.</Text>
  <Text Key="23F91D0D">Epic DIY Shower</Text>
  <Text Key="4F233D17">It kind of makes you wonder what were the signs displayed? The dreams they shared...The colorful text in their infinite possibilities. The current look evokes the deepest thoughts about life and the passing of time.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7930AEE">The 'No Sign' Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="6C8DB3F2">signOutdoorFloor_GP07GENroadside_4x1x8 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="41D98D8D">signOutdoorFloor_GP07GENroadside_4x1x8 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="85AD421D">signOutdoorFloor_GP07GENroadside_4x1x9 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="EC4F7908">signOutdoorFloor_GP07GENroadside_4x1x9 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="9077F754">Durable and rustic, this sign will let you place the signs of your choice and promises to withstand any scenario of disaster. Comes complete with lights so you can see your desired sign, even in pitch black!</Text>
  <Text Key="B0526F3B">Indestructable Industrial Sign</Text>
  <Text Key="393A1348">Perfect complement to The Tekxhnik. This chair will make you feel like you are the captain of a spaceship, or just look super cool in your office, lab, or for the home if you so choose. Assembly not needed.</Text>
  <Text Key="D22F9DE7">The Tekxhnik Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="3E1B630D">For all your futuristic, sci-ency staging needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="3650E858">Glass Top Stage Stairs</Text>
  <Text Key="B9A1B0A9">Welcome to the Soundtastic Fantastic Royale! Prepare for the journey of your life! Want to hear something old? Something new? Have you eyes light up with anticipation for when you think you will hear your favorite song. No shame in listening to that song that makes you sing out of the top of your lungs, or that song that makes you cry and hug everyone. The Soundtastic Fantastic Royale has them all and is there for you!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C01068C">The Soundtastic Fantastic Royale</Text>
  <Text Key="6731FFAD">The strange and inoffensive music it blares is laced with mystery and subliminal messaging. Maybe.</Text>
  <Text Key="73201A78">Strange Tunes Wall Speaker</Text>
  <Text Key="EAFD861B">StreetDecoGP07_AwningSlope3x1</Text>
  <Text Key="9BFB72FA">StreetDecoGP07_AwningSlope3x1</Text>
  <Text Key="E7650AD5">StreetDecoGP07_CellDoor2x1</Text>
  <Text Key="B36776F0">StreetDecoGP07_CellDoor2x1</Text>
  <Text Key="0CCEE03E">StreetDecoGP07_DirtMound</Text>
  <Text Key="C4E1DDC1">StreetDecoGP07_DirtMound</Text>
  <Text Key="8F5AB0BB">StreetDecoGP07_DirtPile</Text>
  <Text Key="EE638F1A">StreetDecoGP07_DirtPile</Text>
  <Text Key="3E990F32">StreetDecoGP07_DoorMat</Text>
  <Text Key="20A7F8CD">StreetDecoGP07_DoorMat</Text>
  <Text Key="25291184">StreetDecoGP07_FenceWood</Text>
  <Text Key="0D67194B">StreetDecoGP07_FenceWood</Text>
  <Text Key="1F019439">StreetDecoGP07_FireEscape</Text>
  <Text Key="1A5C263C">StreetDecoGP07_FireEscape</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D24DCE">StreetDecoGP07_Graffiti_01</Text>
  <Text Key="28865FF1">StreetDecoGP07_Graffiti_01</Text>
  <Text Key="E94EBFE7">StreetDecoGP07_Graffiti_02</Text>
  <Text Key="CEA1E11E">StreetDecoGP07_Graffiti_02</Text>
  <Text Key="CF4965F4">StreetDecoGP07_JunkCar_01</Text>
  <Text Key="9117EC5B">StreetDecoGP07_JunkCar_01</Text>
  <Text Key="852370E1">StreetDecoGP07_JunkCar_02</Text>
  <Text Key="6B382494">StreetDecoGP07_JunkCar_02</Text>
  <Text Key="E3C4F0AE">StreetDecoGP07_LightOutdoorWall</Text>
  <Text Key="6010D451">StreetDecoGP07_LightOutdoorWall</Text>
  <Text Key="032C9BF4">StreetDecoGP07_ParkingStop</Text>
  <Text Key="F5CFAE5B">StreetDecoGP07_ParkingStop</Text>
  <Text Key="C8D1583A">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="8C85A4E5">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="6CD97C03">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="274B2752">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="5C4C4498">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set3</Text>
  <Text Key="27069917">StreetDecoGP07_PipeWall_set3</Text>
  <Text Key="AF80DF80">StreetDecoGP07_PowerBox</Text>
  <Text Key="1285114F">StreetDecoGP07_PowerBox</Text>
  <Text Key="A8E56496">StreetDecoGP07_RV_01</Text>
  <Text Key="F9F1F449">StreetDecoGP07_RV_01</Text>
  <Text Key="B18EA36F">StreetDecoGP07_RV_02</Text>
  <Text Key="03C4BEB6">StreetDecoGP07_RV_02</Text>
  <Text Key="2DB68725">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Awning_01</Text>
  <Text Key="98161EA0">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Awning_01</Text>
  <Text Key="B2D6C3B8">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Awning_02</Text>
  <Text Key="F6A4C2B7">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Awning_02</Text>
  <Text Key="978CA2A7">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Lawn</Text>
  <Text Key="04BA81DE">StreetDecoGP07_RV_Lawn</Text>
  <Text Key="3D4C4D10">StreetDecoGP07_RV_PicketFence</Text>
  <Text Key="943CD23F">StreetDecoGP07_RV_PicketFence</Text>
  <Text Key="7C5003CE">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights</Text>
  <Text Key="1405A1F1">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights</Text>
  <Text Key="70D18DD3">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights_Cascade</Text>
  <Text Key="92FA4482">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights_Cascade</Text>
  <Text Key="19C675A3">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights_Post</Text>
  <Text Key="01FACA72">StreetDecoGP07_StringLights_Post</Text>
  <Text Key="3911F0E0">StreetDecoGP07_Tire</Text>
  <Text Key="FFCC892F">StreetDecoGP07_Tire</Text>
  <Text Key="370539A7">StreetDecoGP07_TownSign</Text>
  <Text Key="79C296DE">StreetDecoGP07_TownSign</Text>
  <Text Key="9297B5C3">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_Connector</Text>
  <Text Key="EEF24C12">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_Connector</Text>
  <Text Key="07596238">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_WindowIron_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="8BF55637">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_WindowIron_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="7E158BB1">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_WindowIron_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="7FA72784">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox_WindowIron_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="BDA9865C">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="D318F733">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set1</Text>
  <Text Key="1288DBE9">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="BE6319CC">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set2</Text>
  <Text Key="3AC7513E">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set3</Text>
  <Text Key="9DCE60C1">StreetDecoGP07_UtilityBox1x2x2_set3</Text>
  <Text Key="97D58E7E">StreetDecoGP07_WallAC</Text>
  <Text Key="F0032A01">StreetDecoGP07_WallAC</Text>
  <Text Key="ECFF14FB">StreetDecoGP07_WaterTank</Text>
  <Text Key="01767E5A">StreetDecoGP07_WaterTank</Text>
  <Text Key="75171A72">A simple pipette.</Text>
  <Text Key="3573F90D">Pipette</Text>
  <Text Key="4C40E876">Pst, Pssstt.</Text>
  <Text Key="62FECEA9">Spray</Text>
  <Text Key="D1B72A93">A simple swab, material unknown.</Text>
  <Text Key="A4109C42">Swab</Text>
  <Text Key="7B03FD06">The B64 Training Bot is the perfect companion for Sims to practice their sparring techniques. Be careful, this bot fights back!</Text>
  <Text Key="0F2F3899">B64 Training Bot</Text>
  <Text Key="FBFD966A">This training bot looks like it has been dressed up to replicate the behavior of something... But what could it be? Looks like whoever put this thing together really needs to work on their hot glue gun skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="7125E6F5">Modified B64 Training Bot</Text>
  <Text Key="F6280009">Unlock by reaching level 8 of the Military career while in the Officer branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="64C4BEAE">Unlocked at level 8 of the Military career while in the Officer Branch.</Text>
  <Text Key="64B25AE4">Made by up and coming design firm We Are Very Mysterious - Really, Inc. This beautiful and regal tall window will be a center of attention of inhabitants and passerbys alike.\n\nThe company's creative minds got inspired by vintage wooden textured windows with a hint of mistery and the phrase "The eyes are the windows of the soul" to create this piece that will make you want to look, but won't let you due to the fantastically crafted iron fence that adorns it.\n\nKeeping secrets in, fabulously.</Text>
  <Text Key="4C93CC2B">Window Of Mystere</Text>
  <Text Key="4E35B494">Looking for some "normal" windows? Not into the over the top flair and intricate designs? Look no further! The Discreet will offer a simple, and functional design that will adorn your home lot as intended. Not calling too much attention to your home lot, but giving a hint of intricacy with its grooves and small details that you can see if you are close...like reaaaaally close.</Text>
  <Text Key="48E97E7B">The Discreet</Text>
  <Text Key="C9148B79">From the secret minds of the Specter design firm, comes a carefully crafted piece that will make your home feel a little bit more Midnight Hollow and less Del Sol Valley. Give your home a classic look that is simple and elegant and create an air of mystery effortlessly.</Text>
  <Text Key="05A6477C">Arched Aperture</Text>
  <Text Key="731B6B07">The Specter design firm decided that if you are going to design a home lot, all aspects should be cohesive. Specter's vision not only focused on the visual real state for living rooms or bedrooms, but the group considered the attic as more than just a storage room, and that it deserved its own window to match.</Text>
  <Text Key="A242BCBE">Sky Parlor Delight</Text>
  <Text Key="5BD0D192">Following the success of "Window Of Mystere", the We Are Very Misterious -Really, Inc. design firm decided to go one pane further. Presenting Shuttered Mystere, with added shutters! For creating a look that only can be opened from within.</Text>
  <Text Key="452111AD">Shuttered Mystere</Text>
  <Text Key="733D6C5B">Following the steps of the original The Discreet, now it comes in a two pane version to delight your classic yet refined vintage taste, giving your lot a cozy, homey vibe.</Text>
  <Text Key="5C47CE3A">Twice Discreet</Text>
  <Text Key="3EF71543">Specter's vision for bigger wall spaces, the three pane offering of the Arched Aperture brings even more visual real state to make your home lot even more luxurious.</Text>
  <Text Key="A60B5292">Thrice Arched Aperture</Text>
  <Text Key="49A2CE47">The residents of StrangerVille say that this mysterious lab holds some deep dark secrets. Though there are many rumours, no one has ever set foot in the Secret Lab since the explosion. The Military seems to be keeping a close watch to ensure nothing goes in or out. Although security is tight around the lab, the locals say there is a small crack in the back of the fence that someone might be able to slip through undetected.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5FE982C">The &lt;font color='#000000'&gt;██████&lt;/font&gt; Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="3559B57D">Located on a spacious corner lot in the StrangerVille Plaza The Riverside Grove is a quaint home for a small family.</Text>
  <Text Key="27D18D5E">The Sigworth family is rather new in town. Jess, the mom, had to transfer to the StrangerVille National Base. After spending a few days on the base Dylan has started to notice something is a bit off about his wife. Although Dylan is doing all he can to reassure their daughter that everything is okay. Christie is starting to catch on and it is only a matter of time until she realizes what is going on.</Text>
  <Text Key="B3035261">Sigworth</Text>
  <Text Key="6E8C735A">Riverside Grove</Text>
  <Text Key="B9273EF2">Old Penelope is the tried and true cargo plane of George Cahill. She has put in many long years shuttling goods back and forth across the world. Unfortunately a freak storm while flying over StrangerVille has put her out of commission. Hopefully one day George will muster up enough energy to put the old horse back together.</Text>
  <Text Key="9CA2CEBB">George Cahill was a retired pilot who enjoyed taking his beloved plane Penelope for long flights across the world. After passing over StrangerVille there was a large flash of light causing his plane to short circuit and crash. George has since set up camp in the cargo bay of Old Penelope, and has lived on the outskirts of StrangerVille ever since. Although he has grown skeptical of the residents of StrangerVille he means no harm and mostly keeps to himself.</Text>
  <Text Key="90E5891A">Cahill</Text>
  <Text Key="0C966691">Old Penelope</Text>
  <Text Key="FE645B07">Nestled in the the heart of the StrangerVille Plaza, this quaint home is perfect for anyone new in town. Right across from the StrangerVille Library and the hottest bar in town Carpophagous Corner will put you right next to all the best attractions StrangerVille has to offer. </Text>
  <Text Key="4FF87DEC">Carpophagous Corner</Text>
  <Text Key="4FBC3924">8 Bells is the hottest bar in StrangerVille. Though they have little competition, the locals swear by the drinks. Located just near the StrangerVille National Base, you can always find Military Personnel winding down after a hard days work. The staff is friendly and are always looking to tell stories of StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="889F904B">8 Bells</Text>
  <Text Key="280BC3A9">The StrangerVille Information Center is a great place to hang out and study. We have a massive StrangerVille Archive where anyone can browse till their heart is content. The archives contain information about all the weird and unusual phenomena that has happened in our lovely little town. You can always find local Scientists here trying to brush up on research.</Text>
  <Text Key="D912285E">StrangerVille Information Center</Text>
  <Text Key="D187EB6E">Slip 42 used to be home to a local Conspiracy Theorist. One day they just decided to leave, no warning or notice, they were just gone. Upon inspection we found a strange note saying something about finding the Answer to the Ultimate Question of Life, The Universe, and Everything. The tenant even left all of their belongings behind. Those Conspiracy Theorists are definitely a strange bunch, but lucky for you Slip 42 is now vacant.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE8017E5">Slip 42</Text>
  <Text Key="836C1A19">Nestled slightly outside of town, and overlooking the StrangerVille creek. This quaint cliff side plot is bound to make the perfect foundation for any home.</Text>
  <Text Key="FFE59A0E">Creek Corner Cove</Text>
  <Text Key="C5CC82DE">Dream Weavers Way is tucked high atop a plateau where you can hear the babbling brook and embrace your inner creative self. Perfect for any starving artist that is just looking to get away from it all.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FED678F">The Eclectic Arts Household consists of three friends who have decided to cut ties with the modern world in order to explore their inner creativity. They received a large sum of money from their parents, and are using it to explore their creative dreams in a less hectic town.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BBEB056">Eclectic Arts Household</Text>
  <Text Key="B7DC5555">Dream Weavers Way</Text>
  <Text Key="0CC0EE53">StrangerVille is known for its plateaus and unique rock formations. There is no better place like Plateau Place to take all of that in.</Text>
  <Text Key="7C8C3700">Plateau Place</Text>
  <Text Key="38FAAD68">Providing the best views overlooking StrangerVille, Cliff Side Crest is the perfect place to build your dream home. Just ignore the strange lights coming from that crater.</Text>
  <Text Key="54DB0C17">Cliff Side Crest</Text>
  <Text Key="A1E57CED">With the best views of the StrangerVille Plaza the StrangerVille Overlook is the perfect place to keep a watchful eye on the tiny town of StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4D4ED6E">The Roswell's are the oldest residents in StrangerVille. Ted Roswell has since become the mayor and has been aggressively pushing to get StrangerVille to be more technologically advanced. He has made some shady deals, but his crowning achievement has been the construction of the Crater Base and Secret Lab. Ted's wife, Meredith, has been noticing Ted acting very strange at night. It might have something to do with his frequent visits to the Secret Lab to try and cover things up.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D812C11">Roswell</Text>
  <Text Key="67B1434A">StrangerVille Overlook</Text>
  <Text Key="A40BFC30">Pries</Text>
  <Text Key="F335B2DF">Clear Out Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="611A83CE">Search StrangerVille Archives</Text>
  <Text Key="8B9B577D">Restricted to Military Career Personnel Level 5 or higher.</Text>
  <Text Key="1471AE79">{0.SimFirstName} has already requisitioned a keycard. Check the mailbox after mail is delivered.</Text>
  <Text Key="75EA8EAD">Requisition Keycard</Text>
  <Text Key="4AA98605">Research Historic Battles</Text>
  <Text Key="B845A15E">Look up Conspiracy Theories</Text>
  <Text Key="31019017">Requires Programming Skill 3 or Higher</Text>
  <Text Key="E050067B">Hack for Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="086196AD">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Secret Dossier&lt;/b&gt;\nUse Evidence in your Sims inventory to compile a Secret Dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="8872BD15">Upload Secret Dossier to the Hacker Forums</Text>
  <Text Key="99394844">Change Passwords</Text>
  <Text Key="626A3A52">Write Report</Text>
  <Text Key="F4797395">{0.SimName} is being devoured by the Mother Plant. This will be the end of {0.SimName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E5F0BEA">Death By Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="4D7F4118">Possessed</Text>
  <Text Key="43B04B1A">Arm for Plant Attack (DEBUG)</Text>
  <Text Key="13E4DE77">Clog with Vines (DEBUG)</Text>
  <Text Key="82302FC5">A &lt;b&gt;Photo of Bizarre Plant&lt;/b&gt; has been added to your Sims Inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9EE48EA">You already have a picture of this in your inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5E2FC50">Harvest Bizarre Fruit</Text>
  <Text Key="C88A3A96">{0.ObjectDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="852F9CE4">Possess to Clear Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="65526FDB">Possess to Destroy Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="468D2548">Open Fan Mail</Text>
  <Text Key="1219085E">Open Fan Mail</Text>
  <Text Key="3DABA82D">&lt;b&gt;Requires: {1.SimFirstName} to Be Recently Vaccinated&lt;/b&gt;\nAdminister Infection Vaccine before trying to Recruit to Fight Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="281C50D9">Create Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="5A77634E">&lt;b&gt;Requires: 5 Spore Clusters and 1 Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt;\nUse the Infection Scanner to scan for Spore Clusters, and Nurture a Bizarre Plant to get Bizarre Fruit.</Text>
  <Text Key="7059D642">Resume Making Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="127B52AB">Create Experimental Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="A7E55F5A">Give Bizarre Fruit</Text>
  <Text Key="5E50092A">You must wait some time before nurturing this plant again.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDA3CF9A">Nurture</Text>
  <Text Key="316628D7">Chat with Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="98D5A4FB">Taunt</Text>
  <Text Key="6BE2F41C">Traces of infection have been detected in your refrigerator. We have confiscated it, and all of its contents. A refund has been issued for any inconvenience this may have caused.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC3D6EAF">&lt;b&gt;Battery Power Low:&lt;/b&gt; Allow time for this unit to recharge.\n\nTry scanning near areas with a high concentration of spores.</Text>
  <Text Key="0685F864">Scan Area</Text>
  <Text Key="E488998F">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;\nQuestion Scientists around town about Spores to get a Spore Filter.</Text>
  <Text Key="DBAE4F66">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Incomplete Hazmat Suite&lt;/b&gt;\nQuestion the Curio Shop Owner about Spores to see if they can help.</Text>
  <Text Key="88278E91">It doesn't look like there's anything useful to find here... for now.</Text>
  <Text Key="B15B442B">This has already been searched. Try asking other StrangerVille residents or looking in other places for more evidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="C45CF274">Blackmail</Text>
  <Text Key="AAAC7812">Listen In On {2.SimName}</Text>
  <Text Key="2BC887A2">Be Blackmailed</Text>
  <Text Key="1D70ECB3">Suspicious Hug</Text>
  <Text Key="F2F7FC24">{1.SimName} wasn't happy about being Blackmailed, but they coughed up some Simoleons to make sure that recording never got into the wrong hands.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F58F879">{1.SimName} didn't notice the bug being planted. Use the &lt;b&gt;Listening Device&lt;/b&gt; to see if {1.SimName} spills any important information!</Text>
  <Text Key="206EED69">Plant Bug</Text>
  <Text Key="689EDFF5">Thank you for shopping at Curios, Creations, and More... No one ever asks me what the "More" is, but any-who enjoy your new items.</Text>
  <Text Key="268C1D33">Buy Discounted Items...</Text>
  <Text Key="A175F27F">Buy Curio</Text>
  <Text Key="2E5578E2">Buy Curio Items...</Text>
  <Text Key="61ADB91D">Buy Tin-foil Hat</Text>
  <Text Key="ADC9D762">Buy a Novelty T-Shirt</Text>
  <Text Key="4DA9BBC1">Buy and Wear Tin-foil Hat</Text>
  <Text Key="E36DDE06">Buy and Wear a Novelty T-Shirt</Text>
  <Text Key="09A76E4B">Requires Secret Dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="170AFE18">???????</Text>
  <Text Key="BEB749E9">Come back after encountering &lt;b&gt;Strange Spores&lt;/b&gt; in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="89B7C0A8">Only 1 Hazmat Suit Per Person</Text>
  <Text Key="D7B1CA7A">Question about Spores in Lab with the Curio Shop owner. Maybe he has something that might help.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CEA2354">Enjoy your brand new &lt;b&gt;Incomplete Hazmat Suit&lt;/b&gt;, I told you it was missing a crucial component... You might want to Question &lt;b&gt;Scientists&lt;/b&gt; about Spores. They might be able to provide some kind of &lt;b&gt;Spore Filter&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="D8BBEB7A">Buy Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="3ACAE7C0">Come back after examining the &lt;b&gt;Lab Door&lt;/b&gt; in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab.&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="BB85986E">&lt;b&gt;Request Keycard&lt;/b&gt; from the Curio Shop owner to see if he can provide any information about this.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B4E4782">Only 1 Keycard Per Person</Text>
  <Text Key="683921CD">Trade the Secret Dossier and some Simoleons for the Keycard to the Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="35D8F52D">{0.SimName} just obtained the &lt;b&gt;Keycard&lt;/b&gt;. It should grant access to any door in the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="5034ABE9">Buy Keycard and Give Dossier</Text>
  <Text Key="B49C4206">Wear Tin-foil Hat</Text>
  <Text Key="983038A5">Wear a Novelty T-Shirt</Text>
  <Text Key="8AD8E426">&lt;b&gt;Requires: StrangerVille Evidence&lt;/b&gt;\nTry searching around StrangerVille to see what you can dig up.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA964300">Your Sim is going to need all the evidence they can get for a Secret Dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="68D53814">Sell All Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="16857581">Sell Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="D44CF75C">Accuse of Spying</Text>
  <Text Key="2141F8EC">Be Accused of Spying by {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="AEB643C8">Tell Story about Defeating the Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="1CD7E2EC">Give Secret Lab Keycard</Text>
  <Text Key="C8D5EED3">Question about StrangerVille Mystery</Text>
  <Text Key="176D7917">Request Evidence from Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="DAA7740F">Request Evidence for StrangerVille Mystery</Text>
  <Text Key="7D6C1ABA">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;\nThis can be discovered on the Chemical Analyzer at the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0CA1271">Ask to Craft Spore Filter</Text>
  <Text Key="403D3338">I really shouldn't... but whatever, the government has tons of these. Here you go!</Text>
  <Text Key="401FE986">Bribe for Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="716EE482">Fight for Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="9688D7DE">Impress for Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="FF08671F">Requires Military Career rank 5 or higher</Text>
  <Text Key="A39F5069">Have the spores gotten to your brain?! You need to be at least a Warrant Officer to do that.</Text>
  <Text Key="EFD663A5">Sir yes Sir! Here's my &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. I will requisition a new one from my CO.</Text>
  <Text Key="24D7F742">Pull Rank for Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="DDC3B051">Seduce for Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="DA4791A6">Question about Spores In Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="499ACE44">&lt;b&gt;{1.SimFirstName} is already recruited&lt;/b&gt;\nRun "Fight with..." on the Mother Plant to have {1.SimFirstName} join you in the fight.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED9F75C6">Recruit to Fight Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="EB95E14C">Talk about StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="A2FED62C">Request Evidence from Military Base</Text>
  <Text Key="1CB27418">Question about Military Base</Text>
  <Text Key="5AF9B28A">Question about Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="0C651874">Request Keycard</Text>
  <Text Key="5007D6CF">Share Conspiracy Theories</Text>
  <Text Key="E3292175">Give Inspirational Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="F919BE8F">Interrogate</Text>
  <Text Key="35B69F01">Attention!</Text>
  <Text Key="E9BAF830">Clean This Place Up</Text>
  <Text Key="A5DB224C">Drop and Give Me 20</Text>
  <Text Key="CEF5AA70">Run a Lap</Text>
  <Text Key="3A34B3BF">Spar Against</Text>
  <Text Key="49BF09CB">Try to Recruit into Military</Text>
  <Text Key="B956FC89">Salute</Text>
  <Text Key="EE3A0CD1">Share War Stories</Text>
  <Text Key="4BC1F829">Spar</Text>
  <Text Key="B15ADCDB">Military Introduction</Text>
  <Text Key="087CBC68">Communicate?</Text>
  <Text Key="325953F2">Confess Fear of Humans</Text>
  <Text Key="AE2ABCB5">Emulate Human Laugh</Text>
  <Text Key="0542FD38">Discuss The Great Mother</Text>
  <Text Key="B76CA600">Move Lips to Make Human Sounds</Text>
  <Text Key="A28232DB">{1.SimFirstName} is acting very odd</Text>
  <Text Key="C3160125">Complain about Normal Human Problems</Text>
  <Text Key="8718A6F3">Discuss Human Things</Text>
  <Text Key="CB30B6C2">Enthuse about Human Hobbies</Text>
  <Text Key="9C30317D">Praise the Great Mother</Text>
  <Text Key="AC3A0042">Talk about Plants</Text>
  <Text Key="368C7860">Share Conspiracy Theories</Text>
  <Text Key="5E024E90">Listen to {1.SimFirstName}'s Conspiracy Theories</Text>
  <Text Key="BE30A1A7">Ask for Fruit</Text>
  <Text Key="BCA78B79">Attempt to Communicate</Text>
  <Text Key="7B55A114">Communicate</Text>
  <Text Key="E8F98A14">The Mother Plant will only grant 1 request a day.</Text>
  <Text Key="41C5089D">With a snap of her mighty tentacle the Mother Plant has spread a small amount of spores over StrangerVille. There will be a small number of Possessed Sims walking the streets, and the Bizarre Plants have returned to their sprout form.</Text>
  <Text Key="B4222093">Request Weirdness</Text>
  <Text Key="6C740598">With a snap of her mighty tentacle the Mother Plant has spread a medium amount of spores over StrangerVille. There will be a medium number of Possessed Sims walking the streets, and the Bizarre Plants have returned to their blooming form.</Text>
  <Text Key="A3281B48">Request Moderate Weirdness</Text>
  <Text Key="E6E0ADFB">With a snap of her mighty tentacle the Mother Plant has spread a large amount of spores over StrangerVille. There will be a large number of Possessed Sims walking the streets, and the Bizarre Plants have returned to their blooming form.</Text>
  <Text Key="AFCE5929">Request Maximum Weirdness</Text>
  <Text Key="A74C618E">With a snap of her mighty tentacle the Mother Plant has removed all spores from StrangerVille. There will be no more Possessed Sims walking the streets, and the Bizarre Plants have all been eradicated.</Text>
  <Text Key="6783D8E6">Request Normality</Text>
  <Text Key="F574CE96">Request Energy</Text>
  <Text Key="EF5FF231">Request Life Extension</Text>
  <Text Key="742E86E0">Request Riches</Text>
  <Text Key="07DC8A11">Request Career Success</Text>
  <Text Key="61ABF7F2">This Sim is knocked out! Command another ally to revive them!</Text>
  <Text Key="3C70F2A7">Command to Fight Possessed Minion</Text>
  <Text Key="1E82F5F0">Command to Revive Ally</Text>
  <Text Key="E1D56D6D">Command to Throw Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="0F5FF023">Eat Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="06ED58C3">Set Alluring</Text>
  <Text Key="A10A5311">Set Default</Text>
  <Text Key="8FE9FA39">Set Dead</Text>
  <Text Key="DEC8FD0B">Kill</Text>
  <Text Key="E153BEB8">Revive Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="78FD770B">Fight the Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="B62A49F1">You are deep in battle with the Mother Plant and unable to save or travel while fighting.</Text>
  <Text Key="F070542C">Attempt to Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="7612E071">Attempt to Fight Again</Text>
  <Text Key="7D2F4C36">Mega Spray</Text>
  <Text Key="84836FA1">Your team deals more damage, but becomes infected faster!</Text>
  <Text Key="DEF5B523">Charge!</Text>
  <Text Key="A4BF952B">Defeat Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="2DDEFF13">You recently changed the fight mode. Your allies need some time to perform your command.</Text>
  <Text Key="878F5FE7">Your team resists the Infection, but deals less damage.</Text>
  <Text Key="0AD3AD15">Be Careful!</Text>
  <Text Key="56FF0306">The sprayer is too hot.  Give it time before unleashing another Mega Spray.</Text>
  <Text Key="CD6C64D1">Your team heals some of their Infection, but does no damage.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E35BC53">Take a Breather</Text>
  <Text Key="67F2C49E">Retreat</Text>
  <Text Key="CEC730EB">It's too dangerous to throw another one right now!</Text>
  <Text Key="66A19430">Your Sim is out of Vaccines!</Text>
  <Text Key="55F87FC0">Throw Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="A90A7977">Your team scares off the Mother Plant's minions, but does less damage.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1F015A5">Warbling War Cry!</Text>
  <Text Key="18F28FDE">Taunt</Text>
  <Text Key="0B496921">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Bizarre Fruit&lt;/b&gt;\nThe Curio Shop probably has a few Bizarre Fruit.</Text>
  <Text Key="8FBC8FFF">Revive Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="280198DC">Attempt to Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="7AFA7609">Fight Mother Plant with</Text>
  <Text Key="93CC0F4D">Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="5759E965">Admire Achievements and Accolades</Text>
  <Text Key="D4179B0D">The circuits are too hot to repair. Give this machine some time to cool down.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AB4A00C">This computer seems to have some encryption. Requires Handiness skill 9 or higher.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B8D0419">Scan Here</Text>
  <Text Key="5968DED4">Purchase Bugs</Text>
  <Text Key="7742C1B2">Curio</Text>
  <Text Key="018F4295">Thank you for shopping at Curios, Creations, and More... No one ever asks me what the "More" is, but any-who enjoy your new items.</Text>
  <Text Key="40B32D39">A &lt;b&gt;Photo of Sealed Door&lt;/b&gt; has been added to your Sims Inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BA3BC9D">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Keycard&lt;/b&gt;\nQuestion Scientists, Military, or Conspiracy Theorists to see how to gain access.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC407420">StrangerVille Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="1F1CB0F9">Clear Out Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="88B6C3F0">Take Picture</Text>
  <Text Key="AAE23FB5">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Level 10 Programming Skill&lt;/b&gt;\n Who knows what secrets this could be hiding...</Text>
  <Text Key="43947250">Decrypt</Text>
  <Text Key="EE6D7560">&lt;b&gt;Requires: 15 Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt;\nQuestion Military Personnel at the &lt;b&gt;Local Bar&lt;/b&gt; to get an &lt;b&gt;Infection Scanner&lt;/b&gt;. It can be used to find Spore Clusters.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E0252FF">Your analysis of the Spores is complete. Ask any Scientists to Craft the Spore Filter to give them the &lt;b&gt;Infection Profile Data&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A8FFF94">Construct Infection Profile Data</Text>
  <Text Key="8AF65C87">Converts an unused &lt;b&gt;Experimental Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; in the sim's inventory into an &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="7A10F3B5">Convert Experimental Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="7F4690F0">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Sim to be Actively Posessed&lt;/b&gt;\nFind Possessed Sims walking around town to test the Experimental Vaccine.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A2E072F">The Vaccine seemed to caused some kind of reaction, but did not completely isolate the Infection. Keep testing on other Possessed Sims to see how it will react.</Text>
  <Text Key="C79DDBBC">Eureka! The Vaccine seems to be isolating the Infection. Head back to the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to create the &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; on the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6545D44">I feel so much better. I can think clearly and that terrible sound in my head is gone.</Text>
  <Text Key="2CD4BEA3">Drink Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="50B0A962">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Requires 15 Pieces of StrangerVille Evidence.&lt;/b&gt;\nWith a Secret Dossier, you can convince someone to give you a Keycard for the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D082108">Compile Secret Dossier</Text>
  <Text Key="5E1A539F">Give Investigation System Inventory Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="953F28C8">Wear Hazmat Suit (DEBUG)</Text>
  <Text Key="3D03192A">Combine With Spore Filter</Text>
  <Text Key="A02B97EF">I don't think that's such a good idea {0.SimFirstName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="05C3911F">Remove Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="D6410456">Wear Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="0A68D782">Combine With Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="7F6CF628">Open</Text>
  <Text Key="BC67377D">Search for Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="82ED4483">Search for Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="CF608DB0">Cry Over Dead Plants</Text>
  <Text Key="972ECB18">Liberate</Text>
  <Text Key="9D4086E0">Stare Blankly</Text>
  <Text Key="4E44655E">Examine</Text>
  <Text Key="234AFEE4">Take Photo for Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="6A77A1CB">Use Keycard</Text>
  <Text Key="B4263C41">Infected Attack</Text>
  <Text Key="E1182CF3">Snap Out of It</Text>
  <Text Key="44EAD031">Fighting the Possession</Text>
  <Text Key="E90F232A">Practice Sparring</Text>
  <Text Key="CBCD795D">Practice Sparring</Text>
  <Text Key="C3AFDB63">Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="D372A947">Practice Ordering Around</Text>
  <Text Key="C2E8D063">Order to Spar Against</Text>
  <Text Key="1175A2D8">{0.SimFirstName} Does not have anyone available on the lot to Practice Sparring With...</Text>
  <Text Key="79EBD687">Practice Sparring With</Text>
  <Text Key="6D121CF4">&lt;b&gt;Requires: 1-3 Allies&lt;/b&gt;\nUse the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt; to construct &lt;b&gt;Vaccines&lt;/b&gt; to Vaccinate and Recruit allies to help fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="B26F6DE1">You must be near the Mother Plant in order to run this interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCCAFEF7">You cannot fight the Mother Plant while you have the Infected Trait. Craft a Vaccine on the Chemical Analyzer to cure yourself.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F750B94">Listen In On</Text>
  <Text Key="B49E7C0E">Place a bug on another Sim to listen in on their conversations.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB3CD1F2">Clear Out Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="C7FDE631">Death will not fall for such silly tricks!</Text>
  <Text Key="3468DB42">β€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥β€ŁŁΔβ€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥β€ΔUŦ¥</Text>
  <Text Key="A41D99E1">ΔĆĆ€PŦ Ħ€Ř ǤI₣ŦŞ ΔŇĐ ΔŁŁ ŴIŁŁ β€ Ŵ€ŁŁ</Text>
  <Text Key="329B15F7">€ΜβŘΔĆ€ ŦĦ€ ΜØŦĦ€Ř ŞĦ€ ŴIŁŁ βŘIŇG ¥ØU P€ΔĆ€</Text>
  <Text Key="7C1C1237">ŁØØK ŦØ ŦĦ€ ŞK¥ IŦ Ŵ€ŁĆØΜ€Ş UŞ ΔŁŁ</Text>
  <Text Key="B79B84D8">ŴΔŦ€Ř IŞ ŁØV€ ŴΔŦ€Ř IŞ ŁI₣€</Text>
  <Text Key="14B8C6D1">Ŵ€ŁĆØΜ€ ŦØ ŞŦŘΔŇǤ€RVIŁŁ€</Text>
  <Text Key="AE878A5A">Ħ€Ř Ň€ŞT IŞ ĆŁØUĐ€Đ IŇ β€ΔUŦ¥ Ŵ€ ĐØ ŇØT Đ€Ş€ŘV€ Ħ€Ř</Text>
  <Text Key="C9C14B46">ØP€Ň ¥ØUŘ €¥€Ş ŦØ ŦĦ€ β€ΔUT¥ ØF Ħ€Ř βŁØŞŞØΜŞ</Text>
  <Text Key="1102082F">ØUŘ ΜØŦĦ€Ř ĐŘ€ŞŞ€Đ IŇ Ř€Đ ŞĦ€ IŞ β€ΔUŦ¥</Text>
  <Text Key="86F401AD">ŦĦ€ ΜØŦĦ€Ř ҜŇØŴŞ ΔŁŁ ĐØ ŇØŦ Ř€ŞIŞŦ Ħ€Ř</Text>
  <Text Key="908B9106">ĴØIŇ UŞ ĆØŇŞUΜ€ ŦĦ€ FŘUIŦ ØF ŦĦ€ ΜØŦĦ€Ř ΔŇĐ KŇØŴ P€ΔĆ€</Text>
  <Text Key="0E00CB01">ØUŘ €¥€Ş ΔŘ€ ØƤ€Ň</Text>
  <Text Key="D000C86C">Try to Talk to {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="AB37AA2A">Welcome to StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="44E84A1B">Listen to Organic Matter Noises</Text>
  <Text Key="31DC8299">Listen to Incoherent Rambling</Text>
  <Text Key="83C4C095">There is nothing to see here.  Everything is within normal operating levels. Please abstain from going near the Secret Lab and have a nice day.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C2E3A42">Get the Facts</Text>
  <Text Key="A7581E3B">Listen to Conspiracy Rant</Text>
  <Text Key="C7F14F47">{1.SimFirstName} has recently been vaccinated.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D0BF775">Accept Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="2FB6AF6A">I feel so much better. I can think clearly and that terrible sound in my head is gone.</Text>
  <Text Key="9EEB59C8">Administer Infection Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="47D966BB">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Sim to be Actively Possessed&lt;/b&gt;\nFind Possessed Sims walking around town to test the Experimental Vaccine.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BAD3EC0">You have all the information that you need to cure the infection. Head back to the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt; to create the &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt; on the &lt;b&gt;Chemical Analyzer&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA43E03E">You've already tested the vaccine in {1.SimFirstName}. Seek out another Possessed sim to test the Experimental Vaccine.</Text>
  <Text Key="97AD42AB">Test Experimental Vaccine</Text>
  <Text Key="0626D7CF">Listen to Fellow Host</Text>
  <Text Key="379D25CF">Salute</Text>
  <Text Key="AB989B52">Judge Physical Condition</Text>
  <Text Key="69054426">Impress With Physical Prowess</Text>
  <Text Key="FA507739">Listen to Strange Tunes</Text>
  <Text Key="B7A35885">Listen to Strange Tunes</Text>
  <Text Key="A93CAE4E">Interrogate</Text>
  <Text Key="5E8C9493">You must wait before spreading more Bizarre Plants.</Text>
  <Text Key="A8BDE11A">Plant Bizarre Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="F182658A">March Around</Text>
  <Text Key="AA9F896C">Clear Out Vines</Text>
  <Text Key="6AD07834">Wander</Text>
  <Text Key="0BC9F92C">Patrol the Streets</Text>
  <Text Key="59C8A896">Larry's Old Watering Hole</Text>
  <Text Key="A1CF5D30">Hunker Down Bunker</Text>
  <Text Key="659BC907">Ominous Observatory</Text>
  <Text Key="3C0FDFB2">Garden of Metamorphosis</Text>
  <Text Key="CF6D69C7">ŦĦ€ ΔŘβØŘ€ΔŁ ΜIŇĐ ĐŘ€ΔΜŞ ŦĦŘØUGĦ ØUŘ FŁ€ŞĦ¥ €¥€Ş</Text>
  <Text Key="83B5BDDA">PØŞŞ€ŞŞ€Đ</Text>
  <Text Key="3758F32A">&lt;b&gt;Welcome to StrangerVille:&lt;/b&gt; "The only thing stranger than the people is the flora!"\n\nSoon after moving in, the town’s slogan is starting to make sense to you. Some of the locals are acting a bit suspicious and there's a large number of Military and Scientists in town.\n\n&lt;b&gt;Try asking people about StrangerVille. They might be able to shed some light on this strange situation.&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="F78989E4">StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="F266A3D3">Leaving the Secret Lab you can't help but notice the sky has shifted to an eerie color. Something has changed in StrangerVille, and not for the better. Opening that lab door must have released some kind of toxin into the air.\n\n&lt;b&gt;You will need to find a way to protect yourself from the toxic spores in the Secret Lab. Try talking to people around town to see if they know of anything that might help.&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="94EFAA61">The Bloom Begins</Text>
  <Text Key="1825E8F0">You’ve discovered the source of the infection plaguing StrangerVille: an enormous “Mother” plant buried in the base of the lab. The only way to get the town back to normal is to defeat the vile creature!\n\n&lt;b&gt;Find a cure for the infection and assemble a team to destroy the Mother Plant.&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="F466747E">Stop The Infection</Text>
  <Text Key="63AAC579">With one last screech the Mother Plant collapses. Returning home you notice that things are beginning to return to normal. The Bizarre Plants are subsiding and the infected are waking up from their nightmare. StrangerVille owes you a huge debt. You are a Hometown Hero!\n\n&lt;b&gt;You have defeated the Mother Plant and returned StrangerVille to “normal”! You can return to the Mother Plant at any point to reawaken her. Once resurrected, you can have her set the Infection Level to your desired Strangeness. This will allow you to replay the story with other families.&lt;/b&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="9B0EACAB">A Little Less StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED7B">Ugh, this air is getting GROSS! One of these &lt;b&gt;scientists&lt;/b&gt; needs to invent something to make it &lt;b&gt;easier to breathe&lt;/b&gt;!</Text>
  <Text Key="9F38D891">All my neighbors have been infected. I’d do anything to help bring them back to normal.</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED78">Why haven’t these &lt;b&gt;scientists&lt;/b&gt; come up with something to &lt;b&gt;filter&lt;/b&gt; this polluted air!</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED79">That &lt;b&gt;Curio Shop&lt;/b&gt; is always selling science-y &lt;b&gt;equipment&lt;/b&gt;... I wonder where it comes from?</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED7E">This air is getting so nasty I’m afraid to even leave my house. I wish I was wearing a &lt;b&gt;hazmat suit&lt;/b&gt;!</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED7F">Be careful walking around outside. The news said the air is getting worse every hour!</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED7C">There are so many possessed people around! Can’t somebody find a cure for them or something?!</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED7D">I think the Scientists are collecting &lt;b&gt;Spore Clusters&lt;/b&gt; so they can make some kind of vaccine at the &lt;b&gt;Secret Lab&lt;/b&gt;.</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED72">It seems like they’ve figured out a way to cure people. I hope this all gets fixed soon!</Text>
  <Text Key="D811ED73">If I had access to the &lt;b&gt;Infection Vaccine&lt;/b&gt;, I’d be willing to help put a stop to this terror!</Text>
  <Text Key="5D64184D">Investigate the Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="8C70204E">Find a Keycard to open the Secret Lab Door.</Text>
  <Text Key="83108FEE">Construct a Modified Hazmat Suit to get through Toxic Spores and explore deeper in the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="252A782D">Buy a Hazmat Suit from the Curio Shop.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F47345">Give a Scientist the Infection Profile Data for a Spore Filter.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1889B6F">Install the Spore Filter on the Incomplete Hazmat Suit.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7A2953B">Wear the Modified Hazmat Suit to open the Second Door to the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="C574B07F">Defeat the Mother Plant and rid StrangerVille of the infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="A000F80A">Recruit Sims to fight the Mother Plant.</Text>
  <Text Key="4FB15BDC">Use the Infection Vaccine to give other Sims immunity to the Infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="1480C72A">Collect and analyze 15 Spore Clusters on the Chemical Analyzer to discover the Infection Profile Data.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AC0F08B">Create an Infection Vaccine on the Chemical Analyzer at the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2BCD8E1">&lt;span class="money"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;\n&lt;b&gt;Used for:&lt;/b&gt; Eating, Fun, Alternate Light Source.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FB344FD">Basic Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="C1387D9F">Top Secret Recording of: &lt;b&gt;{0.SimName}&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThis can be combined with other evidence into a Secret Dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA5A001A">Top Secret Audio Recording</Text>
  <Text Key="F8EA1626">{0.ObjectDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="43B33CBB">Bizarre Fruit</Text>
  <Text Key="B0275CC5">
  </Text>
  <Text Key="0E4F7EA2">
  </Text>
  <Text Key="7F0E55F5">Thank you for saving StrangerVille from that terrible infection. Here is a small token of thanks.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C466A5C">{0.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="F8B1FA7C">{0.ObjectDescription}</Text>
  <Text Key="8B8CBE98">Recording of: &lt;b&gt;{0.SimName}&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThis can be used to Blackmail {0.SimName} into giving you a few Simoleons.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F3DF0BC">Music for when you're feeling a bit strange...</Text>
  <Text Key="82DCA8B9">Strange Tunes</Text>
  <Text Key="B8F290CD">The Listening Device will allow your Sim to plant bugs on other Sims and listen in on them. You never know what juicy gossip you will find out.</Text>
  <Text Key="242FB718">Listening Device W/Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="F0FE55C5">Go for a Jog</Text>
  <Text Key="F8828ADA">Click on your sim and select Go Jogging.</Text>
  <Text Key="344FB4E6">Practice Sparring</Text>
  <Text Key="19D01A9F">Purchase a Training Bot from the Catalog. Click on it and select Practice Sparring.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F5E0CC1">Practice Marching</Text>
  <Text Key="C6AD9246">Click on your Sim select March Around</Text>
  <Text Key="A3803B9C">Run on the Treadmill</Text>
  <Text Key="CF89BE59">Click on the treadmill and select Workout.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED4BE294">Workout at the Exercise Machine</Text>
  <Text Key="A7794ED1">Click on a Workout Machine and select Workout.</Text>
  <Text Key="311A09D7">Find StrangerVille Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="9AA02F18">Search around the secret lab and find some investigation evidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="05053FD1">Interrogate Locals</Text>
  <Text Key="0D222E76">Click on another Sim and run the Interrogate interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FFEE364">Listen in on a Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="5FC37DC1">After you plant a bug on another Sim click on the Listening Device and select Listen In On.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCCCB14B">Plant a Bug on Another Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="22D60E6C">Purchase Bugs from the Listening Device, then click on another Sim and select Plant Bug</Text>
  <Text Key="AB286F1F">Research StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="32F00300">Go to the Library. Click on a bookshelf and select Research StrangerVille Archives.</Text>
  <Text Key="70675C52">Write Report</Text>
  <Text Key="2AEBE89B">Click on a computer and select Write Report.</Text>
  <Text Key="3078B25C">Give Inspirational Speech</Text>
  <Text Key="69552619">Click on another Sim and run the Give Inspirational Speech social interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1ED13A7">Order Around Other Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="BF9D6E88">Click on a Sim, select Order To... and run any Order To... interaction.</Text>
  <Text Key="3F506979">Practice Sparring</Text>
  <Text Key="2EFC651E">Click on the Training Bot and select Practice Sparring.</Text>
  <Text Key="A15592C1">Practice Ordering Around</Text>
  <Text Key="37259446">Click on the B64 Training Bot and select Practice Ordering Around</Text>
  <Text Key="9133CF2A">Recruit Other Sims to the Military</Text>
  <Text Key="32DBF7B3">Click on another sim and select Recruit.</Text>
  <Text Key="E2C956F1">Research Historic Battles</Text>
  <Text Key="D428F3D6">Click on a computer and select Research Historic Battles.</Text>
  <Text Key="3356900E">Spar with a Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="5899AD67">Click on another Sim and select Spar.</Text>
  <Text Key="8DB7130E">Train Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="0851EE67">Click on another Sim and select Order To, then Drop and Give Me 20.</Text>
  <Text Key="48EF3042">Talk about StrangerVille with {1.Number} Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="44BDBB6B">Click on another Sim and select Talk about StrangerVille.</Text>
  <Text Key="0EA91735">Buy Curio from the Curio Shop</Text>
  <Text Key="417FAC2A">The Curio Shop can be found near the trailer park. Click on the stand and run Buy Curio... to see what they have to offer. Supposedly there is even a Secret Inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="32702B17">Examine Sealed Door at Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="FAD000BC">Travel to the Secret Lab at the edge of StrangerVille and investigate the Sealed Door.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B308EE4">Gather {1.Number} Pieces of Evidence</Text>
  <Text Key="DE0A1D81">Evidence can be found all over StrangerVille.\nSearch boxes and papers at the Secret Lab.\nSearch StrangerVille Archives at the Library.\nQuestion Sims around StrangerVille.\nBuy a Listening Device to Listen In On Scientist and Military Personnel.</Text>
  <Text Key="045DB90E">Compile a StrangerVille Secret Dossier</Text>
  <Text Key="818C5067">Collect evidence throughout StrangerVille. Then click on it in your Sims inventory to Compile a StrangerVille Dossier. The Secret Lab might be a good place to start for evidence.</Text>
  <Text Key="2E7036CF">Open the Sealed Door in the Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="78427510">That door at the Secret Lab requires a Keycard. Talk to people around town to see if they know where to get one.</Text>
  <Text Key="53826610">Collect {1.Number} Spore Clusters</Text>
  <Text Key="83B7A18D">Find an Infection Scanner by questioning Military Personnel at the Local Bar. Once you have one in your inventory scan the ground to reveal Spore Clusters.</Text>
  <Text Key="D99C7D37">Assemble the Hazmat Suit</Text>
  <Text Key="7B1D9DB8">Find a Hazmat Suit and a Spore Filter then Combine them in your Inventory. Question about Spores With Scientist at the Local Library, and the Curio Shop Owner to get more information.</Text>
  <Text Key="17308CD6">Traverse to the deepest part of the Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="619BA22F">Pass through the Toxic Hallway to open the final door deep in the Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E3E7517">Vaccinate {1.Number} Sims</Text>
  <Text Key="AE96F458">Create Experimental Vaccine on the Chemical Analyzer at the Secret Lab. Test this 3 times on Possessed Sims to unlock the ability to create the Infection Vaccine on the Chemical Analyzer. Once you have an Infection Vaccine you will be able to Vaccinate other Sims and Recruit them.</Text>
  <Text Key="36CC99F0">Recruit {1.Number} Sims to Help Stop the Source of the Infection</Text>
  <Text Key="EF7D842D">Click on Sims to try and recruit them to Fight the Mother Plant. Infected Sims will not want to assist you.</Text>
  <Text Key="46D19869">Defeat the source of the Infection</Text>
  <Text Key="1F847BAE">This is the Final step to eliminating the infection from StrangerVille. It will not be easy...</Text>
  <Text Key="4903F5B9">Talk with Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="33CAD81E">Buy Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="8CAF5D25">Secret Inventory</Text>
  <Text Key="ECD52FB0">Buy Discounted Clothing</Text>
  <Text Key="D701E362">Order To</Text>
  <Text Key="8C6757FC">Group Commands</Text>
  <Text Key="A265693C">Request Gifts</Text>
  <Text Key="DE4F7E06">Request Weirdness</Text>
  <Text Key="0D19BA2C">StrangerVille Investigation</Text>
  <Text Key="0E7B7B27">Convince to Give Infection Scanner</Text>
  <Text Key="A6D05ACC">ExcUUUUUuuusssEEee yOOuuUu! We prefer the term "Vintage," thank you.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AAC3B83">Old School Stair Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="9BF02D88">StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="46409628">Hero Of StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="20475987">As the Hero of StrangerVille you will receive fan mail as well as being able to retell the tale of how you defeated the source of the Infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="B2057D52">Congratulations!  The vile tyranny of the Mother has been brought to justice.  Your heroic victory has been compensated with a sampling of the Mother for you to display.</Text>
  <Text Key="267288C1">(From Infected Trait)</Text>
  <Text Key="A7395302">(From Being Commanded)</Text>
  <Text Key="218E0FF1">(From Commanding the Group)</Text>
  <Text Key="57D655EB">Pries</Text>
  <Text Key="15E403FA">Erwin</Text>
  <Text Key="340E0E52">Cahill</Text>
  <Text Key="580B2B15">George</Text>
  <Text Key="B7C9DD53">Eggleston</Text>
  <Text Key="A3B89372">Mark</Text>
  <Text Key="BFC209E0">Martin</Text>
  <Text Key="1E1D573F">Alice</Text>
  <Text Key="7D6E30D9">Holland</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D4293C">Leslie</Text>
  <Text Key="33C4838F">Roswell</Text>
  <Text Key="FE262EB1">Ted</Text>
  <Text Key="5CCA1535">Meredith</Text>
  <Text Key="D5360459">Sigworth</Text>
  <Text Key="8849862D">Dylan</Text>
  <Text Key="4C1C8606">Christie</Text>
  <Text Key="126A560F">Jess</Text>
  <Text Key="3657A985">Perform interactions on the Mother Plant to deplete her health!</Text>
  <Text Key="620DCF1A">Defeat the Mother Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="FF90D2B6">Battle In Progress</Text>
  <Text Key="09DA0882">Gather your allies and take battle to the Mother Plant itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="302F692D">(From Infected Trait)</Text>
  <Text Key="DC276252">You are not authorized to do that while being investigated.</Text>
  <Text Key="10E56E80">Welcome to StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="DFB99E0C">Some of your new neighbors are stopping by to welcome you to StrangerVille, but something is definitely... off... about them.</Text>
  <Text Key="C13CA310">Team Infection Level</Text>
  <Text Key="841AD9D8">The Mother Plant is trying to infect you! Defeat her before you get overwhelmed by the Infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F70ABF0">The Brains</Text>
  <Text Key="F6ADAC7B">The Brawn</Text>
  <Text Key="C0787AF2">The Clown</Text>
  <Text Key="F67FF256">The Leader</Text>
  <Text Key="5B863C73">Conspiracy Theorist</Text>
  <Text Key="9C282F06">Military Personnel</Text>
  <Text Key="2612627D">Scientist</Text>
  <Text Key="48F6DE98">{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="7F370808">I really shouldn't be giving you this but... here.\n\n{0.SimFirstName} received StrangerVille Evidence:\n\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="398753AA">All available bathtubs are clogged!</Text>
  <Text Key="A7B4C511">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Higher Relationship&lt;/b&gt;\nPeople in StrangerVille are not going to share top secret information with just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="6234DB57">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Secret Dossier&lt;/b&gt;\nUse Evidence in your Sims inventory to compile a Secret Dossier.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1F5034D">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Higher Relationship&lt;/b&gt;\nPeople in StrangerVille are not going to share top secret information with just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0626E75">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Higher Relationship&lt;/b&gt;\nPeople are not going to put their life on the line for just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1957AD9">&lt;b&gt;Requires: Higher Relationship&lt;/b&gt;\nPeople in StrangerVille are not going to share top secret information with just anyone.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4F61645">The weather is far too strange to use the Weather Machine here.</Text>
  <Text Key="BEC02963">Hero of StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="18E25339">Hero of StrangerVille</Text>
  <Text Key="52C6267E">As the Hero of StrangerVille you will receive fan mail as well as being able to retell the tale of how you defeated the source of the infection.</Text>
  <Text Key="B33C1A19">(From Completing The StrangerVille Mystery)</Text>
  <Text Key="B7F3B15A">Paranoid</Text>
  <Text Key="BBD1E20A">Paranoid</Text>
  <Text Key="7DF2CC35">Paranoid Sims feel that danger is around every corner, and that people are always talking about them. Paranoid Sims feel a sense of security while hanging out in basements.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AD2D902">Infected</Text>
  <Text Key="8FB3C692">Infected</Text>
  <Text Key="C9E7260D">Infected Sims have been exposed to the StrangerVille Infection. Sims might exhibit strange behavior, or even become Possessed.</Text>
  <Text Key="81A78AB8">(From Consuming Bizarre Fruit or Spores)</Text>
  <Text Key="DAC17381">Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="348DBCC9">Secret Lab</Text>
  <Text Key="BB026CB6">Corrugated Metal</Text>
  <Text Key="483828E9">Metal Enclosure</Text>
  <Text Key="DA6F1429">This weather seems a bit out of the ordinary... It might have something to do with that Secret Lab.</Text>
  <Text Key="223CD90C">Strange Weather</Text>
  <Text Key="B30BE857">Mysterious!</Text>
  <Text Key="9563A52E">Crater Base</Text>
  <Text Key="752DD17D">StrangerVille Plaza is where the locals like to hang out. You can find Scientists at the Library, Military Personnel at the Bar, and The Curio Shop near the trailer park.\n\nYou can buy some strange odds and ends here and you will find all the information you need.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E13BFE8">StrangerVille Plaza</Text>
  <Text Key="DF9FB961">Pristine, secluded, and nestled high atop a plateau, Shady Acres is home to the more wealthy locals of StrangerVille. Curious how some of them came into their wealth?</Text>
  <Text Key="AF119614">Shady Acres</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>