<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="30B55D1F">(Putting a Murphy Bed Away)</Text>
  <Text Key="53A2A8DC">(Being Stuck Under a Murphy Bed)</Text>
  <Text Key="31B97511">(Being Swallowed By a Murphy Bed)</Text>
  <Text Key="59EABB89">(From living in a Micro Home)</Text>
  <Text Key="5FF5AC7E">(From living in a Tiny Home)</Text>
  <Text Key="BB16BDCF">(From living in a Small Home)</Text>
  <Text Key="F6A9E6C5">One With The Remote</Text>
  <Text Key="E0B66C22">A remote control is an extension of body, spirit, and soul.</Text>
  <Text Key="E8AD3518">Ouch! That was super scary. What if you were trapped there forever? What body part would you have to saw off to get free? On second thought don't answer that.</Text>
  <Text Key="B69D8297">Stuck Under Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="84BC6891">*!@$*! was that? {0.SimFirstName} barely made it out alive. Be wary of the broken murphy bed.</Text>
  <Text Key="601694E4">Swallowed By Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="257EA8F1">Gaze upon the Micro Home. Gain increased duration to Happy, Inspired and Focused Buffs. Receive Household Bill Reduction. Increased Comfort gain from objects. Increase to Skill gains. Increased Gardening growth and plant health. Bonus Relationship gains with other Sims on lot. </Text>
  <Text Key="513E27C4">Micro Home</Text>
  <Text Key="7293DFB6">Tiny Home, Big Bonuses. Gain increased duration to Happy, Inspired and Focused Buffs. Receive Household Bill Reduction. Increased Comfort gain from objects. Increase to Skill gains.</Text>
  <Text Key="96D27EE9">Tiny Home</Text>
  <Text Key="509605F3">Now that's a Small Home! Gain increased duration to Happy, Inspired and Focused Buffs. Receive Household Bill Reduction. </Text>
  <Text Key="064D3022">Small Home</Text>
  <Text Key="750981D1">Sweater Threads</Text>
  <Text Key="015AA609">Checked for Vintage</Text>
  <Text Key="2089C9CB">Casually Cool</Text>
  <Text Key="19F6C599">Out and About</Text>
  <Text Key="387E1A10">Now you see it... now you don't! With a contemporary and simplistic design, this murphy bed unit will fit anywhere in your Lot. It comes complete with all parts and hardware ready-to-assemble, in fact it comes pre-assembled for your upmost convenience! Comes also with a shelving unit for your favorite accents. Just be sure to make sure it is securely closed when you need to, we wouldn't want you to have an... unfortunate accident.</Text>
  <Text Key="919EA93F">'Now You See It, Now You Don't' Murphy Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="8F7DB935">For even more spacing saving brownie points. This murphy bed and loveseat combo is move-in ready, take advantage of your space and provide a seating place for your guests as well. All in one go, that's right!\n\nComes with an easy to follow template for building effectively and accurately to avoid incidents. The company does not take responsabilities for faulty assembly, or mismanaged use of upgrades.</Text>
  <Text Key="B29794D0">'Now You See It, Now You Don't' Murphy Bed Loveseat Combo</Text>
  <Text Key="48721E34">Embrace back-cramps and your limbs hanging off on all sides of the mattress with this affordable space saving single bed for one, because it’s not like you have anyone to share it with, anyways.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E699D9B">Space-Saving Single</Text>
  <Text Key="D4A3C47E">Space saving and stylish, spacious storage. Wood polished finish makes this look elegant and put together for any type of Lot style and taste. Its generous storage shelves accommodate all your necessities with ease... even those things you want nobody to see at a moment's notice. This bookcase not only will safeguard your books, but also will look good doing so.</Text>
  <Text Key="B58BEC01">Power Tower Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="0127C168">Do you have a collection of unread books that you said you would read, but just never got around to? Don't let them go to waste - repurpose them for decorative use! Now you can look studious without even having to read a single word. That's what I call true ingenuity!</Text>
  <Text Key="CDED5687">Botanical Bookends</Text>
  <Text Key="A5DE2D46">Clever, but most importantly, compact! Because who needs a lot of desk space? Not you!\n\nDesigned with small spaces and tiny living in mind, this desk will fit in nicely with an eclectic mix of styles. It may look small, but it will hold all your wares out of sight in its tiny little cute drawers, unless of course you decide to leave all your pens everywhere... You do you, we don't judge!</Text>
  <Text Key="B8A1FED9">Tiny Desk... For Tiny Living</Text>
  <Text Key="68D17A9E">The perfect solution for those who value their privacy and also want to add a little intrigue in their lives. This door comes with ALMOST perfectly sized glass sections to give your visitors a sneak peek into your humble abode. A favorite of Welcome Wagons everywhere!</Text>
  <Text Key="7AFA76A1">Just A Little Peek - Door Solution</Text>
  <Text Key="749ADAAD">If you need some drawers to store yours, you can't go wrong with the Power Tower dresser! With a minimalist, and modern wood design, this dresser looks great in any bedroom and is guaranteed to keep all of your ugly sweaters out of sight!</Text>
  <Text Key="FBBDBB78">Power Tower Dresser</Text>
  <Text Key="62468FCA">Contrary to popular belief, size really doesn't matter. Despite it's short stature, the Stubby Cubby offers ample space for all kinds of clothes and miscellaneous knick knacks.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E70DCD5">Stubby Cubby Dresser</Text>
  <Text Key="18886544">Compact and convenient, the Media Marathoner is your one-stop-shop for all things entertainment! Complete with the latest InvisiView Flat Screen television and Samdance Soundbar speaker, experience the most dazzling films, cutting-edge games and that one sitcom from the 90’s that you’ve watched way too many times, in stunning HD with rich, clear sound. Oh, and there’s a shelf to display your books too - y'know, to make it LOOK like you read.</Text>
  <Text Key="B516070B">Media Marathoner</Text>
  <Text Key="50B5CA5C">Shelves are soooo 20th century. Save some space with the Media Marathoner All-on-the-Wall! Is there a practical reason to mount your TV on the wall? No – but it looks cool! Complete with the latest InvisiView Flat Screen television and Samdance Supersound stereo system, bring the best parts of cinema-going experience into your living room.</Text>
  <Text Key="D3428333">Media Marathoner All-on-the-Wall</Text>
  <Text Key="2B27D7E4">When you don't want to go full glam with a chandelier, but you want a nice pendant light fixture to add verticality to your space. Look no further than the DonTripp! It is perfect for illuminating an entryway to grab glances as it greets guests, but can also be used to update a more casual ensemble.\n\nNote: Bulbs included!</Text>
  <Text Key="0811B32B">DonTripp Light Fixture</Text>
  <Text Key="F167C375">A slightly longer version of our critically acclaimed DonTripp. This version is perfect for Lots with a little extra vertical space!\n\nNote: Bulbs are still included. If you need an even longer version, try our DonTripp - Definitely Longer!</Text>
  <Text Key="87BFEE10">DonTripp Light Fixture - Slightly Longer</Text>
  <Text Key="ECCFB2AA">What was that? A longer light fixture? No problem! From the makers of the critically acclaimed DonTripp, comes its even longer version for those really tall corners of the Lot that we are never sure what to do with them. Test the boundaries of Lot verticality, and impress your guests with your style.\n\nNote: Bulbs included, however staircase to help change them is not.</Text>
  <Text Key="0CE9AE35">DonTripp Light Fixture - Definitely Longer</Text>
  <Text Key="95FD17E5">Definitely not your standard floor lamp! This functional design is ideal for maximizing floor space while eliminating the need for a side table and a table lamp, or having just a boring floor lamp. Why not both storage and a lamp? Right?! Its storage space is perfect for catching all figurines and clutter, or carefully planned accents. You can now have it all! Less to haul, more to love!</Text>
  <Text Key="22600F60">'All Included!' Lamp With Storage</Text>
  <Text Key="89A47613">Beautifully crafted table tray for all your favorite items, including your ongoing reading novels, or a snack here and there. This table tray comes pre-styled (extremely convenient) and includes a set of candles for creating the perfect ambiance. Even though this tray is not food safe, it is perfect for showing off decorative items, and at the same time create a space for slowing down and relaxing.</Text>
  <Text Key="8E57A6C2">My Kinda Zen - Not Just A Deco Tray</Text>
  <Text Key="CEB6412B">The desk lamp stopped being just a desk lamp. The S1M0 offers a sleek design and seamless functionality to create an elegant, versatile space. Comes in a variety of colors, lightweight, and extremely portable.\n\nComes with an On/Off switch for your convenience.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A2F732A">S1M0 - The Modern Desk Lamp</Text>
  <Text Key="C5C25EE1">Everyone needs some time to reflect, so here is your opportunity to do so! With the Miracle Mirror, you will never look at yourself in the same way ever again!</Text>
  <Text Key="1B658E94">Miracle Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="19307FA7">Do you enjoy deep and complex pieces of art that challenge the form and stimulate the senses? Well, you won't find that here - but hey, it still looks pretty!</Text>
  <Text Key="6BB588DE">Simple and Clean Art</Text>
  <Text Key="F1B96DD6">Bring some life to your space with a stunning vertical mini garden. This planter mounts securely to the wall and offers an unique, space-saving way to have some green in your life. Comes with the perfect plants that are easy to take care of. Its ingenious irrigation system will measure precisely how much water each pot needs, just add water from the top!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8CC5B89">'Grooowing Up!' Vertical Mini Garden</Text>
  <Text Key="26EA9035">Has life pulled the rug out from underneath you? That's okay, because that old rag was starting to look a little ratty, anyways. You owe it to yourself to buy a new one! With a simplistic, but sleek diamond design, the Contemporary Carpet will modernize even the most outdated of living rooms!</Text>
  <Text Key="78C869D0">Contemporary Carpet</Text>
  <Text Key="9D81B8F6">The perfect solution for small spaces! Store your bath essentials, and even hang your favorite towel! This two-tier open design allows for organization optimization as you can actually see what you store in this shelf... at all times!\n\nComes with template for easy assembly, somewhat pre-assembled, and no tools required... that we know of.</Text>
  <Text Key="A16F5829">'No Item Left Behind' Tiered Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="D387B07E">A new classic in modern decorating! This open tiered shelf is perfect for any kitchen that would benefit from a bit of extra storage space. Store your regular use items in this easy to reach shelving system that will save you the agony of spending hours looking for that teapot in every cabinet.</Text>
  <Text Key="96DBF001">'It Should Be There' Open Shelf</Text>
  <Text Key="016F9AC3">Beautiful space saving piece for any bathroom enthusiast! The Sinkz is an all in one piece unit that includes an integrated sink prepared for a single-hole faucet, no complicated assembly required... but we would hire a professional, just in case. Its open storage allows for easy access of your toiletries or any essential in your life.</Text>
  <Text Key="61BAEB12">The Sinkz Bathroom Vanity</Text>
  <Text Key="09F0A747">Complements the Orbital High Dining dining table perfectly. This chair offers not only timeless appeal and sophistication, but also comfort and stability. Designed with generous sitting for long meals or for relaxing in an easy, effortless way.</Text>
  <Text Key="48CFBCFE">Not Quite Orbital Sitting</Text>
  <Text Key="A30F7E2A">Love the Lovely Dining Chair. While this matches the Lovely set of furniture, this chair has its own personality to style a room by itself. Use it as a dining chair or a chair for your guests, or for yourself to just sit and relax. So plush and sophisticated that it can be seen as a piece or art.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4A038B5">Lovely Dining Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="A1F32B0E">We know you love seats! But do you really, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt;, love seats? Then this chair is also for you! From the makers of the Lovely Loveseat comes this modern armchair that takes comfort to new levels with its deep seat and somewhat slopped arms. It lovely complements the Lovely Loveseat and it will make you feel cozy from the get go!\n\nMade to order, so you can be assured that it is quality seating. So have a seat love!</Text>
  <Text Key="32175A31">Lovely Armchair</Text>
  <Text Key="33037577">Do you love seats? Then you will love the seat on this loveseat. We just hope that you love this loveseat as much as this loveseat loves you - so please take a seat, love.</Text>
  <Text Key="365A94CE">Lovely Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="44E73BAF">No table is complete without coffee and no coffee is complete without a table, since coffee is unable to float...unless?</Text>
  <Text Key="55D7DFF6">Sir Cumference Coffee Table</Text>
  <Text Key="DC2269F5">Retro inspired, but never will look outdated. The glass top allows the table to be admired from every possible view. Perfect for small dining rooms, spacious enough for four Sims to enjoy a meal and deep conversations.</Text>
  <Text Key="0CAA1990">Orbital High Dining</Text>
  <Text Key="0AAE0C89">In a pouffe of magic this lovely and elegant footstool appears!</Text>
  <Text Key="B325A6EC">Modern Pouffe</Text>
  <Text Key="B2D8CF3E">Masterfully blending elements of wood and color, the result is a fantastic versatile piece for your space. It could be a side table, bedside table, or try it in a corner for a functional focal point or where you need a little surface space or small storage.</Text>
  <Text Key="21AE7AC1">Not A Table's End</Text>
  <Text Key="1E089D7D">Sometimes we have to live small, and that is all about compromises. But compromises don't have to be not stylish. With the Tiny Console every piece and every accent makes a difference. Added drawer for those important items that we don't want our visitors to see in surprise visits, and its added bottom shelf allows for easy storage. Pairs nicely with the Tiny Desk... For Tiny Living. Each sold separately!</Text>
  <Text Key="53D263E8">Tiny Console... For Tiny Living</Text>
  <Text Key="321B0964">Tiny bathroom? Not a problem! The great minds at Whenugougo Industries found themselves solving the age of dilemma, a giant toilet in a small space is a thing of the past with this compact and water efficient design that you don't need to sacrifice your style for. This product's flushing system is controlled by a button on the top of the tank that is noiseless when triggered, perfect for those times where you don't want anybody to know where you are.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0998FAB">Compact Lavatory by Whenugougo Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="267A73C1">Oh no! {0.SimName} has been crushed underneath a malfunctioning Murphy Bed! {0.SimFirstName} will be missed...</Text>
  <Text Key="8220D45E">Be Crushed to Death by Murphy Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="65E154CD">Brag About Small Home</Text>
  <Text Key="0AC0FB7D">Brag about &lt;i&gt;really &lt;b&gt;REALLY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Micro Home</Text>
  <Text Key="14CEECAE">Brag about &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; Tiny House</Text>
  <Text Key="1EB187CF">Put Bed Down</Text>
  <Text Key="4D4FDCFC">Put Bed Up</Text>
  <Text Key="EFF75FAF">Spring Loaded</Text>
  <Text Key="99A0FF71">Continue Upgrading Spring Loaded</Text>
  <Text Key="60C442AA">Reinforced Spring Wiring</Text>
  <Text Key="2DCA7FCE">Continue Reinforced Spring Wiring</Text>
  <Text Key="95C7ABEA">Reduces how often the bed will break.</Text>
  <Text Key="136200C3">Infused wire and reinforced springs make the bed unbreakable.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF833EF4">Disturbed Sleep</Text>
  <Text Key="409C4A21">Wake Up and Warn!</Text>
  <Text Key="71583BD0">Possess For Energy</Text>
  <Text Key="CC4C0426">Warn About the Bed Safety</Text>
  <Text Key="938D1D72">Itty-Bitty Bathroom</Text>
  <Text Key="C9846F18">Tiny Living, Big Dreams</Text>
  <Text Key="BDBE0C16">Downsized Den</Text>
  <Text Key="FB5056ED">There’s nothing better than cuddling up with a good book in your cozy bed after a long day’s work. Complete with a marvelous murphy bed sandwiched between two spacious bookshelves, The Snore and Store is perfect for any novel-loving napper.</Text>
  <Text Key="23563CB8">The Snore and Store</Text>
  <Text Key="ACD0F1FF">Bring home the ultimate space-saving Murphy Bed kit on the market with The Schmooze and Snooze. Transform your cozy bedroom into a relaxing lounge in only a matter of minutes. Combining the best-selling “'Now You See It, Now You Don't' Murphy Bed and Loveseat Combo” and "Power Tower Bookcase", the Schmooze and Snooze is the bargain you’ve been waiting for!</Text>
  <Text Key="B105DF26">The Schmooze and Snooze</Text>
  <Text Key="4E5B10D4">Tier 1\nMicro Home</Text>
  <Text Key="4CE3CFCB">Tier 2 - Tiny Home</Text>
  <Text Key="49A4D987">Tier 3 - Small Home</Text>
  <Text Key="4CDC730B">Tier 1 - Micro Home</Text>
  <Text Key="F3A10A24">Tier 2\nTiny Home</Text>
  <Text Key="C61C6503">Tier 3\nSmall Home</Text>
  <Text Key="35B4E039">Too many tiles! 100 is the maximum allowed.</Text>
  <Text Key="5D9C7FFB">You need at least {2.Number} placed tiles; you currently have {0.Number}</Text>
  <Text Key="33C6CB6C">You've placed {0.Number} tiles of {1.Number} for this tier</Text>
  <Text Key="A5870B37">At least 4 tiles are required to start a Tiny Home.\n\nFoundations, Basements, and Decks all count towards the Total Tile Count.</Text>
  <Text Key="E737C8B9">Tier 3 - Small Home</Text>
  <Text Key="B9336AD6">Tier 1 - Micro Home</Text>
  <Text Key="CC61B7CD">Tier 2 - Tiny Home</Text>
  <Text Key="2FD5D3AA">Tiny Home Residential</Text>
  <Text Key="7CB3BA0D">Tiny Home Residential Incomplete</Text>
  <Text Key="EFC7B9F0">Tiny Home Residential - {0.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="84FF3EB5">In Build Mode open the Lot Info Panel and select the Tiny Home Residential under Lot Type to build a Tiny Home and experience unique Lot Perks.</Text>
  <Text Key="5365B2CC">Tiny Homes are a way of life. How small a space can you fit the essentials? There's three progressively difficult goals to challenge yourself; Small, Tiny, and Micro! How low can you go?</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>