<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<STBLKeyStringList>
  <Text Key="E4943697">{0.SimFirstName} has learned all possible potions for their current rank. Practicing magic or experimenting on the cauldron will continue to improve {M0.his}{F0.her} Spellcaster prowess.</Text>
  <Text Key="69F891B6">{0.SimFirstName} already knows every potion recipe. Experiment will provide Spellcaster XP, as well a chance to gain potion ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="62EE7954">Through fizzle fazzle and all the dazzle, {0.SimFirstName}'s experiments with the cauldron has yielded fruitful results!\n\n{0.SimFirstName} has gained:\n{1.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="0E8CBF78">{0.SimFirstName} failed to craft their potion, but not all is lost. They were able to bottle up\n1 Potion of Questionable Contents.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F0C5778">{0.SimFirstName} has learned a new potion recipe and has found a sample.\n\n1 {1.String} has been added to {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="4083BFA8">{0.SimFirstName} has been taught a new potion recipe and has been given a sample.\n\n1 {1.String} has been added to {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="E885CB81">(From Potion of Alluring Aura)</Text>
  <Text Key="A9EEF88E">(From Potion of Prompt Resurrection)</Text>
  <Text Key="5D4AF318">(From Potion of Questionable Contents)</Text>
  <Text Key="74F85316">Is that bacon-scented deodorant you're wearing? I think I'm in love with you...</Text>
  <Text Key="871C4D7F">My psychic told me to avoid Sims like you. Please stay away from me.</Text>
  <Text Key="4914AE91">Are you my long-lost BFF from a while back?  No? Oh well, let's be BFFs anyway!</Text>
  <Text Key="E811904A">I don't understand why, but I'm pretty sure we're best friends now!</Text>
  <Text Key="39FBC045">Ooooh, you have a really nice shouting voice! Wanna be my best friend?</Text>
  <Text Key="4E55270D">All that shouting really made my heart flutter! I... I love you!</Text>
  <Text Key="D63744B4">That's not nice. You're a meanie.</Text>
  <Text Key="52675494">My mother was right, I should have un-friended you a long time ago!</Text>
  <Text Key="27F0ACD7">Your attempt at romance was not the worst I have seen. Perhaps we are destined to be just friends.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0314C67">I'm going to be honest, that showing of affection was pretty terrible. Try harder next time, okay?</Text>
  <Text Key="DCAAAE87">You're not too bad. Just kidding, you're cool. Just kidding, I love you!</Text>
  <Text Key="C61BC2C1">You make my heart flutter! This is either an issue I should seek medical help for, or I'm in love with you!</Text>
  <Text Key="814A7249">(From Potion of Immortality)</Text>
  <Text Key="58972B53">{0.SimFirstName} now has the Immortal trait and can no longer die of old age.</Text>
  <Text Key="A974EA16">(From Potion of Good Fortune)</Text>
  <Text Key="EB61378C">(From Potion of Magical Aura)</Text>
  <Text Key="2D6DC8C9">(From Potion of Emotional Stability)</Text>
  <Text Key="F425BF0C">(From Potion of Emotional Stability)</Text>
  <Text Key="75EC03C4">(From Potion of Emotional Stability)</Text>
  <Text Key="9CEE62C8">(From Potion of Nausea)</Text>
  <Text Key="1B7FEFC9">{0.SimFirstName} doesn't have any curses to remove.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0F960D9">{0.SimFirstName} has cleared their mind of all their previous teachings. {0.SimFirstName} may now select different perks.</Text>
  <Text Key="A21D6468">(From Potion of the Nimble Mind)</Text>
  <Text Key="3C02B6B1">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="9B301597">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of the Duelist while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="8287C906">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Infectious Laughter while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="C7E4283F">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of the Night Wraith while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="6B379FDE">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Unwarranted Hostility while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="09299B45">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Repulsiveness while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="A954DC79">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncleansable Stench while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="986A89AE">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Awkward Embraces while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="4D9C2688">Backfire! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge while trying to remove another curse!</Text>
  <Text Key="73585360">{0.SimName} got the Curse of the Duelist from losing too many Duels.</Text>
  <Text Key="E0567497">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Unwarranted Hostility from losing too many Duels.</Text>
  <Text Key="91D60D23">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Awkward Embraces from losing too many Duels.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3AC3DD6">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge from letting the Spellcaster Power Explode!</Text>
  <Text Key="94FA3CB2">{0.SimName} got the Curse of the Night Wraith from letting the Spellcaster Power Explode!</Text>
  <Text Key="B25624AF">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Scrambled Spells from letting the Spellcaster Power Explode!</Text>
  <Text Key="21EC2123">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge from overcharging so many times.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDE86548">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Infectious Laughter from overcharging so many times.</Text>
  <Text Key="CE2B1DDF">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncleansable Stench from drinking too many potions.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C6A0CB0">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Awkward Embraces from drinking too many potions.</Text>
  <Text Key="F675C971">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Unwarranted Hostility from failing to make a potion.</Text>
  <Text Key="30D93B36">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Repulsiveness from failing to make a potion.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0E2E088">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncleansable Stench from failing to make a potion.</Text>
  <Text Key="27517763">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="1D111B27">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of the Duelist while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE82C488">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Infectious Laughter while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="8835662F">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Night Wraith while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="04AFD252">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Unwarranted Hostility while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="51F08667">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Repulsiveness while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="02935185">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncleansable Stench while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="9804AD56">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Awkward Embraces while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6AB7500">Oops! {0.SimName} got the Curse of Scrambled Spells while drinking {1.ObjectName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="26C64BA4">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Uncontrollable Charge from failing spell casting too many times.</Text>
  <Text Key="27D2EE94">{0.SimName} got the Curse of Scrambled Spells from failing spell casting too many times.</Text>
  <Text Key="C494F91A">{0.SimName} is overcome by a strong magical force as all of the the negative energy leaves their body. {0.SimName} has successfully removed all their curses!</Text>
  <Text Key="2B8075C7">{0.SimName} found a {1.String} while out foraging.  It has been placed into the household's inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="8AE39875">{0.SimFirstName}'s familiar has brought back some exciting magical goods: {1.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="A85FEED4">Your familiar has protected you from death. Be more careful in the near future; death does not like to be cheated twice. Your familiars may not be able to protect you for awhile.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFEA4614">Hey! A new spell, great!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7A56431">{0.SimFirstName} found a tome:\n{1.ObjectName}</Text>
  <Text Key="02233382">{0.SimFirstName} has discovered a new spell: {1.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="5A9839AA">{0.SimName} is not a high enough Spellcaster rank to read this tome. Keep practicing magic and building your prowess.</Text>
  <Text Key="0CDEF021">{0.SimFirstName} tried valiantly to make sense of these mystic runes, but alas, only a Spellcaster can read this magical tome!</Text>
  <Text Key="7D72089B">{0.SimFirstName} has learned all possible spells for their current rank. Practicing magic or experimenting on the cauldron will continue to improve {M0.his}{F0.her} Spellcaster prowess.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9F08CDF">(From Burgliate Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="31C4741D">{1.SimFirstName} is now a Spellcaster. You can view {F1.her}{M1.his} Spellbook by opening {F1.her}{M1.his} perks panel, or by clicking on the button in this window.</Text>
  <Text Key="6436CEBE">{0.SimFirstName} is now a Spellcaster. You can view {F0.her}{M0.his} Spellbook by opening {F0.her}{M0.his} perks panel, or by clicking on the button in this window.</Text>
  <Text Key="C276F727">Your prowess in the magical arts is gaining recognition. A Magical Care Package is sent to every Acolyte containing some everyday essentials for an up-and-coming Spellcaster. Be sure to check your mailbox!</Text>
  <Text Key="329A39DB">(From the Magical Sage)</Text>
  <Text Key="68BC3114">{1.SimFirstName} is no longer a Spellcaster.</Text>
  <Text Key="43EB31C6">(From Spellcaster Ranking Up)</Text>
  <Text Key="39BB0C45">{0.SimFirstName} has discovered a new potion recipe and has bottled up a sample.\n\n1 {1.String} has been added to their inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A49692B">The Luck of The Spellcaster is with {0.SimFirstName}.\n{0.SimFirstName} found\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="F1530374">It's always refreshing to clean up. Plus, {0.SimFirstName} found something in the drain. \n{2.String}\n\n How lucky!\n</Text>
  <Text Key="536F229B">The bubbling magic of the cauldron reveals an unexpected gift.\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="143E15FD">What's the best thing about gathering collectables, {0.SimFirstName}? Probably finding extra loot!\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="4612D764">It's that classic "Waiter, there's something in my {1.ObjectName}" situation for {0.SimFirstName}. Only instead of an insect,it's something useful. Check out this haul!\n\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="129F9AE3">If {0.SimFirstName} was a pirate, these {2.Money} would be an incredible haul. Unfortunately, those days are in {0.SimFirstName}'s past.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6ED001F">Free simoleons? Why yes, {2.Money} free simoleons.</Text>
  <Text Key="FA2D5AEC">Lucky day! {0.SimFirstName} just found {2.Money}!</Text>
  <Text Key="A3D98D8E">There's no better feeling than finding lost simoleons! {0.SimFirstName} just found {2.Money}!</Text>
  <Text Key="51E0885E">{2.Money} Simoleons is nothing to shake a stick at. Why would {0.SimFirstName} shake a stick at found Simoleons anyway? What purpose would that serve? They're Simoleons, they can't be intimidated.</Text>
  <Text Key="894A42AB">Mopping the floor is usually monotonous, but not today! Look what {0.SimFirstName} just found in the dust and grit!\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="D02F96BF">Hey! I was cleaning my house and ran across a spare box of collectibles. I'm sure that you could use this for something.\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="64C1BA15">Here's a fish for you to hold in your pockets. I hope that it doesn't get really smelly in there.\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="EB81EAC1">I'd love to offer you a small token of my affection. Please take this and know that I care for you deeply.\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="91763352">What's that nibbling at {0.SimFirstName}'s toes?\n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="9A715686">Potion of Curse Cleansing failed, nothing happened.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F168A9E">{0.SimName} won the Magic Duel and received {2.Money} for being a worthy opponent.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED04D0B9">{0.SimName} won the Magic Duel and got: \n{2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="F6065D6D">Even in victory, the Curse of the Duelist prevents a Spellcaster from gaining significant rewards.</Text>
  <Text Key="A54ED31B">(From A Potion With Extra Chemistry)</Text>
  <Text Key="0F3820B0">First Steps</Text>
  <Text Key="011AE63B">Learning the Ways</Text>
  <Text Key="81AD7EB2">Devilish Dueler</Text>
  <Text Key="ADC9459D">Wand-erful Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="DEB0A0C1">First Steps</Text>
  <Text Key="ED98F9CA">Bubbling Up</Text>
  <Text Key="82AD9D53">Cauldron Concoctions</Text>
  <Text Key="9A90CD54">Potion Pro</Text>
  <Text Key="C7A9983B">The hours of hard work have paid off as the power of the Realm now courses through the veins of {0.SimFirstName}. Marshal your powers well.\n\nTrait Earned: Slinger of Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="07DEA353">This Sim craves a deep knowledge of the arcane magical arts.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCFC4C4F">Spellcraft &amp; Sorcery</Text>
  <Text Key="F7BA2634">{0.SimFirstName} really is a potions expert now. This advanced knowledge has given {M0.him}{F0.her} an edge and potions will almost never fail when {M0.he}{F0.she} consumes them {M0.himself}{F0.herself}.\n\nTrait Earned: Master Mixer</Text>
  <Text Key="43E4FD04">This Sim wants to learn every potion's recipe and craft each one!</Text>
  <Text Key="2624F470">Purveyor of Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="210B2BD4">Spectral Reach</Text>
  <Text Key="D012962B">Sim can now cast long distances (without having to move closer to the target). Also, Sims no longer know who cast the spell on them so they won't react negatively to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF966EB1">Mix Master</Text>
  <Text Key="8D6397B6">Extra servings will be in the Cauldron each time a potion is successfully created.</Text>
  <Text Key="8C6AC010">Blender Arm</Text>
  <Text Key="8FDA2F5F">Potion crafting speed significantly increased.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A0B8072">A Little Extra Chemistry</Text>
  <Text Key="F6EB2D3D">Potions crafted by this Sim are surprisingly tasty and have an additional small benefit triggered when the potion is consumed.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF46161D">Frugal Combination</Text>
  <Text Key="C281162A">Chance on potion creation that all of the required ingredients will not be used.</Text>
  <Text Key="A72A3E79">Hexproof</Text>
  <Text Key="C867423E">Sim is now protected from Curses.</Text>
  <Text Key="530AA1DC">Insightful Eye</Text>
  <Text Key="49DE93F3">Research, experiment, and tome reading speeds are all greatly increased.</Text>
  <Text Key="F17BE5B7">Knowledge Is Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="106D3CB0">Sim reads and does computer research at a faster rate. These interactions also provide Magical experience over time.</Text>
  <Text Key="E516E2B8">Master Caster</Text>
  <Text Key="6F779B47">Casting spells no longer fails when the Sim is in a Normal Spellcaster Charge range, Backfires are greatly reduced in Charged and Overcharge states.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A679433">Incredible Forager</Text>
  <Text Key="2AA79814">This Sim now receives more items when harvesting magical ingredients in the Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="4FBE6223">Experimenter</Text>
  <Text Key="95039064">When experimenting and practicing, Sim gains experience faster with less failures.</Text>
  <Text Key="D432E468">Spellcaster Socialite</Text>
  <Text Key="C149E8D7">Unlock Magical social interactions with other Spellcasters that will provide some Spellcaster XP.</Text>
  <Text Key="19F213BE">Mischief Master</Text>
  <Text Key="E6BDFB71">Mischief Spells &amp; Potions always succeed when Sim is in a Normal Spellcaster Charge range, Failure is greatly reduced in Charged and Overcharge states.</Text>
  <Text Key="12ABA183">Tame the Untameable</Text>
  <Text Key="F0BF33C4">Untamed Spells &amp; Potions always succeed when Sim is in a Normal Spellcaster Charge range, Failure is greatly reduced in Charged and Overcharge states.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB1F63AE">Practiced Practicality</Text>
  <Text Key="BBDDF001">Practical Spells &amp; Potions always succeed when Sim is in a Normal Spellcaster Charge range, Failure is greatly reduced in Charged and Overcharge states.</Text>
  <Text Key="69E8145F">Natural Mentor</Text>
  <Text Key="38FD7F58">Increased relationship and skill gains when training or experimenting with other Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D90BB84">Magical Discounts</Text>
  <Text Key="C7F515BB">Sim receives a 50% discount on all purchases from the market stalls in The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="3CCD8E56">Potent Potables</Text>
  <Text Key="CE2BC929">Effects on all potions are increased and/or last significantly longer. Sim can now Hex their Potions to have them always fail.</Text>
  <Text Key="82474553">Power Shunt</Text>
  <Text Key="0DEC7C34">Casting a spell now adds significantly less Spellcaster Charge.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FD417B4">Mote Hound</Text>
  <Text Key="01B07A8B">Sim can now always see Magical Motes and collect them. Motes can be consumed for experience and minor, random motive boosts.</Text>
  <Text Key="C37997A3">Charge Control</Text>
  <Text Key="889C9DE4">All Spellcaster Charge increases are reduced</Text>
  <Text Key="324C6962">Magical Resonance</Text>
  <Text Key="89A1C28D">While in The Magic Realm, the Sim is extremely powerful. They are protected by Death from Overload and can more freely Build Charge and Discharge their Spellcaster Charge levels. Also increased success chance of potion making, drinking and spellcasting.</Text>
  <Text Key="D6705296">Discharge</Text>
  <Text Key="C1F4DC69">This Sim can now cast Discharge which empties Spellcaster Charge.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D8BE81A">Master Duelist</Text>
  <Text Key="4AA1F2A5">This Sim has significantly increased chances of winning a duel and reaps better rewards from them.</Text>
  <Text Key="79BED44C">Friendship Forcer</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E750EE">Every Sim will want to be my friend now... hopefully?</Text>
  <Text Key="8626762D">Every Sim will want to be my friend now!</Text>
  <Text Key="D776EC5F">{0.SimFirstName} tried to cheat the Reaper and failed. The Reaper will not spare {0.SimFirstName} if they die anytime soon.</Text>
  <Text Key="BA283C06">Irredeemable</Text>
  <Text Key="D8C3483C">Death is no longer the end for {0.SimFirstName}! {M0.He}{F0.She} may fall down, but {M0.he}{F0.she}'ll get up again and again and again.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0418493">Death-Proof</Text>
  <Text Key="6CE6C9E1">Drinking the product of failure ensures history's mistakes are not repeated.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A40DF94">Learning From Mistakes</Text>
  <Text Key="65E0E69C">Insults at the Ready</Text>
  <Text Key="5DFE83FE">{0.SimFirstName} seems to be ready to be the most hated Sim in town... Well, we hope {M0.he}{F0.she} is prepared for it anyway...</Text>
  <Text Key="FCDE61FD">{0.SimFirstName} is unfazed by being the most hated Sim in town. Bring it!</Text>
  <Text Key="01E266D0">The pursuit of immortality is full of failures and accidents. Luckily, it looks like this will pass in a while. Try to enjoy your phantasmal existence while you can.</Text>
  <Text Key="E47CE8FF">Ghastly Consequences</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9CB90A">Using The Power of Love will make any Sim fall in love with me... right?</Text>
  <Text Key="8351BC15">Power of Love</Text>
  <Text Key="92ABAEB9">Now {0.SimFirstName} should be able to make any Sim fall in love with {M0.him}{F0.her}! Completely irresistible!</Text>
  <Text Key="A87A9D6F">Feeling lucky? Sims will gain random ingredients or money from Experimenting on the Cauldron and performing other household interactions.</Text>
  <Text Key="E6F38CB6">Luck of the Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="7899B306">Luck Results Always Money</Text>
  <Text Key="7D5F714B">Luck Results Always Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="9B2685C6">Was that 5 apples or 6 apples? Best not do anything risky for a while.</Text>
  <Text Key="E002A059">Do You Feel Lucky?</Text>
  <Text Key="FAB0EABA">Something was a bit off with that Magical Aura Potion. It looks like it stopped working part way through...</Text>
  <Text Key="25B2D465">Aura of Failure</Text>
  <Text Key="998382E9">An aura of magic courses through {0.SimFirstName} veins.</Text>
  <Text Key="D3345ECC">Magic Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="A2838087">Something went horribly wrong! The amount of emotions {0.SimFirstName} is feeling is overwhelming!</Text>
  <Text Key="EF8C053E">Emotional Overload</Text>
  <Text Key="06329ACD">A clear mind is a happy mind!</Text>
  <Text Key="B6FDB518">Clear Minded</Text>
  <Text Key="AD68C77B">Pheromone Cloud</Text>
  <Text Key="398D2B6B">{0.SimFirstName} is releasing pheromones into the world, but they may not be well received...</Text>
  <Text Key="32AFF3A4">{0.SimFirstName} has released pheromones out into the world that Sims cannot resist.</Text>
  <Text Key="2D5F77D5">Make it stop! Make it stop... I don't wanna, I don't wanna. Who wants chowder?!</Text>
  <Text Key="77812DF0">Poisoned</Text>
  <Text Key="446E2A8C">{0.SimFirstName}'s mind is empty, but not quite the way they expected.</Text>
  <Text Key="F5E31F43">Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="617ACF68">{0.SimFirstName} will learn skills much faster as long as this potion effect is active.</Text>
  <Text Key="70BD2087">Skill Boost</Text>
  <Text Key="1F7A5016">{0.SimFirstName} is going to have a hard time building skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="B25DDEC9">Uninspired</Text>
  <Text Key="BA2B558F">{0.SimFirstName} is being stalked by something really creepy, {M0.He}{F0.She} should stay as far away from it as possible</Text>
  <Text Key="38991A56">It's Chasing Me!</Text>
  <Text Key="C51C8BC3">Your face has become horrific! Socializing will be much harder and nearby Sims will be disgusted by your presence.</Text>
  <Text Key="0C9CEE12">Magical Repulsiveness</Text>
  <Text Key="CDAAC1F4">It's a good thing this horrible face is only temporary... right??</Text>
  <Text Key="B085405B">Hideous Visage</Text>
  <Text Key="ED4BFBCD">{0.SimFirstName}'s familiar fills {M0.him}{F0.her} with confidence. Familiars make your magic more potent and offer a protection from death that is still not fully understood.</Text>
  <Text Key="9A9A0818">Active Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="3523E932">Being defeated in a magic duel is one of the most frustrating things for any Spellcaster. Keep practicing magic to have a better chance at winning duels.</Text>
  <Text Key="98BD66CD">Agony and Defeat</Text>
  <Text Key="BF35A01B">{0.SimFirstName} sees victory's face...{M0.He}{F0.She} then realized it was {M0.him}{F0.her}.</Text>
  <Text Key="8714A0FA">It Was All Skill</Text>
  <Text Key="DA3F026A">{0.SimFirstName} has become frozen, cannot somehow let go. Hopefully it doesn't bother {M0.him}{F0.her} too much anyway when {M0.he}{F0.she} defrosts.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F166AF5">Chilling...literally.</Text>
  <Text Key="81DEF561">A sudden urge to fight overcomes {0.SimFirstName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="4DF28A14">Fist of Fury?</Text>
  <Text Key="B28360A7">Fire -exclamation point- Fire -exclamation point-</Text>
  <Text Key="55C65BDE">Burning, Burning, Burning!</Text>
  <Text Key="5DE9587E">Brr! It's cold in here. I said there must be some magic in the atmosphere...BRR!</Text>
  <Text Key="99806801">Chilled</Text>
  <Text Key="24C012D8">So... cold... can't... move!</Text>
  <Text Key="7A8E5A57">Frozen!</Text>
  <Text Key="9A3C0EDD">There must be a lot of static in the air, that was a serious jolt!</Text>
  <Text Key="E0A57EC8">Zip Zap Zippidy Zam</Text>
  <Text Key="8C1AD67B">Pierced by cupid's arrow? This surely feels a bit different.</Text>
  <Text Key="75F30ADA">Cupids Touch</Text>
  <Text Key="AE449468">Must obey...</Text>
  <Text Key="0CF55F87">Minionized</Text>
  <Text Key="A9991622">Wait... what was I doing?</Text>
  <Text Key="0F4ED79D">Foggy Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="8B88FA72">{0.SimFirstName} has been objectified!</Text>
  <Text Key="A063990D">Objectified!</Text>
  <Text Key="9CB9234B">Guess its true what they say... Never cross the streams.</Text>
  <Text Key="AEABC8CA">Now Who To Call?</Text>
  <Text Key="F6F8607B">A wave of sadness washes over {0.SimFirstName} for no apparent reason.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC2188DA">Sudden Despair</Text>
  <Text Key="F71D8058">It is never good getting caught Burgliating things.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB7D65EA">Nothing is more thrilling than Burgliating objects from others.</Text>
  <Text Key="29D53D75">Spectacular Steal</Text>
  <Text Key="70662905">While Mote Sight is active you can find and collect floating Motes in The Magic Realm. Keep an eye out for them!</Text>
  <Text Key="1D2AB400">Temporary Mote Sight</Text>
  <Text Key="D6C22150">Spellcasting is more powerful, but success chance is slightly decreased. There's also the possibility of becoming cursed so cast carefully!</Text>
  <Text Key="B2E2107F">Charged</Text>
  <Text Key="68C26C89">Overcharged - Magic is even more powerful. Success chance is moderately decreased. Curse chances are increased</Text>
  <Text Key="E674C6EC">Overcharged</Text>
  <Text Key="2267AEB9">Final state of Spellcaster Charge. Great power, but also a greater chance of failure or death by overload. </Text>
  <Text Key="5EC66DBC">Dangerously Overcharged</Text>
  <Text Key="84044C1E">Due to overmaxing, your chance of successful Spellcasting and Potion making is increased. Conversely, your chance of Death by Overload is reduced.</Text>
  <Text Key="8EEF3321">My Power Grows</Text>
  <Text Key="CB6DA2F9">A nearby Spellcaster is Dangerously Overcharged. No one is feeling very comfortable around them.</Text>
  <Text Key="838EF5FC">Scared By Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="8EEEB38F">That Sim just exploded?! It's definitely time to book it!</Text>
  <Text Key="A628D456">Did They Just Explode?!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D7654F9">{0.SimFirstName} has been channeling too much magic and have paid the price. Tone it down or risk Death by Overload!</Text>
  <Text Key="0D866BFC">Magical Overload</Text>
  <Text Key="E4FCB814">Mmmmm, that potion was one tasty beverage.It went down smooth and delicious. The Little Extra Chemistry perk definitely came in handy.</Text>
  <Text Key="7EA030FB">Surprisingly Tasty Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="235443FB">I'm a level 3 fire mage in my role-playing group!</Text>
  <Text Key="84C38E58">Give me a wand and a spellbook and I'll show you magic.</Text>
  <Text Key="32AC5D9D">I believe in science, thank you very much.</Text>
  <Text Key="EFC7D462">Do you believe in magic?</Text>
  <Text Key="3EA8F863">This smartly designed ceiling rail brings style to any room, while preventing swarms of pixies from getting caught in your ceiling fan or rafters. Save the pixies without sacrificing style!</Text>
  <Text Key="7C072D32">Pixie Saver Ceiling Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="BC111BE5">Use Cauldron</Text>
  <Text Key="8696CC8E">Use Cauldron</Text>
  <Text Key="5E180738">Don't Use Cauldron</Text>
  <Text Key="3B47A46E">Cast Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="1EF3FB65">Cast Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="9F9E6EF5">Don't Cast Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="DFB1A4F5">Warlock Bixby Beetlestone first conjured this column in the early 1600s while trying to conjure dinner. After several unsuccessful attempts, Beetlestone's spouse took care of dinner and Beetlestone was demoted to taking out the trash. It's a very posh column, though.</Text>
  <Text Key="902CDA90">Conjured Column</Text>
  <Text Key="2497E6F2">I hear you have been building your magical prowess. Would you like to put it to the test and duel me at the dueling grounds?</Text>
  <Text Key="B74F3C9B">You're cursed?! Oh no!</Text>
  <Text Key="B74F3C98">Eek! You’ve been cursed!</Text>
  <Text Key="B74F3C99">You got cursed! Are you okay?</Text>
  <Text Key="4EF8D15B">Over the ages I have seen many a curse. This one could be serious. Do not gamble with your well being.</Text>
  <Text Key="D5A4EBFB">Hey listen! You should be more careful! You don't want more curses do you?</Text>
  <Text Key="F8F06C44">You’re cursed? I feel your pain. How do you think I became like this? I wasn’t always a frog, you know.</Text>
  <Text Key="5CC9F6C5">Oh noes! Are you hurt? Are you okay? Oink, how bad is that curse?</Text>
  <Text Key="2707BA7E">Curses build character. Now you have a chance to learn.</Text>
  <Text Key="BDF45365">Your curse is only a temporary setback, you will rise again.</Text>
  <Text Key="20CBEDE6">A curse? Tread lightly. Where the carcass is, the ravens will collect together.</Text>
  <Text Key="23022E1F">Cursed! Serves you right for messing around like that.</Text>
  <Text Key="23022E1C">You got a curse, nya nya nya! Hahahahaha!</Text>
  <Text Key="23022E1D">I knew you shouldn’t have done that. Now you’re cursed. Oh well, maybe it’ll be an improvement.</Text>
  <Text Key="03D041CF">You’ve been cursed. If one is not careful with the arcane, one must face the consequences.</Text>
  <Text Key="03D041CC">Curses build character. Use yours as a way to learn something about yourself.</Text>
  <Text Key="15891954">Hey, that’s my job! Don’t take all the good curses!</Text>
  <Text Key="15891957">Getting cursed is my job! What do you think you’re doing?</Text>
  <Text Key="156AFFC2">Thank goodness that curse is gone!</Text>
  <Text Key="156AFFC1">Phew! Glad you’re finally rid of that curse.</Text>
  <Text Key="00700F17">Exquisite. I no longer smell the scent of curse upon you. You have done well to remove it.</Text>
  <Text Key="C432508A">Oh thank the Watcher! You’ve removed that curse. I was so worried.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5BD5A2">Nice! You removed the curse. Can you remove warts too?</Text>
  <Text Key="635E13AA">Oh thank the Oinker. You’ve removed that nasty curse. Oink!</Text>
  <Text Key="30353BC7">I hope you’ve learned something from having that curse.</Text>
  <Text Key="2B5D659C">The curse is gone, this is the beginning of the new you!</Text>
  <Text Key="B564925F">Curse removal has fared well for thee. Beware future transgressions so as not to repeat history.</Text>
  <Text Key="E59E638E">Getting rid of the curse? That’s no fun!</Text>
  <Text Key="E59E638D">Your curse is gone? Aww. Hopefully you’ll get another soon. Hehehehe!</Text>
  <Text Key="E59E638C">Good for you; you got rid of that curse. Next time maybe don’t get cursed in the first place. Just a thought.</Text>
  <Text Key="AB7E9C6E">Your curse is gone? The universe has blessed you!</Text>
  <Text Key="4FCA99E3">Getting rid of the curse? That’s no fun!</Text>
  <Text Key="4FCA99E0">Your curse is gone? Aww. Let me know if you want it back!</Text>
  <Text Key="8C593ADB">Not your best duel. Better luck next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB77A6F3">Looks like you could use a little dueling practice.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB77A6F2">Well, not every duel can be a win, right?</Text>
  <Text Key="CB77A6F5">You lost that duel, but you can get ‘em next time!</Text>
  <Text Key="3E92630A">Don’t give up so easily, you need to wake the dragon when you duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="9BA70B34">Hey, listen up! Duel harder next time!</Text>
  <Text Key="C959DD8C">Don’t let a loss get you down. You’ve gotta hop up, dust yourself off, and keep on keepin’ on.</Text>
  <Text Key="4935C5AC">It was pretty batty of you to think you could win that duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="557B3699">Next time, maybe think a bit more about whooooo you duel.</Text>
  <Text Key="9F72F356">Don’t let defeat discourage you. Success will rise from the flames of failure.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0B23D1D">You lost that duel?! The croaking raven doth bellow for revenge! Get them next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="84BFFBC0">Hahaha! You really blundered that duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="84BFFBC3">That was a bit weak... You’re going to need to get a lot better if you expect to win duels.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA488E7C">We can learn from defeat. Get up and duel again!</Text>
  <Text Key="AA488E7F">Yawn. Was that a duel or just dull? Your loss was foretold before you even began.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4733045">That looked painful. I like it!</Text>
  <Text Key="D92ED3AF">Nice work, sometimes the stick is more important than the carrot!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB84CB31">Nice dueling, you showed them!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB84CB32">That was a great duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB84CB33">Now THAT was a duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC1C5221">You really burned it up in that duel!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC1C5222">YESSSSS! The heat of battle makes my blood boil in excitement. Masterful dueling!</Text>
  <Text Key="EC1C5223">Congratulations on the dueling win, champion.</Text>
  <Text Key="99A44B75">Hey! I always fret during duels, but I am happy that you won and relieved that you’re safe.</Text>
  <Text Key="4249C519">Ribbit! You won the duel! Your opponent almost croaked!</Text>
  <Text Key="7321466A">That duel had me hopping with excitement!</Text>
  <Text Key="DDFEDA17">Oink! Oink! Yay!</Text>
  <Text Key="5C677798">You showed them whoooo’s boss!</Text>
  <Text Key="18EDEBCF">That duel was fire!</Text>
  <Text Key="18EDEBCC">You have flamed your competition! Good work winning that duel.</Text>
  <Text Key="812424D4">With brawn and mighty brains you have triumphed over your pitiful opponent. You are made to duel.</Text>
  <Text Key="281C6B89">Yes, yes! Destroy your enemies!</Text>
  <Text Key="46662C65">Through the eons of time and memory I have never seen a duel to be so exciting. Congratulations on your win.</Text>
  <Text Key="FAA55C06">That looked painful. I like it!</Text>
  <Text Key="26ED8488">Wow, you’re turning out to be quite the spellcaster! Congrats!</Text>
  <Text Key="26ED848B">Your powers are growing so much faster than I expected! Nice work!</Text>
  <Text Key="26ED848A">You’ve reached a new spellcaster rank! Good job!</Text>
  <Text Key="26ED848D">You’ve reached a new rank, can’t wait to see what spells you learn next!</Text>
  <Text Key="26ED848C">You’re really getting a handle on this magic stuff, I’m impressed!</Text>
  <Text Key="903F5B58">Hey! I see you have moved up the ranks! Can you do anything cool yet?</Text>
  <Text Key="903F5B5B">Great job reaching a new rank. Seriously, that must’ve been super hard. Like, nobody has EVER done that before, eh? For real though, I’m SOOOOO proud.</Text>
  <Text Key="903F5B5A">Well you’re not exactly the chosen one, but good job on the new spellcaster rank I guess.</Text>
  <Text Key="903F5B5D">It’s about plumbin’ time you reached a new rank. Nice plumbin’ job.</Text>
  <Text Key="322C9125">Looks like you're getting a bit hopped up on magic there. Might want to watch out.</Text>
  <Text Key="769B71A7">You’re looking REALLY magical… like, maybe too much? Be careful.</Text>
  <Text Key="769B71A4">Your magic charge is getting pretty strong. Might want to keep an eye on that.</Text>
  <Text Key="769B71A5">I can feel your magic charge from here. Hope you know what you’re doing…</Text>
  <Text Key="CB06319F">Having trouble handling your power? What does that feel like? I wouldn’t know. Perhaps monitor your spellcaster charge more closely.</Text>
  <Text Key="0077CB2F">Listen up! You better watch your magic charge!</Text>
  <Text Key="0077CB2C">Hey! Watch that magic charge of yours!</Text>
  <Text Key="0077CB2D">Listen, please be careful when flexing your magical muscles. Magical charge is nothing to treat so cavalier.</Text>
  <Text Key="29EF1760">Your aura is starting to glow bright like my tail! Watch that magic charge!</Text>
  <Text Key="29EF1763">Mind how much magic charge you try to handle. How many times have I toad you that?</Text>
  <Text Key="668843D1">Oink. Oink? Oink!</Text>
  <Text Key="FD8F4B92">It appears as if your magical energy is potent at the moment, but also wild.</Text>
  <Text Key="A0906979">Don’t flame out! You seem to be ok, but always be aware of your magical energy levels.</Text>
  <Text Key="8CC6409A">Fare thee well, brave spellcaster. Your power is in flux; I can feel it. Be careful how you proceed.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E9414A3">You’ve got a lot of magic charge there. You should go for more!</Text>
  <Text Key="3E9414A0">Let’s see what happens if you get even MORE magically charged. Do it! DO IT!</Text>
  <Text Key="3E9414A1">I can feel the dangerous amount of magic energy you’re emanating. I love danger!</Text>
  <Text Key="1FC061CB">Power is complimented by restraint. Use your magic charge responsibly.</Text>
  <Text Key="1FC061C8">I feel the energies of the stars and skies swirling uncontrollably. Beware your magical charge lest it burn you forever.</Text>
  <Text Key="42C708C8">That potion didn’t quite come out right, did it?</Text>
  <Text Key="42C708CB">Something looks off about that potion.</Text>
  <Text Key="42C708CA">That potion looks weird. Are you sure you know what you’re doing?</Text>
  <Text Key="42C708CD">Looks like you could use a little more potion practice.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8FE1A02">Bah! You botched that potion. How will you add to my hoard if you keep failing!?</Text>
  <Text Key="5E185D7C">Hey! It’s okay that you failed to make that potion. You’ll get it next time. I believe in you.</Text>
  <Text Key="22BC36E5">Ribbit. Where’s the potion? Did it hop out of your hands?</Text>
  <Text Key="83C100C4">Oink. *the leafbat looks really sad that you failed to craft that potion*</Text>
  <Text Key="17FC43C1">Maybe you should seek out someone whoooo knows a bit more about potions before you try to brew another?</Text>
  <Text Key="874DDB2E">Don’t let a mistake discourage you. Success will rise from the flames of failure.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9070A55">You failed to make that potion? Please… nevermore.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0A0EC98">Whoopsie, just a little mistake, no need to lose your head over a spilled potion though. HAHAHAHA!</Text>
  <Text Key="F0A0EC9B">Hahahaha. Well that went terribly (as expected). Nice "potion" there, Merlin.</Text>
  <Text Key="6A9D7E54">You have failed at that potion, but hopefully you have learned. The universe will forgive this.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E5BD25D">What happened to that potion you were trying to make? You've got me on pins and needles here!</Text>
  <Text Key="05C60530">New potion? Nifty, let’s try it out!</Text>
  <Text Key="05C60533">You learned a new potion recipe? You’re so smart!</Text>
  <Text Key="F7B9D64A">Ahhh, a new potion recipe. Knowledge is power and power is wealth. Well done.</Text>
  <Text Key="EA41AB74">Hey, a new potion recipe! Cool!</Text>
  <Text Key="C13DF91D">You’ve learned a new potion recipe? Will that one transform me into royalty?</Text>
  <Text Key="E49914EC">One oinking new potion recipe coming right oinking up!</Text>
  <Text Key="75A7CBD9">It is indeed a wise spellcaster who stocks up on the proper recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0749C96">I’m burning to see what you’ll do with that new potion recipe.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0749C95">Your burning thirst for knowledge is admirable. Congratulations on the new potion recipe.</Text>
  <Text Key="087A915D">Twas a brilliant move to learn that potion recipe. I wonder, pray tell, what the application will yield.</Text>
  <Text Key="02141600">Ooooh, new potion? I hope it’s a nasty one!</Text>
  <Text Key="02141603">Well good for you. You learned something new for a change.</Text>
  <Text Key="B827ABBC">Impressive, your knowledge of the arcane grows deeper.</Text>
  <Text Key="B827ABBF">With every bit of knowledge, you are one step closer to the mysteries of the universe.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8A35585">Does that potion you just learned do icky stuff to people? I hope so!</Text>
  <Text Key="E1280859">*nibble nibble* Mmmm, a potion! Can I chew on it?</Text>
  <Text Key="E128085A">That potion smells terrible. You don’t actually drink that, do you?</Text>
  <Text Key="90DB03DB">That potion looks delicious!</Text>
  <Text Key="90DB03D8">Ohhh, a potion! What are you going to do with it?</Text>
  <Text Key="657A9A9B">A potion? I want it. What is it? I want it. What does it do? I want it.</Text>
  <Text Key="EE77963B">Hey! Nice work on that potion crafting!</Text>
  <Text Key="74B74A84">I hope no frogs were harmed in the brewing of that potion.</Text>
  <Text Key="74B74A87">If you had to use any frogs to brew that potion, I hope I didn’t know them.</Text>
  <Text Key="2C327805">OINK!</Text>
  <Text Key="2C327806">Oink. That potion looks super yummy. I wish I knew how to make one.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A7A14BE">Exactly how many drops of potion does it take to fill to the center of a flask? Let’s count together next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="8453A3A5">Good work on crafting that potion. You must be feeling fired up!</Text>
  <Text Key="F68D3B26">You made a potion? I’m super curious; what’s it taste like?</Text>
  <Text Key="F68D3B25">A potion? I want it. What is it? I want it. What does it do? I want it.</Text>
  <Text Key="3E4F415F">If I had a digestive tract, I’d chug that potion right now!</Text>
  <Text Key="AB50DA0F">So much power in such a tiny bottle. What will you do with that potion?</Text>
  <Text Key="A4992B94">Hey, what kind of potion is that? I hope it’s the kind that does something weird to someone!</Text>
  <Text Key="F48C2779">Yikes! That spell massively backfired. I’m so hoppy it didn’t do anything worse.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECFB">Oh no! Are you okay? That spell backfired!</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECF8">Whoa there, maybe you need a little more spellcasting practice?</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECF9">Yikes! What went wrong with that spell?</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECFE">Whoops, you kinda missed that spell, huh?</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECFF">Whoa! Careful! You almost hit ME with the spell backfire.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE5DECFC">Did you mean to do that or did that spell just totally backfire?</Text>
  <Text Key="68E8155B">Hey! I don’t think that spell was supposed to do that. It’s okay; better luck next time.</Text>
  <Text Key="F729E9A4">Yikes! That spell massively backfired. I’m so hoppy it didn’t do anything worse.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DF395A5">Backfire! It was pretty batty of you to think you could pull that spell off right now.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6195CDE">Whoooo do you think you are, losing control of your spells like that?!</Text>
  <Text Key="B142DDC5">Don’t let a mistake discourage you. Success will rise from the flames of failure.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A49A5C6">It is not weakness to fail, but failed you have. That spell did not work.</Text>
  <Text Key="8A0646FF">Backfire! You should do that with your spells more often!</Text>
  <Text Key="DC6B43AF">The universe is made up of infinite energy. You, however, are not. Pay more attention to your magic charge levels, friend.</Text>
  <Text Key="9FBE4434">Whoah! That spell did NOT do what it was supposed to do! You need better mojo.</Text>
  <Text Key="B67E0949">I love it when you learn new spells!</Text>
  <Text Key="B67E094A">New spells are fun!</Text>
  <Text Key="B67E094B">Oh, neat! Show me your new spell!</Text>
  <Text Key="213F84F9">Knowledge is eternal and the greatest of loot. I know these things from experience. You do well to learn new spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="2ECBAC92">A new spell, eh? Well hop to it and try it out!</Text>
  <Text Key="9D103E4F">OINK! OINK! OINK! I’m so excited you learned a new spell!</Text>
  <Text Key="AD619900">Whooo just got a bit wiser? You, that’s whooooo! Congrats on the new spell!</Text>
  <Text Key="49919447">I’m burning to see what you’ll do with that new spell!</Text>
  <Text Key="49919444">You're smart to learn more spells. I’m impressed with your growing skillset. Don’t let your passion flame out.</Text>
  <Text Key="1E80B04C">You have a raven’s knowledge. Congratulations on learning a new spell.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3C15F01">Nothing like some spell knowledge to fill that empty head of yours.</Text>
  <Text Key="E3C15F02">A new spell? You sure you can handle it?</Text>
  <Text Key="B15B3AFD">Impressive, your knowledge of spellcasting grows deeper.</Text>
  <Text Key="B15B3AFE">With every bit of knowledge, you are one step closer to the mysteries of the universe. Always keep learning!</Text>
  <Text Key="1298DF3E">You learned a new spell? Does that one hurt or help?</Text>
  <Text Key="15B1CC66">Sovereign Mage</Text>
  <Text Key="ECBBE041">Mystical Guardian</Text>
  <Text Key="F9AF8FD3">The Enchantress</Text>
  <Text Key="0F9786F5">Distressed Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="E8E28E95">Arcane Curator</Text>
  <Text Key="024DFF0F">Astral Overseer</Text>
  <Text Key="8A30E9AE">A few friendly fairies are a welcome addition to any magical garden, but an infestation can cause tiny footprints, loud parties and fireballs. This sturdy fence utilizes iron -- a natural fairy repellent! Aesthetically pleasing design keeps hordes of wild fairy pests out of gardens to protect your home.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B716F51">Fae-Away Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="7EED3CDF">Made from melted down fences of previous homes, Phoenix Fences are examples of recycling at its finest. Phoenix Fences: so durable, they'll outlive you!</Text>
  <Text Key="72414586">Phoenix Fence</Text>
  <Text Key="5F3AE696">Bewitching Wood</Text>
  <Text Key="BDC9E05B">Arciform Cobblestone</Text>
  <Text Key="318E89DD">Protector from the Sun, Rain, and the Darkness of the Night.</Text>
  <Text Key="D18DFFC8">Enchanting Awning</Text>
  <Text Key="35CA804D">Over centuries, balconies have performed important roles - this one is not different. Perfect for Spellcasters and Non-Spellcasters to pretend to be star crossed lovers or practicing speeches, maybe even practicing their own spell delivery to the masses!</Text>
  <Text Key="FF2D6D98">Bewitchingly Wicked Balcony</Text>
  <Text Key="17E5D98F">There once was a spellcaster bar: haunted by things most bizarre. Exorcisms were held and the spirits expelled were then banished away in a jar.</Text>
  <Text Key="30F96656">"Don't Open That Jar" Bar</Text>
  <Text Key="F82C6FFE">bassinet_GP08GENwitch Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="A7071681">Spellcaster Bassinet</Text>
  <Text Key="CF8C0878">Beautiful bassinet, in very good vintage condition! It is very sturdy, we promise! Perfect for newborn Spellcasters as they are starting to get in touch with their magical powers.</Text>
  <Text Key="CE406077">Antique Spellcaster Bassinet</Text>
  <Text Key="6FB28774">You can't incant on a poor night's sleep! Retreat from the world into a peaceful night of magical replenishment with this elegant bed.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B3E98DB">Selene's Sanctuary Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="8593D45E">All spellcasters have a third eye: the invisible mind's eye which helps with clairvoyance and links them to a higher consciousness. But is yours getting its recommended eight hours of rest? This bed features a special inlay carving to promote serenity, comfort and serve as a reminder to take care of yourself so you can be at one with the energies of the universe. Includes 300 threadcount sheets!</Text>
  <Text Key="24597761">The Mind's Eye Twin Bed</Text>
  <Text Key="6A95DA1A">All the tricks you could possibly teach your familiar. Too bad they are always so stubborn they never actually listen.</Text>
  <Text Key="C6055F45">1001 Tricks You Can Teach Your Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="E3972FE3">By: U.K. Englishlady\n\nFollow the adventures of young spellcaster, Darley Porter, and her friends Harmony Ginger and Rowan Measley, as they solve the mystery of the shadowy chamber beneath their high school gym.</Text>
  <Text Key="8D653BB2">Darley Porter &amp; The Basement of Shadows</Text>
  <Text Key="DFD829F8">By: Peter K. Dark\n\nThe renowned sci-fi author brings to life a terrifying alternate history where magic never existed.</Text>
  <Text Key="CCA00CF7">A World Without Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="9B5EE399">By: Bro Fiery\n\nAdd a little extra "kick" to your boring, weekday recipes! Magical motes might not be the healthiest (or the most edible) ingredient, but nothing takes a dish from bland to BLAM like a little magic.</Text>
  <Text Key="77F1681C">Cooking With Motes</Text>
  <Text Key="C7EC62EE">By: T.R. Ashy\n\nJulie has always been cold when it comes to showing her feelings, but can a dashing older spellcaster melt her heart? Magic is in the air in the first novel of this forty-three volume romantic series.</Text>
  <Text Key="65FA9491">Wands of Desire</Text>
  <Text Key="12B16307">By: Cornelius J. Implorium\n\nThe history of spellcasting is long and extensive. In this four-thousand page volume, every feat completed and spell casted in the last two-hundred-an... Oh, it doesn't matter, no one is going to read this book.</Text>
  <Text Key="2EB324BE">Famous Spellcasters Throughout History</Text>
  <Text Key="74CE07CC">By: Professor Toot\n\nWhich witch did switch my 'wich?? A bewitching switch does make my eye twitch! </Text>
  <Text Key="74EBB283">Which Witch Bewitched Which Witch?</Text>
  <Text Key="4873D88D">By: Norm Solomon\n\nPhil is a practical spellcaster and Oliver studies mischief. They've been friends since childhood, but can they handle living together? </Text>
  <Text Key="9EBD50D8">Broomies!</Text>
  <Text Key="667E1195">This bookshelf was once owned by spellcaster Francine Ville, a powerful herbalist. It wasn't until years later that her friends discovered Francine had been replaced with a mandrake doppelgänger of her own creation. Ville stored her extensive research of mandrakes in this very bookshelf, then hid it in the basement before running off to Sulani, leaving the mandrake to take over her "regular" life.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC885BB0">Mandrake Bookshelf</Text>
  <Text Key="5B3E3343">Proudly display your affinity for the magical arts with this bookcase, complete with grimwoire collection and power crystal. A built in cloaking spell disguises the bookcase to non-spellcasters, showing them shelves full of finance and budgeting literature.</Text>
  <Text Key="F75A4C92">Spellbound Bookcase</Text>
  <Text Key="51AEA9AE">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a potion that will revive them immediately if they die.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9FEAF51">Tome of Prompt Resurrection</Text>
  <Text Key="F6BE20AA">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a potion that unlocks that power of animosity.</Text>
  <Text Key="10ED9835">Tome of Masterful Insults</Text>
  <Text Key="04412727">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a potion to prevent death from old age.</Text>
  <Text Key="140FE75E">Tome of Immortality</Text>
  <Text Key="67674FD4">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a potion to allow a Sim to remain at their current age.</Text>
  <Text Key="ADF810BB">Tome of Rejuvenation</Text>
  <Text Key="064E8B0E">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a potion to unlock the power of romantic conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="478B7A31">Tome of the Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="1F9C1EF5">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a potion to remove all curses from a Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="890F2890">Tome of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="CF4CD764">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a potion that unlocks the power of friendly conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="124999AB">Tome of Forced Friendship</Text>
  <Text Key="2B3532AF">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a potion that allows a Spellcaster to choose different perks.</Text>
  <Text Key="2AA214F6">Tome of the Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="4E10E711">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a potion to fulfill all of a Sim's needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D76C864">Tome of Plentiful Needs</Text>
  <Text Key="57D88109">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a potion to find helpful items while doing everyday activities.</Text>
  <Text Key="8919DC6C">Tome of Good Fortune</Text>
  <Text Key="5103851C">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a potion that will display a Sims magical aura.</Text>
  <Text Key="5A5EFAF3">Tome of Magical Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="8653FF17">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Neophyte\nTeaches the reader a potion to remove unnecessary emotional baggage.</Text>
  <Text Key="DD65B0EE">Tome of Emotional Stability</Text>
  <Text Key="821A97D3">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Neophyte\nTeaches the reader a potion that makes those around the drinker more receptive to romantic conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1934282">Tome of Alluring Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="D7073750">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a potion to annoy an enemy and turn their stomach.</Text>
  <Text Key="E159727F">Tome of Nausea</Text>
  <Text Key="3CD7E657">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a potion that will increase the speed your Sim's gain skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="746B3F2E">Tome of the Nimble Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="F3E0A2DD">A Tome that contains the teachings of high ranked Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="3986FAC8">Tome for High Ranked Spellcasters</Text>
  <Text Key="92D8AF27">A Tome that contains the teachings of low ranked Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="97AFFF5E">Tome for Low Ranked Spellcasters</Text>
  <Text Key="106BA886">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a Spell to acquire something that doesn't belong to them.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2176319">Tome of Burgliate</Text>
  <Text Key="3390D956">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a Spell to transform a hapless Sim into an inanimate object.</Text>
  <Text Key="4277C609">Tome of Morphiate</Text>
  <Text Key="3479E842">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell that will allow them to scramble Sim's thoughts.</Text>
  <Text Key="415B9B3D">Tome of Deliriate</Text>
  <Text Key="5BD9BBBD">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell that fills a Sim's mind with feelings of intense sadness.</Text>
  <Text Key="9AF87128">Tome of Despairio</Text>
  <Text Key="B4AC63DC">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to convince two Sims to argue and fight with each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D2817B3">Tome of Furio</Text>
  <Text Key="6E527316">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to convince two Sims to get romantic with each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="9C16D7C9">Tome of Infatuate</Text>
  <Text Key="25956EE6">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a Spell to turn one small object into many.</Text>
  <Text Key="95539EF9">Tome of Copypasto</Text>
  <Text Key="3A89AB01">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a Spell to create a fully grown plant in even the most fallow of soils.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE8D7634">Tome of Herbio</Text>
  <Text Key="6DF6D5CE">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a Spell to move instantly to another location, regardless of distance.</Text>
  <Text Key="283D77F1">Tome of Transportalate</Text>
  <Text Key="41669ADC">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a Spell to return to The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="F5030CB3">Tome of Homewardial</Text>
  <Text Key="0A4ACAD9">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to create a tasty meal out of thin air.</Text>
  <Text Key="DEF6AB5C">Tome of Delicioso</Text>
  <Text Key="47104F39">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to help keep your plants healthy and bug free.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC45673C">Tome of Floralorial</Text>
  <Text Key="F4A94631">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell to fix a broken object, or make it higher quality.</Text>
  <Text Key="5CE84F04">Tome of Repairio</Text>
  <Text Key="F38270C0">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell to make something (or someone) squeaky clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="6DAFBB8F">Tome of Scruberoo</Text>
  <Text Key="1EABA3CF">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to create a blast of cold air that freezes anyone it touches.</Text>
  <Text Key="9313D396">Tome of Chillio</Text>
  <Text Key="4E435E27">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a Spell to free yourself from the effects of a magical curse.</Text>
  <Text Key="3142DC5E">Tome of Decursify</Text>
  <Text Key="B4083956">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Master\nTeaches the reader a Spell to restore a ghost to their original physical form.</Text>
  <Text Key="797FE609">Tome of Dedeathify</Text>
  <Text Key="28467569">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Adept\nTeaches the reader a Spell to control another Sim's mind and bend them to your will.</Text>
  <Text Key="74EDAE4C">Tome of Minionize</Text>
  <Text Key="17D40562">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell to instantly incinerate your target with the power or fire.</Text>
  <Text Key="96D539DD">Tome of Inferniate</Text>
  <Text Key="27B5269C">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Acolyte\nTeaches the reader a Spell to summon the dead from their final resting place.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBF72773">Tome of Necrocall</Text>
  <Text Key="26CE97B7">&lt;b&gt;Requires:&lt;/b&gt; Rank Apprentice\nTeaches the reader a Spell to harness electrical energy and give something a jolt.</Text>
  <Text Key="EF48350E">Tome of Zipzap</Text>
  <Text Key="820CB114">Every Spellcaster's dream! Beautifully accented crystals to not only brew excellent potions, but brewing them with style. Show off how good of a Spellcaster you are by having this cauldron in your ritualistic toolkit.</Text>
  <Text Key="94ACCBFB">Cauldron Of Excellency</Text>
  <Text Key="A7207C70">For those Spellcasters that are just starting out! This low budget option is great to start tasting and testing your personal concoctions!\n\nNote: We don't guarantee the quality of the potions you brew with this, we are not sure if it really works, but hey, at least looks the part.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCECEB1F">Paramount Cauldron</Text>
  <Text Key="57F3CE3D">Like all Kingdoms, they all wish to expand. Made of iron from the thrones of kings and queens of old — as its counterpart The Iron Counter, this unit offers significant space gain, without needing to plan a siege to get it.\n\nCounter space was coming... and it was made.</Text>
  <Text Key="50CD20A8">The Iron Counter Island</Text>
  <Text Key="60A4A472">Made of iron from the thrones of kings and queens of old. This unit comes pre-enchanted for all your cooking and storing needs.\n\nWe are not responsible for anything odd happening to anything that gets placed on it though, specially if made with fire and plasma.</Text>
  <Text Key="EEB2770D">The Iron Counter</Text>
  <Text Key="501D5900">Looking for a lighter window treatment? These breezy curtains bring a sprightly bounce to any room. Perfect for the spellcaster who wants to soak up the sun during their morning chant or afternoon sage smudging.</Text>
  <Text Key="9BB645CF">Sprightly Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="49CDCDAA">A lighter, breezy window treatment for larger windows. Bask in the healing nature of the sun while you peruse your favorite spells, or spy on that neighbor you've been trying to hex! The possibilities!</Text>
  <Text Key="69C30F35">Otherwordly Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="F4CDEBE2">Fairy queens have excellent taste, which we're bringing to you at bargain prices! Add a touch of royalty to your home with these elegant curtains -- replicas of what Queen Titania has in her boudoir. There's magic in every stitch!</Text>
  <Text Key="23D9255D">Titania's Curtains</Text>
  <Text Key="4EBB9B8E">Perfect for creatives who are looking for a little spark of inspiration to light the way. This engraved desk harbors an actual will-o'-the-wisp, which are associated with hopes, dreams and goals. Make yours come true!</Text>
  <Text Key="BF4CC3B1">Will-'o-the-Wisp Desk</Text>
  <Text Key="13746CFD">Ancient grimoires tell of a phenomenon where every thirteenth door crafted from the same materials will bring good fortune to its owners each time they pass through it. Doors 1-12 are recycled sustainably.</Text>
  <Text Key="8285BA68">The Thirteenth Door</Text>
  <Text Key="3F129B79">This baronial double door is a replica of one found in a mysterious home in Dragon Valley (or so we are told! Not sure if it is true!). The door opened into oblivion: a void described as existing outside time and space itself. Inside, a single multi-faceted hovering green rhombus. The homeowners no longer let guests inside for fear of destroying the universe. Thankfully, this replica door opens up to whatever you put it in front of. Whew!</Text>
  <Text Key="D023777C">Door to Nowhere</Text>
  <Text Key="7A7C5322">This majestic double door brings serenity to any spellcaster's residence. Smooth, carved sandstone allows passage into a safe haven of magic. Crafted by WiseWitch Inc.</Text>
  <Text Key="CF29FE9D">Lotus Door</Text>
  <Text Key="76B55693">Originally built to hold up entryways in underground crystal mines, this arch can withstand thousands of pounds of surface pressure... or just hold up a second story. A fine specimen in gnomish architectural design!</Text>
  <Text Key="1C1B6042">Gnomish Crystal Arch</Text>
  <Text Key="3ED47E2E">The cackling witch that donated this door said it was "just an ordinary door" and assured everyone there was nothing special about it. She said it's definitely not cursed, vexed, evil, sentient, haunted, and absolutely is not made from hallucinogenic wormwood. What a nice lady!</Text>
  <Text Key="764704D1">Ordinary Door</Text>
  <Text Key="C040CFDE">This enchanted door is rumored to have once possessed the ability to send spellcasters back in time. The enchantment has since worn off, but previous owners have reported hearing distant songs in dead languages emanating from the other side. One owner admits the noise could have been the neighbors affinity for polka music. Investigations remain ongoing.</Text>
  <Text Key="227091E1">Door of Yore</Text>
  <Text Key="3EF5349E">In these drawers lies the answer to your most burning question: what should I wear tomorrow? This fine oak dresser comes pre-enchanted with a special spell that will show you what you were meant to wear. If only all of life was this simple and stylish!</Text>
  <Text Key="52C484A1">Dresser of Divination</Text>
  <Text Key="B02D7161">Spellcaster, divinator, and amateur furniture designer Osman Sparrow was inspired to design this ornate dresser after spilling an entire mug of tea leaves. The leaves showed him an embellished piece with botanical accents, and beautifully swirled carvings reminiscent of the tea itself. Please use coasters and drink tea responsibly!</Text>
  <Text Key="F95D3E14">Spill the Tea Leaves Dresser</Text>
  <Text Key="8D090B19">Consuming this potion will reset all of your Spellcaster's Perk Points. Allowing them to be reassigned.</Text>
  <Text Key="35E0469C">Potion of Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="6D14C85E">Potion of Forced Friendship</Text>
  <Text Key="2BE0EBA3">Potion of Masterful Insults</Text>
  <Text Key="B82583BC">Potion of the Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="90813A31">Potion of Alluring Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="72B1C652">Potion of the Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="D1D46318">Potion of Prompt Resurrection</Text>
  <Text Key="38C476B9">Ensures the next potion your Sim crafts is a guaranteed success. Minor side effects may include...</Text>
  <Text Key="883245BC">Potion of Questionable Contents</Text>
  <Text Key="9DF15B2F">Potion of Plentiful Needs</Text>
  <Text Key="01D5D0D3">Potion of Magical Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="E56DD045">Potion of Immortality</Text>
  <Text Key="F1C47C4F">Potion of Rejuvenation</Text>
  <Text Key="09B7D087">Potion of Good Fortune</Text>
  <Text Key="70C8B337">Potion of Emotional Stability</Text>
  <Text Key="43951B74">Potion of Nausea</Text>
  <Text Key="35CDAAB2">Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="7C870B77">Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="74A426B7">Potion of the Nimble Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="3778DEFD">familiar_GP08GENdragon Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="E6247068">familiar_GP08GENdragon Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="B6E86B30">familiar_GP08GENbat Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="A2299CDF">familiar_GP08GENbat Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="61994F40">familiar_GP08GENbunnerFly Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="C7090F0F">familiar_GP08GENbunnerFly Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="D2704A3E">familiar_GP08GENfairy Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="3E55FBC1">familiar_GP08GENfairy Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="B2F2A8C5">familiar_GP08GENfrog Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="DDB22FC0">familiar_GP08GENfrog Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="94B7321D">familiar_GP08GENowl Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="126A4908">familiar_GP08GENowl Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="600EC750">familiar_GP08GENphoenix Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="5BBB227F">familiar_GP08GENphoenix Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="6E5A23D5">familiar_GP08GENraven Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="F1D971F0">familiar_GP08GENraven Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="EFC74262">familiar_GP08GENskull Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="9EE060DD">familiar_GP08GENskull Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="4B306DBA">familiar_GP08GENvoidCritter Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="A303ED65">familiar_GP08GENvoidCritter Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="54FFA844">familiar_GP08GENvoodooDoll Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="3142600B">familiar_GP08GENvoodooDoll Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="7FBE5866">A classic Spellcaster companion, bats have commonly been closely associated to magic users since the times of ancients.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF9F2379">Familiar Orb of the Snub-Nosed Leaf Bat</Text>
  <Text Key="706F277E">This interesting creature is an unexpected entity that defies normal boundaries and demands a closer inspection. Its true nature is unknown.</Text>
  <Text Key="913AA501">Familiar Orb of the Bunnerfly</Text>
  <Text Key="24BC3FF6">Regal and powerful, this dragon should never be discounted based on its size. It is a formidable foe as well as a cherished companion.</Text>
  <Text Key="793A3D29">Familiar Orb of the Dragon</Text>
  <Text Key="B611AD50">Bathed in pure energy it is nigh impossible to make out the true form of a fairy beyond its magical wings. One can feel what can only be described as a slight spark when near.</Text>
  <Text Key="D462F47F">Familiar Orb of the Fairy</Text>
  <Text Key="720B9383">Be warned to avoid the direct gaze of the glowfrog. They are usually quite mischievous characters although quite harmless when left to their own devices.</Text>
  <Text Key="546ED5D2">Familiar Orb of the Glowfrog</Text>
  <Text Key="01103E67">The preeminent symbol of magic and ancient knowledge. They have a strong connection to the moon and stoically follow their chosen Spellcaster.</Text>
  <Text Key="B1B9149E">Familiar Orb of the Sixam Owl</Text>
  <Text Key="DF8FC342">The Phoenix is intimately familiar with the cycle of life, death, and rebirth. From the ashes they arise and into the ashes they fall. So has it always been.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9703C3D">Familiar Orb of the Phoenix</Text>
  <Text Key="26C0593B">The harbingers of prophecy and, some say, bad luck. Ravens are an ancient creature that remain steadfast alongside their favorite Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="AFFB209A">Familiar Orb of the Raven</Text>
  <Text Key="E40B2FFC">When you need a protector that truly frightens your opponent consider the skull. It is hard not to be intimidated by this floating, haunting familiar.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF6D4F53">Familiar Orb of the Skull</Text>
  <Text Key="274D7FE0">The Veild is a Voidcritter deep with the knowledge of countless galaxies across space and time. No one really knows the true motivation of this critter, but that didn’t stop one well known kids TV show from almost featuring the Veild as a main character.</Text>
  <Text Key="9D3C062F">Familiar Orb of the Veild</Text>
  <Text Key="7EBDE6FA">Despite this familiar being the mysterious and silent type you may still catch yourself whispering to them, “Do that voodoo that you do!”</Text>
  <Text Key="A26311A5">Familiar Orb of the Hex Doll</Text>
  <Text Key="737415AB">Oh dear, a bit watery;\nOn some days, it seems completely empty\nWhen not, it continues day and night\nSometimes enhanced by fright.\n\nIgnited by magic\nSprays into the sky's reaches\nThen it brims over, going to sleep...</Text>
  <Text Key="D9BFC8AA">Mystical Reservoir</Text>
  <Text Key="B1BBED1C">… My wife says “haunted”. Personally, I don’t really care what ya call it. All I know is that, over the past 30 days, every time I open my new Glimmerbrook Fridge, all my stuff seems to have been moved around. In fact, I think someone swiped the other half of my haggis &amp; cheese sandwich. Who does that? Far be it from me to judge but making a guy’s sammy disappear from the fridge… that just gives me the shivers.</Text>
  <Text Key="FECBB2F3">30 Day Glimmerbrook Fridge</Text>
  <Text Key="4904FCA6">This root, that is known to sometimes be shaped like a Sim, has strange properties when mixed with other ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="E64767B9">{S.Mandrake}{P.Mandrakes}</Text>
  <Text Key="6F2AB68F">Known to draw in many species of flies with its fragrant scent. Best keep them away from your home cooking...</Text>
  <Text Key="35076D56">{S.Valerian Root}{P.Valerian Roots}</Text>
  <Text Key="19709AE3">A magical bush that produces Mandrake Root.</Text>
  <Text Key="504F8CB2">Mandrake Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="59F58BB6">A magical bush that produces Valerian Root.</Text>
  <Text Key="99AFC2E9">Valerian Plant</Text>
  <Text Key="C172CD5D">First impressions are everything! This gate was previously owned by Wizard Valishbane, the legendary socialite and host of many-a-late-night-rager for magical high society. After an incident involving a levitating punch bowl, Valishbane retired from the party circuit and retreated into a hermit lifestyle. Dazzle your guests, but party responsibly!</Text>
  <Text Key="11987248">Razzle Dazzle Gate</Text>
  <Text Key="D0A9785F">The Glimmerstone is given to every Spellcaster. It gives them the ability to travel to The Magic Realm once per day. If a stone is ever lost or destroyed a new one can be claimed from any of the three Sages.</Text>
  <Text Key="2DE22006">Glimmerstone</Text>
  <Text Key="015B0C16">This is the Spawner that will spawn Magic Motes in the world. Only Sims with Mote sight can see them.</Text>
  <Text Key="336B52C9">Magic Mote Spawner</Text>
  <Text Key="A0691ACF">This invisible objects is what the Sages will be attracted to to stay in their respective areas in The Magic HQ.</Text>
  <Text Key="58148896">Sage Attractor</Text>
  <Text Key="9F0F1F92">Magic Motes are an ancient magic that people still do not fully understand. Sages have the power to harness the motes' energy and transfer their magic into others, turning them into Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A4E9BAD">{S.Magic Mote}{P.Magic Motes}</Text>
  <Text Key="C96644DA">Jig_2x3_solo_magicBroom placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="9CCDF425">Named after the famous Queen of the Non-Sleepers, this light fixture is imponent and elegant, comprised of orbs filled with magical light.\n\nLegend says that in the later days of her reign, the queen had sent knights to get these light orbs from the depths of the Moon, testing the consistence of reality.</Text>
  <Text Key="62F6D5A0">Light Of The Marasenna</Text>
  <Text Key="64ADB0FF">Hauntingly beautiful light can be yours with this subtle yet stately orb torch. Engineered and enchanted by WiseWitch Inc. -- your source for environmentally friendly and energy conscious energy!</Text>
  <Text Key="3631EC26">Orb Torch</Text>
  <Text Key="953E89C7">Recovered from an ancient Celtic ritual site, this torch glows only for those who possess a connection to the magic realm. But even if you don't, it still looks pretty snazzy.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF56DC7E">Iona Knot Torch</Text>
  <Text Key="96F0A395">For spellcasters looking to purify the air in their home! This particular type of crystal's porous surface absorbs negative energy and transforms it into pure positivity. Toxicity be gone!</Text>
  <Text Key="17D771B0">Crystal of the Air</Text>
  <Text Key="292F4AB1">If I had a Simoleon for every time I’ve said to myself, “Man, I wish I had a sweet looking, jewel encrusted, artzee shmartzee fly, that is also a light, to slap on my wall to brighten up my dull rooms”… Yeah, I’d have me a bunch O’ Simoleons. Even when the Totally Lit Bug Light is not lit, it’s still totally lit, ya know. So, get the fly on the wall that everyone’s buzzing about  ⁠— The Totally Lit Bug Light.</Text>
  <Text Key="0FFA3484">Totally Lit Bug Light</Text>
  <Text Key="B1A6E86D">Built from the light and energy from Spellcasters of old, this sconce guides new Spellcasters through the halls in their thirst of knowledge and greatness. Every sconce seeks out the darkness to vanquish it, like a scout. But alas, it is not immortal - or is it? Repairs may be necessary.</Text>
  <Text Key="83EA3938">Sconce For Little Light</Text>
  <Text Key="11524220">Carved from the ancient trees of The Magic Realm. The Gnarled Broom has a natural form, twisting and turning, hopefully it doesn't fly the way it looks.</Text>
  <Text Key="43C1D96F">Gnarled Wood Broom</Text>
  <Text Key="94E5226D">Powered by crystals from The Magic Realm, this broom travels so fast it can open inter-dimensional portals. Where they lead nobody knows!?</Text>
  <Text Key="0AFBC738">Crystal Zoomer</Text>
  <Text Key="D61C1A42">The Classic Wood Broom is tried and true. With just enough power to get you from point A to point B, this is the perfect broom for any new Spellcaster.</Text>
  <Text Key="3BE7913D">Classic Wood Broom</Text>
  <Text Key="16E69E6F">Infused with wild magic, this Rocket Broom can reach insanely fast top speeds. Go faster! Higher! Up, up, and away!</Text>
  <Text Key="ACC5BFB6">Rocket Broom</Text>
  <Text Key="0B1FD4F3">Perfect for any practical Spellcaster, the magic mop not only can get you where you need to be, it has the power to remove the toughest of stains.</Text>
  <Text Key="AED36D22">Magic Mop</Text>
  <Text Key="4E14F1AB">This portal will allow you to travel to The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="32D39CAA">Pristine Portal to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="27BDFB44">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot, and Sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="2476E90B">Portal Exit 1</Text>
  <Text Key="0A1BAD38">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot, and Sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="55844737">Portal Entrance 1</Text>
  <Text Key="7D8B1798">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot, and Sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4D4A217">Portal Entrance 2</Text>
  <Text Key="5CB0D35B">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To you use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot and sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="59A7533A">Portal Entrance 3</Text>
  <Text Key="8BA438F0">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot, and Sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="7D9A789F">Portal Exit 2</Text>
  <Text Key="29BAFFEF">These portals will allow your Sim to teleport between the matching pairs. To use them you need to place the matching Exit and Entrance on your lot, and Sims will choose to use them when it is the shortest distance to their destination.</Text>
  <Text Key="2FCA2C36">Portal Exit 3</Text>
  <Text Key="E347F78D">This portal will allow you to travel to The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="FA717DD8">Damaged Portal to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="34C30100">Forged from the spirits of the the underworld. This wand holds strange mysteries that have yet to be discovered.</Text>
  <Text Key="51E6BDCF">Wand of the Forgotten</Text>
  <Text Key="78A5B0CD">Hand-carved from the trees of Sylvan Glade, this wand holds immense power.</Text>
  <Text Key="A89F1718">Wand of The Sylvan Forest</Text>
  <Text Key="A3E24E22">A basic wood wand. The perfect start to any Spellcasters collection.</Text>
  <Text Key="CAF4FF9D">Wood Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="C6FAD74F">Forged out of moonstones and imbued with astral vapors, this wand holds the power to a million galaxies.</Text>
  <Text Key="658C1616">Wand of Astral Creation</Text>
  <Text Key="25705914">Forged from the rocks deep within the crust of the Earth. This wand contains the power of every elemental.</Text>
  <Text Key="2EB743FB">Wand of The Elementals</Text>
  <Text Key="22579E01">Hand-carved by the finest woodworkers in the land. This wand is not produced by mere machines. Each one is slightly different than the last.</Text>
  <Text Key="869EDF34">Natural Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="BD796376">Far more sturdy than the Wood Wand and the Bone Wand. The Marble wand is encrusted with an elemental gem and has all the markings of elegance.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0B94FA9">Marble Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="25EEC123">Crafted with the methods of old, this Ancient Wand hearkens back to a simpler time, a time when wands didn't represent your wealth or status, but your passion for the magic arts.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE02D4F2">Ancient Wood Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="7A56C038">The Bone Wand is slightly more robust than classic wood variant. Just don't ask where the bones came from...</Text>
  <Text Key="2B131037">Bone Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="94746432">You want to see a magic trick? Perfect for any Spellcaster that likes pulling familiars out of hats... Though that trick has been banned for centuries due to familiar cruelty.</Text>
  <Text Key="C53FE7CD">Magician's Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="FC1B654D">Do not be deceived by its simple look. This wand display was crafted form the wood of the ancient trees of Glimmerbrook, and has been passed down generations over generations of great Spellcasters. Display your favorite wand proudly, knowing that generations of wisdom has been passed down to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="BD110C98">Luxuriously Luxe Wand Display</Text>
  <Text Key="B242158D">Come one! Come all! Grab a broom to test drive! Note: You break it - you buy it.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F6977D8">Brooms, Baubles, and Beyond</Text>
  <Text Key="1D18F49E">Come one! Come all! Grab a broom to test drive! Note: You break it - you buy it.</Text>
  <Text Key="F863C4A1">Brooms, Baubles, and Beyond</Text>
  <Text Key="B325B649">Trying to make that perfect potion and need ingredients fast!? Look no further - we've got what you need!</Text>
  <Text Key="85B0E6AC">Questionable Quacks Emporium</Text>
  <Text Key="C6A23AAE">Trying to make that perfect potion and need ingredients fast!? Look no further - we've got what you need!</Text>
  <Text Key="2AB29251">Questionable Quacks Emporium</Text>
  <Text Key="830895A4">What we want when we want worthwhile wands! Wait no more and wander in! Our wandolier waves you over in welcome and will treat you well!   </Text>
  <Text Key="50ACB2EB">Juan's Wonderful One Stop Wand Warehouse</Text>
  <Text Key="C34B04C1">What we want when we want worthwhile wands! Wait no more and wander in! Our wandolier waves you over in welcome and will treat you well!</Text>
  <Text Key="DF8F0CF4">Juan's Wonderful One Stop Wand Warehouse</Text>
  <Text Key="60E295B8">Forget about those old clunky Crystal Balls. They’re so 5th century. Don’t scry about it. Get with it! Get the Town Scryer Mirror and see who’s at your door BEFORE you open it right from the comfort and safety of your full-length Town Scryer Mirror. Just look deeply. You’ll be the Nostradamus of your neighborhood.</Text>
  <Text Key="58FB98B7">Towne Scryer Mirror – by Towne Industries</Text>
  <Text Key="7F595870">Mirror Mirror, what the heck?\nWhy doesn’t thou pain my neck?\nI see my scalp, but that is all.\nMe thinks that I have shrunk so small.\nBut then it’s clear for me to see\nTis hung too high for the size of me.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B48BF1F">Mirror Mirror</Text>
  <Text Key="02294D0A">Illustrations from the late 1800s encyclopedia "The Science of Magic" by Doctor Fen Bittern -- the only known instance where a non-spellcaster secretly studied the magical arts. Bittern's research was dismissed and mocked by other non-spellcasters. However, in the magical community he has gained a cult-like following, and many still draw amusement from his work. Print options include "Sentient Swamp Creatures", "Poisonous Potions", or "Snowdrops and Skullflowers."</Text>
  <Text Key="426B3815">The Science of Magic Print Series</Text>
  <Text Key="0F6661AF">When you’re a spellcaster you live on a pretty tight schedule. If you don’t budget your magical time, it can get embarrassing – for everyone. Well, no need to stain the rug about it anymore. Just pick up the Spellcaster Scheduler and track the phases of the moon, and the ideal potion making times...but on YOUR time. Available at Badbibidibabidyboopidy.com</Text>
  <Text Key="5EC071F6">Spellcaster Scheduler</Text>
  <Text Key="087A73E0">plant_GP08Philodendron01 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="C388A22F">plant_GP08Philodendron01 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="AD21F013">plantGP08_mushroom_lg_01 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="A782F4C2">plantGP08_mushroom_lg_01 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="BDDE6BF4">The center of the home is the hearth -- especially in a spellcaster home! Features a cluster of gnome-mined crystals that have been charged by moonlight for over three months. Note: crystals may or may not attract faeries and faerie rings. To prevent this please see "Fae-Away" products.</Text>
  <Text Key="B49C1E5B">Crystal Garden Hearth</Text>
  <Text Key="AB45CB96">I am a rock!(Rock!)\nI am a rock!(Rock!)\nI am a rock!(Rock!)\nRock!</Text>
  <Text Key="24887949">Giant Rock Cluster</Text>
  <Text Key="21E1C3FC">Represents intuition and omnipotent knowledge. The bigger the better!</Text>
  <Text Key="0A44CB53">Mystical Crystal Cluster</Text>
  <Text Key="52B27D33">Slightly taller! Still represents intuition and omnipotent knowledge.</Text>
  <Text Key="3C7FA062">Mystical Crystal Cluster (Tall)</Text>
  <Text Key="2BD91BA2">Slightly leaning, in the search of more power to absorb.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8BCF01D">Mystical Crystal Cluster (Slightly Leaning)</Text>
  <Text Key="0849EE99">Growing horizontally, for better access to power to absorb and consume.</Text>
  <Text Key="521E991C">Mystical Crystal Cluster (Horizontal)</Text>
  <Text Key="C011F8C9">rockGP08_group_med_01 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="4005262C">rockGP08_group_med_01 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="330257BB">rockGP08_group_sm_01 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="6FABD41A">rockGP08_group_sm_01 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="F00B5E12">Four score and many moons ago, lived a king who inhabited a grand, stone castle with very lengthy hallways. Though he possessed boundless riches, the king’s hallways were barren &amp; cold. There was no known carpet that could cover such prodigious expanses at any cost. So, the king sought consultation with his wizard. The king queried the wizard, “Ever yank a large roll of toilet paper? Yeah, I want a rug that works kinda like that.”  And so, it was, in the wink of that wizard’s eye, the Relentless Rugs of Repetitiveness was conjured. And, much like this description, the rug goes on and on and on and…</Text>
  <Text Key="FA9A0F2D">Relentless Rugs of Repetitiveness</Text>
  <Text Key="8291578E">Is your broom in the shop again but you have an urgent levitation situation on your hands? Don’t come unraveled, man! Call GuberLift Carpets. We’ll come pick you up. Choose from 3 plush flying carpet discs that’ll drop you at work or take you around the cosmos. Leave the soaring to a GuberLift Carpet!</Text>
  <Text Key="3A2937B1">GuberLift Magic Carpets</Text>
  <Text Key="312EB8F3">Where would you go if this thing worked?\nWhere will you land?\nIn another place?\nIn another time?\nIs this a portal? We might be being deceived.</Text>
  <Text Key="8542D922">Tapestry To Nowhere</Text>
  <Text Key="311C6FD2">Hold onto your hemlock and nestle up to your nightshades! This classic apothecary cabinet is perfect for the organized herbalist. With ample shelf space for your canisters and vials, you'll never mix up your mugwort and nettles again.</Text>
  <Text Key="41061AED">Classic Apothecary Cabinet</Text>
  <Text Key="57E74184">Has this ever happened to you? You've cast your circle. The candles are set. Your sacred altar is ready. But wait...where's the incantation?! This beautiful and functional piece of furniture displays your incantation sheets so you'll never lose them again!</Text>
  <Text Key="BBEAA94B">Incantation Escritoire</Text>
  <Text Key="F9E537D7">While it is missing the numbers to measure, this scale is still in mint working condition. Take a leap and use it for recipes, potions, and whatever you please - anything that requires little to no accuracy!</Text>
  <Text Key="59E77BAE">Antique 'Working' Scale</Text>
  <Text Key="20437A7A">sculptTableBByBunny_01 Placeholder Description</Text>
  <Text Key="EBF07425">sculptTableBByBunny_01 Placeholder Name</Text>
  <Text Key="E867CC76">Drier, drier, plants be drier!\nHanging by a magic wire!\nNot a deceiver, your herbs are drained!</Text>
  <Text Key="10363AA9">"Drier, Drier" Plants Drier</Text>
  <Text Key="706C4B5D">A basic packet of magical plants. What will you grow? How tall will it grow? Who knows!</Text>
  <Text Key="35B08C48">Starter Magical Plants</Text>
  <Text Key="0540B641">Going Round &amp; Round about how to display your Odds &amp; Ends? Asking yourself, what are the Pros &amp; Cons of furniture for my Odds &amp; Ends? Can the Q&amp;A Curio Case really keep all my Odds &amp; Ends, Safe &amp; Sound?...Or will the constant Opening &amp; Closing of the Q&amp;A Curio Case cause excessive Wear &amp; Tear on its Fit &amp; Finish? – Or worse - Slice &amp; Dice my Odds &amp; Ends? That’s a lot to go Back &amp; Forth about it? Put aside your Fear &amp; Loathing. Just Get it &amp; Forget it!</Text>
  <Text Key="4C966974">Q&amp;A Curio Case</Text>
  <Text Key="25BBCC4E">At the start of his career, average illusionist, Larry Loudini (known as the OK Loudini), had an idea for a magic trick he knew would catapult him to instant celebrity. He eagerly began construction of a water-filled, steel &amp; glass tank. Inside the tank, he would be shackled &amp; suspended upside down. He would then make his escape from this watery debacle. Well, It was plenty dangerous! So, the OK Loudini made a few slight safety modifications to the original design. Before his first performance, he added sliding doors, an adjustable showerhead, non-slip flooring &amp; a soap dish. Captivating. Well, Safety First!</Text>
  <Text Key="0A959371">Loudini’s Chamber of Sprinkles</Text>
  <Text Key="C93DB1A1">In Greek mythology, goddess Hera took the eyes of many-eyed giant Argus and set them into the tail of the peacock. Gruesome? Perhaps. A lovely adornment for your bathroom? Definitely! No giants were harmed in the making of this sink.</Text>
  <Text Key="BFDD5854">Hera's Peacock Sink</Text>
  <Text Key="CBFFD3AA">Modeled after the pub stools at ancient spellcaster hangout O'Growley's pub, these stools bring a warm and relaxed atmosphere to any magical home.</Text>
  <Text Key="CB8E4135">Pub Perch</Text>
  <Text Key="8BC16E0D">After hanging up his bass guitar in the 80’s, Dr. Von Funkenstein opened a used furniture store. But selling other people’s used furniture was not enough for the frustrated doctor. So, late at night, with funk music blasting, he would take “acquired” furniture pieces &amp; cobble together his OWN creations. It is said the doctor’s chairs would come back to life &amp; dance to those pulsing beats as the doctor sunk deeper &amp; deeper into funky chair madness. What? You never heard of Musical Chairs? Get yours today!</Text>
  <Text Key="CFBF1958">Born to Boogie – The Funkenstein Collection</Text>
  <Text Key="D674442B">This very chair was once the property of one of THE MOST average illusionists who ever lived - Larry Loudini. Touted as The OK Loudini (by some), he demonstrated his pure lack of magic &amp; sleight of hand abilities to several people throughout much of the west side of Throckmorton, North Dakota. When Loudini finally passed over to the great beyond he left behind this fairly cool Séance chair which he never really used. Now, you can have it if you want it.</Text>
  <Text Key="73F40C2A">Loudini Séance Chair</Text>
  <Text Key="43904FAD">Sea god Poseidon doesn't surface much, but when he does, this seashell-carved chair is his favorite seat in the beach house.</Text>
  <Text Key="764A0A78">Poseidon's Armchair</Text>
  <Text Key="4098E36C">I don’t know about you but when I begin my day I look at this loveseat and it just sings to me. I love it so much that it makes me smile &amp; lights up my day from the inside out. I feel like I can fly on the wings on this loveseat. It’s a dee-lightful and magical experience that can only be shared by two.</Text>
  <Text Key="51D2B0A3">On the Wings of a Loveseat</Text>
  <Text Key="EABBABA8">It started showing up in an old house. Some people were checking it out, it was a bench - some say - so we bought it anyway.\n\nWe named it in a whim, it was an ottoman? Eh...it was 1981 or 1881...so we went with it. It has no feelings, and it doesn't know who owns it.\n\nI got a backyard, with nothing on it, except for this? The Hardest Seat to Sit On...</Text>
  <Text Key="69DF28C7">The Hardest Seat To Sit On</Text>
  <Text Key="76D10461">If you’re looking for a new sofa, the back of this sofa is looking at you. How is that possible, you may ask? Well, one day, bespectacled soothsayer, Clair Voyant, was crystal ball gazing on a sofa when she accidentally dropped her soothsaying spectacles. Of course, the sofa ate her glasses, as sofas do, &amp; they were lost forever. But those glasses had a mighty powerful prescription &amp; over time the back of the sofa morphed into the upside down shape of Clair’s glasses. To this day, the davenport keeps both eyes open to reunite the specs with their rightful owner.</Text>
  <Text Key="DCBD8714">The Farsighted Davenport</Text>
  <Text Key="8289812B">Like all good kitchen witches, this stove encourages productivity and safety in the kitchen. Modeled after traditional wood-burning stoves but comes pre-enchanted with several fire spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AC5332A">Kitchen Witch Stove</Text>
  <Text Key="ABD06E61">streetDeco_GP08fountainGENstone4x4 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="29EBA514">streetDeco_GP08fountainGENstone4x4 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="343304D9">streetDeco_GP08fountainGENstone5x5 placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="45E6395C">streetDeco_GP08fountainGENstone5x5 placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="B463718B">streetDeco_GP08GardenStatue placeholder description</Text>
  <Text Key="DEE6070A">streetDeco_GP08GardenStatue placeholder name</Text>
  <Text Key="15A135CE">This aethereal coffee table is hand tooled from the phantom planks of the wreckage from the doomed sailing vessel, the Flying Dutchman. This beautifully inlaid coffee table can often be seen on dark &amp; stormy evenings, far off in the distance, mournfully sailing just above the horizon, endlessly seeking any matching sofa in the storm.</Text>
  <Text Key="B86E97F1">Fata Morgana Table</Text>
  <Text Key="0867BFD0">Got a coven load of friends coming over but you need to conjure up a bigger table if you’re gonna make that next séance truly magical?  Now you can make ALL your gatherings magical with the Magical Gatherings Séance Table. Plenty of room for 8 of your closest believers. The glass top ensures no under the table flim-flam from the invited guests or uninvited spirits. Plus, we won’t pull the old coin trick on you for the price. It’s great for a magical night of cards with friends too!</Text>
  <Text Key="002BA3FF">Magical Gatherings Séance Table</Text>
  <Text Key="E7FFFFCB">Once upon a time, this big ol’ beautiful table was just a tiny, magical stool belonging to Carl “left ear” Lemmkey. Carl, a porch toad, lived in the bayou, on the porch of the local Spellcaster. He loved to sit on that ol’ magic stool &amp; play his electric banjo all day &amp; night. But that mean old spellcaster constantly nagged Carl to “turn it down!” One day, she’d had enough &amp; tried to cast a spell on the magic stool. Unfortunately for her, it backfired &amp; she was transformed into the AbraCaTable*. Hey, everyone knows it’s dangerous to mess with a toadstool. Get your AbraCaTable today. Free home deliverance. *Note: No one croaked in the making of this table.</Text>
  <Text Key="FBF8B64A">AbraCaTable</Text>
  <Text Key="F24E0CEA">This table is enchanted. No kidding. It changes to look like whatever it thinks YOU want it to look like. So, perhaps you can explain why the Magical Mystery Table has taken first place honors for best looking horseshoe mustache on an end table for the past 14 years running at the International Table Mustache Festival? Oh, you can also put stuff on it. Try doing that with any standard stache.</Text>
  <Text Key="4A488275">The Magical Mystery Table</Text>
  <Text Key="D716FFE6">"When ya gotta go, ya gotta go" - ya know? Butt what if you gotta go and get to another parallel dimension in a flash? Just Flush!  The Portal Potty is THE fastest and most luxurious way to go. Voted #2 Time Traveling Toidy of the year by Home &amp; Loo Magazine. Plus, it’s got plenty of leg room &amp; a lid that doubles as a panini press. Trust me, it’s the Plumb I tell you!*\n\n*Please remember to wash hands before returning to the present dimension.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A5181F9">Portal Potty</Text>
  <Text Key="6467AA02">Here lie the remains of a slinger of spells. May the memories of magic run deep and true.</Text>
  <Text Key="D730EDFD">Spellcaster's Tombstone</Text>
  <Text Key="825B258E">Here remains a slinger of spells. May the memories of magic run deep and true.</Text>
  <Text Key="502141B1">Spellcaster's Urn</Text>
  <Text Key="49E5C7A8">Here remains a slinger of spells. May the memories of magic run deep and true.</Text>
  <Text Key="7BCABCC7">Spellcaster's Urn</Text>
  <Text Key="6412C3AA">Most travelers who transcend to the astral plane wander aimlessly. Gazing into the Astral Window before the spiritual journey allows the viewer to lift the haze of unknowing and reach your true destination. It's like a GPS for astral projection!</Text>
  <Text Key="FC741135">Astral Window</Text>
  <Text Key="C9B115E2">Let the moonlight in with this understated yet brilliant window. Includes a special tint to maximize the power of moonlight. The moon may be waning, but the magic doesn't have to!</Text>
  <Text Key="2FE6835D">Waning Moon Window</Text>
  <Text Key="4DF68F7E">Opportunity knocks but once, but if you keep a window around, it might hang out for a long time! Legends say this particular window style is said to attract plentiful opportunities. Disclaimer: buyer must discern good opportunities from bad opportunities.</Text>
  <Text Key="24E45D01">Window of Opportunity</Text>
  <Text Key="3F01F262">Magic pirates? Was that ever a thing? Yes! This window was owned by one such pirate: Baron Von Lapis, who insisted on having it in his quarters. Von Lapis claimed the window aided in the casting of elemental spells, but we think the main selling point is that it was owned by a pirate warlock. It just has a nice ring to it.</Text>
  <Text Key="E93170DD">Divine Porthole Window</Text>
  <Text Key="15AED981">Useful for everyone! We swear! Special crystalline glass draws power from the full moon, this window amplifies moonlit spells. Increase your night-time productivity! Also perfect for night owls and insomniacs.</Text>
  <Text Key="AE20B9B4">Spellcaster's Delight Window</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D498B8">Adopt the soul of a wayward spellcaster by placing this window in your home! As part of the Spellcaster Reform Program, witches or warlocks found guilty of major crimes are banished to these windows. Hopefully by observing actions of upstanding spellcaster citizens, they will one day be freed. Take a banished soul home today!</Text>
  <Text Key="5D1C31B7">Banished Soul Window</Text>
  <Text Key="250B1081">The Magic Realm is the source of all magic. Unfortunately, it is slowly being pulled apart by the swirling vortex surrounding it. The only thing that is keeping it together is the balance between the three houses of magic. Each house has a Sage that is the master in their respective style. If any imbalance is ever struct between these Sages the entire realm could collapse.</Text>
  <Text Key="82BF55D6">The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="5E0C20FA">Ember</Text>
  <Text Key="4B89A531">Faba</Text>
  <Text Key="CF0CB147">Silversweater</Text>
  <Text Key="20DCB087">Situated in the center of Glimmerbrook this simple cottage is near the best fishing spots in all of Glimmerbrook. Not to mention the gorgeous Simstagram photos that can be taken from the nearby bridge.</Text>
  <Text Key="D25AE920">Grace and Tomax have been roommates ever since they first became Spellcasters. They have day jobs, but magic is their main focus, and they've got a friendly competition going to see who will become an Adept Spellcaster first!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D5D1E6F">Amicable Acolytes</Text>
  <Text Key="D36C776C">Brooks Bridge Borough</Text>
  <Text Key="D0BF1EB8">A local establishment that's been in Glimmerbrook as far back as anyone can remember, and though it has had some upgrades through the years, it's still full of nostalgic charm.</Text>
  <Text Key="0D368D27">Elixirs and Brews</Text>
  <Text Key="57D20AFD">If peace and quiet appeals to you, the Rock Ridge Canyon is perfect. Nestled up against Glimmerbrook's towering boulders, this quaint location is sure to give any Spellcaster the silence they need to practice and study to hone their magical prowess.</Text>
  <Text Key="AC2AB5DE">The Charm family has produced generations of distinguished Spellcasters, as Minerva often reminds her children. Gemma resents her family's high expectations even though she secretly wants to make them proud. Darrel is an aspiring duelist who just got engaged to Emilia, a newly ascended Spellcaster who has a lot to live up to.</Text>
  <Text Key="DA1D63E1">Charm Family</Text>
  <Text Key="F2006CDA">Rock Ridge Canyon</Text>
  <Text Key="F40040EE">With breathtaking views of Glimmerbrook Falls, this location is perfect for any cozy home.</Text>
  <Text Key="81F41165">Creek Side Corner</Text>
  <Text Key="1D9EB663">An ancient plot nestled deep within Glimmerbrook. Some say the previous resident was tasked with guarding an ancient relic located atop the Glimmerbrook Waterfall. Legend has it the owner disappeared one night never to be seen again. Maybe they vanished into some other dimension?</Text>
  <Text Key="EEF1AC10">Glimmerbrook Watch</Text>
  <Text Key="EA8BE3C5">Touchy Feely</Text>
  <Text Key="1DA041CD">Unset {1.ObjectName} as Favorite Broom</Text>
  <Text Key="59C8F530">Set {1.ObjectName} as Favorite Broom</Text>
  <Text Key="D8B37404">Bottle Up</Text>
  <Text Key="5A90CD77">Bottle Up All</Text>
  <Text Key="D32A194B">Discard Content</Text>
  <Text Key="F41556E9">Drink From</Text>
  <Text Key="0387AD6A">Experiment</Text>
  <Text Key="BB5D0E52">Cook {2.String}</Text>
  <Text Key="C4FD5068">Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="AEAFF483">Grab All Servings</Text>
  <Text Key="695AE64E">Help with Potion Brew</Text>
  <Text Key="AA2393D6">Invite to Brew Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="CA0E2297">Hex Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="DF0D6A95">Brew Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="2D9706F0">Set Potion VFX</Text>
  <Text Key="1323415D">{0.SimName} does not know any recipes that can be made here.</Text>
  <Text Key="570F7AE3">Set Brewing Visual State</Text>
  <Text Key="0DBB2019">Break into Uncontrollable Laughter</Text>
  <Text Key="1016BB5D">{0.SimFirstName} is dying by Spellcaster Overload!</Text>
  <Text Key="138A44D2">Death By Spellcaster Overload</Text>
  <Text Key="A6E80A72">Add Dragon Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="071C29AB">Add Fairy Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="B6A374A2">Add Frog Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="6342EE61">Add Bunnerfly Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="D7588760">Add Owl Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="4EDAE1C6">Bind Bat Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="0E39FBC6">{1.SimName} is now bound as {0.SimName}'s Familiar.</Text>
  <Text Key="792C7AA4">Bind as Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="57D5AD66">Add Phoenix Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="9320E16D">Bind Raven Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="B1904F34">Add Skull Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="A60812F4">Add Voidcritter Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="F63375B2">Add Voodoo Doll Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="30F00017">Turn Into Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="95938741">Learn all Cauldron Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="DAC40058">Unlock All Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="9769B5F4">Cauldron Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="F329923A">Give Potion Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="E2610A5F">{0.SimFirstName} does not have a familiar bound to them.</Text>
  <Text Key="1A29C83B">You must be a spellcaster to bind familiars.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D01F5CA">Bind Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="59DBE251">Open</Text>
  <Text Key="28D0FDC3">Summon Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="B043B5A0">Unbind Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="E830B527">(From Being Chased By a Night Wraith)</Text>
  <Text Key="3FA28ABD">Being Chased By Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="97A5843E">Are you sure you want to destroy this Glimmerstone? You can always request a new one from any of the 3 Sages in The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="CA39AC7B">Destroy Glimmerstone</Text>
  <Text Key="A44D141F">The Glimmerstone needs time to recharge its power.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6116719">{0.SimFirstName} is already in The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="5FC915BA">Travel to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="E46BC3A9">Are you sure you want to leave The Magic Realm?</Text>
  <Text Key="9804D594">The swirling vortex appears to lead to a realm beyond our own reality. Do you dare cross the threshold?</Text>
  <Text Key="00C754A0">Turn Back</Text>
  <Text Key="25BA1A2C">Enter the Portal</Text>
  <Text Key="1289BFFD">Dismiss Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="377F8C7A">Send to Forage</Text>
  <Text Key="403D63B7">The familiar is already out foraging.</Text>
  <Text Key="4B725B21">Open Spellbook</Text>
  <Text Key="2A60C49F">Sim Spells/Potions Temporarily (Almost) Always Fails</Text>
  <Text Key="F595FC67">Sim Spells/Potions Temporarily Always Succeed</Text>
  <Text Key="8806239A">Return to HQ</Text>
  <Text Key="44D1D5B6">Go to Dueling Grounds</Text>
  <Text Key="01193F76">Go to Casters Alley</Text>
  <Text Key="0A4A8977">Go to Gardens</Text>
  <Text Key="58BE526A">Study Magical Tome</Text>
  <Text Key="160DEF3B">Buy Brooms &amp; Crystals</Text>
  <Text Key="7A163892">Buy Potion Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="AF286FD8">Buy Wands, Tomes, &amp; Familiars</Text>
  <Text Key="7BC81732">Ask To Teach Mischief Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="B39D72AD">Ask To Teach Practical Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="C6294F66">Ask To Teach Untamed Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="B86452EB">Ask To Teach Ultimate Practical Spell</Text>
  <Text Key="CB6AD58D">Ask To Teach Ultimate Untamed Spell</Text>
  <Text Key="90322127">Ask To Teach Ultimate Mischief Spell</Text>
  <Text Key="495BD49C">Discuss Overcharge Risks</Text>
  <Text Key="7F758888">Enthuse About Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="99EE5AEB">Talk About Potion Mishaps</Text>
  <Text Key="897F38A2">Rename Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="D9A11729">Give Curse</Text>
  <Text Key="B96DD5F3">Thanks for shopping at Brooms, Baubles, and Beyond! Check back tomorrow as our daily offerings are always changing. The items {0.SimFirstName} bought can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="B10E65D9">Brooms &amp; Crystals</Text>
  <Text Key="2E6E48F8">Thanks for shopping at Questionable Quacks Emporium! Check back tomorrow as our daily offerings are always changing. The items {0.SimFirstName} bought can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="5F330A6C">Potion Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="40C8D666">Thanks for shopping at Juan's Wonderful One Stop Wand Warehouse! Check back tomorrow as our daily offerings are always changing. The items {0.SimFirstName} bought can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="7B727F0A">Wands, Tomes, &amp; Familiars</Text>
  <Text Key="FF5E6C0B">Return to Glimmerbrook</Text>
  <Text Key="495696C6">Return to Glimmerbrook With</Text>
  <Text Key="F5677CD5">Travel to The Magic Realm With</Text>
  <Text Key="F38FC16B">Travel to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="140D6444">Be Disgusted</Text>
  <Text Key="00717FDC">Fawn</Text>
  <Text Key="C3D8D7F7">Drink Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="E20FCC26">Magic Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="04BA94A2">Go To Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="E98E562E">Watch Magic Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="C0C13A21">Give Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="CE751F35">Receive Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="5AF56879">Give Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="0EEEECBC">Command to Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="3E478F84">{1.SimFirstName} is beyond {0.SimFirstName}'s magical abilities.</Text>
  <Text Key="CAC3A13D">This Sim is already under a spell's influence.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5E5CE8D">Furio</Text>
  <Text Key="0F081F1F">Infatuate</Text>
  <Text Key="B84F0421">There are no Sims nearby for {1.SimFirstName} to target.</Text>
  <Text Key="3FA327D9">There are no Sims nearby for {1.SimFirstName} to target.</Text>
  <Text Key="FB74FDC0">(From Losing a Magic Duel)</Text>
  <Text Key="18133E0F">(From Winning a Magic Duel)</Text>
  <Text Key="A7230BD3">Magic Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="9B2EF648">Discuss Casting Techniques</Text>
  <Text Key="6DA1C929">{0.SimFirstName} has learned every possible potion they could. However, Experimenting on the Cauldron will provide a chance to gain potion ingredients.</Text>
  <Text Key="796D8CB4">Ask to Teach a Potion Recipe</Text>
  <Text Key="32571123">Discuss New Potion</Text>
  <Text Key="5337D0B7">I can't share my knowledge with just anyone... Let's get to know each other first, then I'll decide if you are worthy.</Text>
  <Text Key="81F3811B">You are not ready to learn any more spells in this school of magic. Keep practicing the magical arts and come back when you are a higher rank.</Text>
  <Text Key="C893EFA2">Ask For Mote Sight</Text>
  <Text Key="7D71ACB9">Learning the magical arts is a wonderful and perilous journey. Are you sure you are prepared to become a Spellcaster?</Text>
  <Text Key="6FC61DA5">Uhh, maybe later...</Text>
  <Text Key="768023A1">I was BORN ready!</Text>
  <Text Key="8926B5BA">The magical Sages are the only Spellcasters that can bestow their power onto other Sims.</Text>
  <Text Key="59F7BEAA">In order to bestow the gift of magic upon you, I will need &lt;b&gt;7 Magical Motes.&lt;/b&gt;\n\nI have granted you Mote Sight in order to see and retrieve them. &lt;b&gt;Search the realm for motes&lt;/b&gt; and return to me. \n\nQuickly, before the spell wears off!</Text>
  <Text Key="5797A8E6">Ask How to Use Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="A95D0EE2">Offer Magical Training</Text>
  <Text Key="6A9994D3">Ask For Magical Training</Text>
  <Text Key="DB71C2A4">You have recently requested a Glimmerstone. These things take time to make. Give the Sages some time before asking for another.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F64CAE9">Request Glimmerstone</Text>
  <Text Key="1789F14D">Magic essence still lingers on {1.SimFirstName}. Try again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="D2568BAF">Offer Rite of Ascension</Text>
  <Text Key="0BCEBB16">Magic essence still clings to {0.SimFirstName}! Ask again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="A5FF367E">Ask For Rite of Ascension</Text>
  <Text Key="7804898B">Are you sure you don't want to be a Spellcaster anymore?</Text>
  <Text Key="1D370E6C">Ask For Rite Of Dissolution</Text>
  <Text Key="B75FA63E">Be De-Spellcastered</Text>
  <Text Key="5BECA357">Perform Rite of Ascension</Text>
  <Text Key="5A1E9807">Be Transformed Into Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="550416BA">Turn In Motes</Text>
  <Text Key="8893F9CA">Use the Power of Forced Friendships</Text>
  <Text Key="F8960952">Feel the Friendship!</Text>
  <Text Key="EA9D6690">Use the Power of Masterful Insults </Text>
  <Text Key="9D24DBE0">Feel the Hatred!</Text>
  <Text Key="1A0E2D58">Use the Power of Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="67831648">Feel the Love!</Text>
  <Text Key="3530A138">Win some Wands or Brooms</Text>
  <Text Key="EC1523B9">Duel for Artifacts</Text>
  <Text Key="4F9F7BC2">Challenge to Duel for Artifacts</Text>
  <Text Key="7CCBD685">Friendly Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="FBFDE516">Challenge to Friendly Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="5D71CFA5">Heated Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="3E57E376">Challenge to Heated Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="366F1B60">Win some potion ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="2791B988">Duel for Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="A42CE1DF">Challenge to Duel for Ingredients</Text>
  <Text Key="2CECB5D8">Learn some new spells!</Text>
  <Text Key="D5199860">Duel for Knowledge</Text>
  <Text Key="04E27D57">Challenge to Duel for Knowledge</Text>
  <Text Key="A1529CB9">Disobedient Clone</Text>
  <Text Key="30F528FF">Controlled to Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="8EDE48AC">Rebellious Clone Fight</Text>
  <Text Key="0EFC0384">Spawn Clone</Text>
  <Text Key="9815D944">Luck Potion - Interactions Give Money</Text>
  <Text Key="553F17AC">Luck Potion - Interactions Give Objects</Text>
  <Text Key="A4787280">Be Fought</Text>
  <Text Key="2246CD78">{1.SimFirstName} is already commanded to clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="15999023">Unable to command an evil clone.</Text>
  <Text Key="F3E3B388">Command to Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="C9BBDF65">{1.SimFirstName} is already commanded to cook.</Text>
  <Text Key="5825A7F7">Command to Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="8D7A1AFF">(From Morphiate Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="07D6B5AA">Exist in Object Form</Text>
  <Text Key="ABC44EC9">Make Food</Text>
  <Text Key="88E984E6">Go to Sleep</Text>
  <Text Key="8D93BE25">(From Chillio Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="CF886D5F">Chillio-ed</Text>
  <Text Key="7FD1B12B">{0.SimFirstName} got caught, but still Burgliated an object. The item can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} Household Inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="A273B604">{0.SimFirstName} successfully Burgliated an object without drawing any attention. The item can be found in {M0.his}{F0.her} Household Inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="BBFE9DEB">{0.SimFirstName} successfully Burgliated an object, without drawing any unwanted attention.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FD91021">{0.SimFirstName} got caught, but still Burgliated the object.</Text>
  <Text Key="15DB8EF9">Copied item has been added to household inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="C131B143">Copied item has been added to {0.SimFirstName}'s inventory.</Text>
  <Text Key="798F4244">Copypasto</Text>
  <Text Key="56EF1875">Inferniate</Text>
  <Text Key="FB75DF40">Chillio</Text>
  <Text Key="66D2E98C">This plant does not need tending.</Text>
  <Text Key="11B89312">Floralorial</Text>
  <Text Key="CA9CC8F9">Zipzap</Text>
  <Text Key="CA3B4738">Herbio</Text>
  <Text Key="9FC9BBAA">Recently Burgliated an Object</Text>
  <Text Key="6E99FE66">Burgliate</Text>
  <Text Key="CB8F7719">Sim is already in this plane of existence.</Text>
  <Text Key="DDAD7172">Delicioso</Text>
  <Text Key="12CD5B8D">Practice Mischief Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="69D521EC">Practice Practical Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="36553F5F">Practice Untamed Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="0E221168">{0.SimFirstName} has already searched through the bookshelves. Try again later.</Text>
  <Text Key="5FC3D82B">{0.SimFirstName} found a Familiar: {1.ObjectName}\n\nWhat a fortuitous meeting!</Text>
  <Text Key="599F4F95">{0.SimFirstName} didn't find anything of interest in the shelves. Increasing {F0.her}{M0.his} magical prowess might help.</Text>
  <Text Key="B785CA81">Search For Tomes</Text>
  <Text Key="5A7EABCC">Creating clones too fast is dangerous. You will have to wait to cast Duplicato again.</Text>
  <Text Key="A7DAD07F">Duplicato</Text>
  <Text Key="C4B8E208">Decursify takes a lot of work to cast. {0.SimName} needs some time before trying again.</Text>
  <Text Key="313C5FCA">Transportalate to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="FFFC55A8">{1.SimFirstName} is already under the influence of Strangeify.</Text>
  <Text Key="71191A41">(From Strangeify Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="BC621034">Strangeify</Text>
  <Text Key="78F61A35">(From Deliriate Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="BB31C0F3">Bind Pet as Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="2DDD75B0">(From Furio Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="14D0F212">(From Inferniate Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="720EE19F">Inferniate</Text>
  <Text Key="E89F4FCC">On Fire</Text>
  <Text Key="CF4873C6">Chillio</Text>
  <Text Key="B9BA3BEF">(From Zipzap Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="4B83B017">Zipzap</Text>
  <Text Key="581A0A94">Electrocuted</Text>
  <Text Key="9FFAA794">(From Infatuate Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="F1EA783E">(From Minionize Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="150ED32B">Clean</Text>
  <Text Key="1DDF5773">There is a strange force preventing spells from being cast on Vendors.</Text>
  <Text Key="34A2B149">This Pet is already a Familiar.</Text>
  <Text Key="683386F5">Deliriate</Text>
  <Text Key="7BDDC70F">Dedeathify</Text>
  <Text Key="6E6C8DDF">Despairio</Text>
  <Text Key="29B1E237">Morphiate</Text>
  <Text Key="537D6699">(From Dedeathify Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="D658C9D0">{1.SimFirstName} is already under the influence of Despairio.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0A23FA4">(From Despario Spell)</Text>
  <Text Key="150776CA">Never Transportalate</Text>
  <Text Key="534983F3">Always Transportalate</Text>
  <Text Key="9CD8E567">Delicioso</Text>
  <Text Key="5D7D28A1">Grand Delicioso</Text>
  <Text Key="2E894391">Inferniate</Text>
  <Text Key="0BDBC31C">Herbio</Text>
  <Text Key="8CAFC485">Cast...Something?</Text>
  <Text Key="59493B41">Transportalate</Text>
  <Text Key="7E25A7D6">Fly Here</Text>
  <Text Key="4D75CE44">Awkward Hug</Text>
  <Text Key="5A8F3AE7">Snap Out of It</Text>
  <Text Key="A3F56D26">Unset {1.ObjectName} as Favorite Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="990F901B">Set {1.ObjectName} as Favorite Wand</Text>
  <Text Key="D12A8839">Is this...MAGIC?!</Text>
  <Text Key="E1790E64">Wander Aimlessly</Text>
  <Text Key="373C4CBA">Build Charge is currently on cooldown. Try this later.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4587E24">Build Charge</Text>
  <Text Key="03BB4616">See Overcharged Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="635CAC4B">(From Seeing An Overcharged Spellcaster)</Text>
  <Text Key="EDAADCC2">Terrified by Overcharged Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="794215D6">Discharge is on cooldown</Text>
  <Text Key="5868C890">Discharge</Text>
  <Text Key="BD560E9F">{0.SimFirstName} cannot collect any more Motes.</Text>
  <Text Key="3095B1BB">Collect Mote</Text>
  <Text Key="73A566FB">Destroy Mote</Text>
  <Text Key="7B562A6B">Train {1.SimFirstName}</Text>
  <Text Key="B174F354">Be Trained</Text>
  <Text Key="706F3F9E">Absorb Mote</Text>
  <Text Key="A4A85E70">(From Seeing a Spellcaster Overload)</Text>
  <Text Key="6A4FA2FD">Never Use Brooms</Text>
  <Text Key="7B0B7DB1">Always Use Brooms</Text>
  <Text Key="E51806F0">This toggle is used to let your Sim to automatically use their Favorite Broom or not. </Text>
  <Text Key="BFBC5B6F">This toggle is used to let your Sim to automatically use their Favorite Wand or not. </Text>
  <Text Key="FCDB8DF3">Never Use Wands</Text>
  <Text Key="50AA669C">Always Use Wands</Text>
  <Text Key="0F893AB8">(From Energy Overcharge)</Text>
  <Text Key="41F8F3DC">Spellcaster Overload</Text>
  <Text Key="E45747B3">React to Overload</Text>
  <Text Key="5537F7D9">Arcanist's Retreat</Text>
  <Text Key="3D438E41">Alchemist's Scullery</Text>
  <Text Key="61DF0F15">Summoner's Nook</Text>
  <Text Key="20610D3E">Wizard's Lair</Text>
  <Text Key="6055B06C">&lt;span class="money"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;\n&lt;b&gt;Used for:&lt;/b&gt; Cauldron Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="C2F69665">&lt;span class="money"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;\n&lt;b&gt;Used for:&lt;/b&gt; Cauldron Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="07A9DA38">{0.SimFirstName} knows this spell already.</Text>
  <Text Key="259DA79F">The concepts in this tome are too simple for {0.SimFirstName}.</Text>
  <Text Key="082C53D6">{0.SimFirstName} knows this potion already.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DD0BC45">Hexed Potion of Forced Friendship</Text>
  <Text Key="356FC94B">(From Potion of Forced Friendship)</Text>
  <Text Key="40D23F3B">Hexed Potion of Plentiful Needs</Text>
  <Text Key="CFF70B6C">(From Potion of Masterful Insults)</Text>
  <Text Key="E541D9F7">Hexed Potion of Masterful Insults</Text>
  <Text Key="50BB967D">Hexed Potion of Immortality</Text>
  <Text Key="9543A379">Hexed Potion of Rejuvenation</Text>
  <Text Key="7952FA8B">(From Potion of Transcendent Charmer)</Text>
  <Text Key="5C90D507">Hexed Potion of the Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="9C9F6452">Hexed Potion of Good Fortune</Text>
  <Text Key="2F04CFA0">Hexed Potion of Magical Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="8FDC0573">Hexed Potion of Emotional Stability</Text>
  <Text Key="E0427983">Hexed Potion of Alluring Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="0B98A29E">Hexed Potion of Nausea</Text>
  <Text Key="D445EFDD">Hexed Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="2EBE8101">Hexed Potion of Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="D93A9D0C">(From the Potion of Perk Purging)</Text>
  <Text Key="DAE7F76B">Hexed Potion of the Nimble Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="AA4F3022">Hexed Potion of Prompt Resurrection</Text>
  <Text Key="24978A7F">Made By: Questionable Quacks Emporium</Text>
  <Text Key="EFB1A807">Normal</Text>
  <Text Key="741D33E1">Mandrake</Text>
  <Text Key="E3AC725B">First Harvest: 3 days\nAdditional Harvests: 2 days</Text>
  <Text Key="0BF9BAD8">First Harvest: 5 days\nAdditional Harvests: 3 days</Text>
  <Text Key="90CB7BDA">Valerian</Text>
  <Text Key="AD424B18">First Harvest: 3 days\nAdditional Harvests: 2 days</Text>
  <Text Key="990A7A09">First Harvest: 5 days\nAdditional Harvests: 3 days</Text>
  <Text Key="FA49B446">Collect 7 Magic Motes and turn them in to any of the 3 Sages in The Magic Realm to become a Spellcaster. Spellcasters with the Mote Hound perk can also eat them for some Spellcaster XP.</Text>
  <Text Key="6D143BB4">Magic Mote</Text>
  <Text Key="3EF73040">2 - Color Reveal</Text>
  <Text Key="B729A50D">4 - Done</Text>
  <Text Key="3CB811FD">5 - Half Full</Text>
  <Text Key="8409BA48">0 - Generic</Text>
  <Text Key="7F16EB72">Become a Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="68DE1EFB">First things first. You need to become a Spellcaster. Seek out the help of a Sage in The Magic Realm to learn about magic and eventually perform the Rite of Ascension.</Text>
  <Text Key="1814F65C">Travel to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="FF479219">The Magic Realm is hidden deep within a vortex of swirling magic. Search for the mystical portal in Glimmerbrook if you don't already know the spell that leads there.</Text>
  <Text Key="E6E44162">Learn a Spell</Text>
  <Text Key="B6D2144B">The Spellcaster's journey would not be complete without access to an arsenal of varied, potent spells. Search for Tomes in The Magic Realm or ask powerful Spellcasters to teach you their secrets. Good luck!</Text>
  <Text Key="08F4352E">Reach Spellcaster Rank 2 - Acolyte</Text>
  <Text Key="C595C6C7">Become an Acolyte by casting or practicing magic, creating and drinking potions, or dueling your way up the magical ranks.</Text>
  <Text Key="C0C9A839">Know 3 Different Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="2FBDD2DE">Knowledge is power. Continue your training by learning additional spells. Search for Tomes, practice on your own, or seek out training from powerful Sages and Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="1BDE1B40">Cast a Spell on Another Sim</Text>
  <Text Key="86194E9D">Find a willing (or unwilling) target and try out a spell on them.</Text>
  <Text Key="24E9AB14">Reach Spellcaster Rank 3 - Adept</Text>
  <Text Key="8C805C51">Become an Adept by continuing to cast or practice magic, creating and drinking potions, or dueling your way up the magical ranks.</Text>
  <Text Key="35E4771D">Win 3 Duels Against Other Spellcasteres</Text>
  <Text Key="53775232">Target 3 other Spellcasters for duels and be victorious!</Text>
  <Text Key="09C7A1E5">Know 5 Different Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="3A258ABA">Knowledge is power. Continue your training by learning additional spells. Search for Tomes, practice on your own, or seek out training from powerful Sages and Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="6E765A8F">Reach Spellcaster Rank 5 - Virtuoso</Text>
  <Text Key="C95481D0">You are on your way to the tippity top of the mountain. Continue doing what you've been doing. It's been working well up to this point.</Text>
  <Text Key="4EB7BB97">Know 10 Different Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="945AABD8">Knowledge is power. Continue your training by learning additional spells. Search for Tomes, practice on your own, or seek out training from powerful Sages and Spellcasters.</Text>
  <Text Key="ACDA944E">Learn a Potion Recipe</Text>
  <Text Key="F083A7A7">You can pick up a Cauldron any time and begin Experimenting to learn new recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="C5A3E43B">Own a Cauldron</Text>
  <Text Key="E7F269FC">Locate and place a cauldron on your lot from the build catalog.</Text>
  <Text Key="506FC7DA">Know 3 Different Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="D84C3783">Continue to experiment on the Cauldron or discover new ways to accumulate additional potion recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="C364A2E2">Know 5 Different Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="093B94CB">Continue to experiment on the Cauldron or discover new ways to accumulate additional potion recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="B0F78AE4">Brew 5 Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="C6D54041">Locate or place a cauldron to brew something up. If you are lacking recipes try experimenting on the cauldron, asking sages, or finding tomes.</Text>
  <Text Key="415670BD">Know 10 Different Potions</Text>
  <Text Key="7D7BFF92">Continue to experiment on the Cauldron or discover new ways to accumulate additional potion recipes.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E8C0A81">Cook</Text>
  <Text Key="3E8FB1EA">Familiars</Text>
  <Text Key="C04691D9">Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="55E1C0B1">Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="2E2891A8">Practice Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="CB952791">Magic Duel</Text>
  <Text Key="2635E98B">Challenge to Magic Duel at the Dueling Grounds</Text>
  <Text Key="4A30CED3">Spellcaster Cheats</Text>
  <Text Key="75D7D882">Another fine product from the Fae-Away line! Keep fairies from infesting your home with aesthetically pleasing pure iron railing solutions.</Text>
  <Text Key="51B5317D">Fae-Away Stair Rail</Text>
  <Text Key="17B98116">There is no cauldron available.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B75DB80">Potion of Forced Friendship</Text>
  <Text Key="393B558B">Brew Potion of Forced Friendship</Text>
  <Text Key="C8C25470">A potion that unlocks the power of friendly conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6A02E8A">Potion of Prompt Resurrection</Text>
  <Text Key="323BC335">Brew Potion of Prompt Resurrection</Text>
  <Text Key="D7AF4966">A Sim that drinks this potion will revive immediately if they die.</Text>
  <Text Key="913440B9">Potion of Plentiful Needs</Text>
  <Text Key="7D2DCA82">Brew Potion of Plentiful Needs</Text>
  <Text Key="5D6C8275">A potion to fulfill all of a Sim's needs.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F3E435E">Potion of Masterful Insults</Text>
  <Text Key="A1F50511">Brew Potion of Masterful Insults</Text>
  <Text Key="A1D1D202">A potion that unlocks that power of animosity.</Text>
  <Text Key="E1D020EB">Potion of Immortality</Text>
  <Text Key="6471CEC4">Brew Potion of Immortality</Text>
  <Text Key="7EF1DBB3">A potion to prevent death from old age.</Text>
  <Text Key="148D7CC3">Potion of Rejuvenation</Text>
  <Text Key="782AD6BC">Brew Potion of Rejuvenation</Text>
  <Text Key="4E6C196B">A potion to allow a sim to remain at their current age.</Text>
  <Text Key="23B61F36">Potion of the Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="F6B61B29">Brew Potion of the Transcendent Charmer</Text>
  <Text Key="DC90C5BA">A potion to unlock the power of romantic conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="E65E6531">Potion of Good Fortune</Text>
  <Text Key="4E5C7BFA">Brew Potion of Good Fortune</Text>
  <Text Key="665CBCAD">A potion to find helpful items while doing everyday activities.</Text>
  <Text Key="F89ED048">Potion of Magical Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="F9A8C4D3">Brew Potion of Magical Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="4642B5F8">A potion that will display a Sims magical aura.</Text>
  <Text Key="68FDF45D">Potion of Emotional Stability</Text>
  <Text Key="7507AEAE">Brew Potion of Emotional Stability</Text>
  <Text Key="426C11B1">A potion to remove unnecessary emotional baggage.</Text>
  <Text Key="A794C2BD">Potion of Alluring Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="D81AAE0E">Brew Potion of Alluring Aura</Text>
  <Text Key="89288451">A potion that makes those around the drinker more receptive to romantic conversation.</Text>
  <Text Key="77B7AADE">Potion of Nausea</Text>
  <Text Key="B2D75891">Brew Potion of Nausea</Text>
  <Text Key="E82DED82">A potion to annoy an enemy and turn their stomach.</Text>
  <Text Key="F6F975CB">Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="BAA51824">Brew Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="62FED853">A potion to remove all curses from a Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="49DDA743">Potion of Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="6B85E53C">Brew Potion of Perk Purging</Text>
  <Text Key="0A5B3FEB">A potion that allows a Spellcaster to choose different perks.</Text>
  <Text Key="BACCA4CD">Potion of the Nimble Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="0C7AEB7E">Brew Potion of the Nimble Mind</Text>
  <Text Key="C2C78C01">A potion that will increase the speed your Sims gain skills.</Text>
  <Text Key="44C7B27A">The quiet town of Glimmerbrook may have more to it than meets the eye...</Text>
  <Text Key="63013609">Glimmerbrook</Text>
  <Text Key="E928497D">The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="045A2BC0">The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="8C2AF3D8">Potion of Curse Cleansing</Text>
  <Text Key="2D5B4877">A potion to remove all curses from a Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="751A53DA">Master Mixer</Text>
  <Text Key="2BEB4DC9">As a Master Mixer, {0.SimFirstName} rarely fails when using potions on themselves.</Text>
  <Text Key="A62ED606">Slinger of Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="3B2965C5">As a Slinger of Spells, {0.SimFirstName} generates much less charge when casting spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="AF4E2D0E">Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="2FC29049">Darrel</Text>
  <Text Key="222E127F">Ernest</Text>
  <Text Key="0C396C86">Emilia</Text>
  <Text Key="6D4D4CBF">Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="0BACC746">Gemma</Text>
  <Text Key="CF450A39">Anansi</Text>
  <Text Key="F8A7059C">Grace</Text>
  <Text Key="433A7E2D">Faba</Text>
  <Text Key="D0154968">L.</Text>
  <Text Key="75A2EC34">Charm</Text>
  <Text Key="F9648EAB">Minerva</Text>
  <Text Key="1F746074">Ember</Text>
  <Text Key="DA18BD6B">Morgyn</Text>
  <Text Key="7B17A736">Silversweater</Text>
  <Text Key="91555C61">Simeon</Text>
  <Text Key="53D70DE2">Collette</Text>
  <Text Key="598F5645">Tomax</Text>
  <Text Key="DDD6D3F2">Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="B4D52D96">Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="59D50016">Sage of Mischief Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="803B6211">Sage of Practical Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="D73ADCCA">Sage of Untamed Magic</Text>
  <Text Key="9D5DF00F">Astral Projection Vendor</Text>
  <Text Key="8B5224BF">Frugal! {0.SimFirstName} saved ingredients while crafting {2.String}:\n{3.String} </Text>
  <Text Key="AD06901F">{0.SimFirstName} is a Spellcaster Neophyte</Text>
  <Text Key="202A751C">{0.SimFirstName} is a Spellcaster Acolyte</Text>
  <Text Key="878CD969">{0.SimFirstName} is a Spellcaster Adept</Text>
  <Text Key="1D68F77E">{0.SimFirstName} is a Spellcaster Master</Text>
  <Text Key="00D28E23">{0.SimFirstName} is a Spellcaster Virtuoso</Text>
  <Text Key="13522B8B">{1.SimFirstName} must be on solid ground to use this spell.</Text>
  <Text Key="C8BB4ABF">This Sage has recently taught you a spell. Come back later to learn more Spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="0B20E74C">You cannot learn any new spells from this Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="40F701F3">Make a Sim appear repulsive to everyone around them.</Text>
  <Text Key="ED2BA998">Strangeify</Text>
  <Text Key="213F99F0">Change Appearance spell</Text>
  <Text Key="BC2D1C8A">Make something (or someone) squeaky clean.</Text>
  <Text Key="E440BAA3">Scruberoo</Text>
  <Text Key="5E08702D">Clean spell</Text>
  <Text Key="AEDE16CC">Create a perfect replica of yourself, for a time.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9E0D929">Duplicato</Text>
  <Text Key="7470981B">Clone self spell</Text>
  <Text Key="4086E122">Reach into a Sim's head and scramble their thoughts.</Text>
  <Text Key="08F7D64B">Deliriate</Text>
  <Text Key="F648FD65">Confusion Spell</Text>
  <Text Key="7E754743">Restore a ghost to their original physical form.</Text>
  <Text Key="04275108">Dedeathify</Text>
  <Text Key="0B5AA1A0">Convert ghost tooltip</Text>
  <Text Key="1DD2C9E2">Bestow the gift of magic to another Sim.</Text>
  <Text Key="3AD00B0B">Rite of Ascension</Text>
  <Text Key="E1057625">Convert Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="12C58AB2">Turn one small object into many.</Text>
  <Text Key="A3BCCE3B">Copypasto</Text>
  <Text Key="645CF155">Duplicate object spell tooltip (I copy pasto'd this.)</Text>
  <Text Key="4E118D77">Convince two Sims to argue and fight with each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="B582B974">Furio</Text>
  <Text Key="CF270F84">Fight spell</Text>
  <Text Key="C6CB3CB9">Instantly incinerate your target with the power of fire.</Text>
  <Text Key="F94D7FDA">Inferniate</Text>
  <Text Key="E6015602">Is this burning an eternal flame?</Text>
  <Text Key="62DF5678">Fix a broken object, or make crafted objects higher quality.</Text>
  <Text Key="173B1FBD">Repairio</Text>
  <Text Key="7BA49857">Fix-it Felix</Text>
  <Text Key="A2051DB9">Create a tasty meal out of thin air.</Text>
  <Text Key="666352DA">Delicioso</Text>
  <Text Key="AFEF2702">Feed me</Text>
  <Text Key="23582078">Create a blast of cold air that freezes anyone it touches.</Text>
  <Text Key="68D75DBD">Chillio</Text>
  <Text Key="57C4C257">Chill out, man.</Text>
  <Text Key="4341FB1C">Keep your plants healthy and bug free.</Text>
  <Text Key="96285B99">Floralorial</Text>
  <Text Key="24C466CB">Green thumbs up!</Text>
  <Text Key="5780645D">Create a fully grown plant in even the most fallow of soils.</Text>
  <Text Key="5936B396">Herbio</Text>
  <Text Key="9B0F8CE6">Let it grow, let it grow...</Text>
  <Text Key="4ECDDC43">Harness electrical energy and give something a jolt.</Text>
  <Text Key="B9330008">Zipzap</Text>
  <Text Key="7B23E6A0">Pika pika?</Text>
  <Text Key="271F81F5">Convince two Sims to get romantic with each other.</Text>
  <Text Key="48C2D21E">Infatuate</Text>
  <Text Key="2763F9DE">Will you still love me tomorrow?</Text>
  <Text Key="FF4305C6">Control another Sim's mind and bend them to your will.</Text>
  <Text Key="41DCBB07">Minionize</Text>
  <Text Key="059118E9">BANANA!</Text>
  <Text Key="138FCC83">Free yourself from the effects of a magical curse.</Text>
  <Text Key="38B97248">Decursify</Text>
  <Text Key="FB23E1E0">Curse-B-Gone</Text>
  <Text Key="E84553C3">Despairio</Text>
  <Text Key="F8CB754F">Fill a Sim's mind with feelings of intense sadness.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCF86373">Sadness spell</Text>
  <Text Key="A51F4FD8">Acquire something that doesn't belong to you.</Text>
  <Text Key="DF7B1D9D">Burgliate</Text>
  <Text Key="866CF9B7">Rubble rubble!</Text>
  <Text Key="C66BF897">Summon the dead from their final resting place.</Text>
  <Text Key="514D7E94">Necrocall</Text>
  <Text Key="93D05824">Summon ghost</Text>
  <Text Key="76013A28">Move instantly to another location, regardless of distance.</Text>
  <Text Key="7FF5448D">Transportalate</Text>
  <Text Key="7ACF9D27">Teleporting may have side effects, call your doctor if you experience nausea, diarrhea, or loss of eye sight.  Do not teleport if your name is Reginald Barclay.</Text>
  <Text Key="D9A79C41">Transform a hapless Sim into an inanimate object.</Text>
  <Text Key="32C901D2">Morphiate</Text>
  <Text Key="409CB9AA">Presto change-o!</Text>
  <Text Key="A354FC0E">Return to The Magic Realm.</Text>
  <Text Key="C2DEAF5F">Homewardial</Text>
  <Text Key="DEC90BD1">Opens a portal to The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="E4162773">Bind Pet as Familiar</Text>
  <Text Key="201D7BA9">(From the Curse of Repulsiveness)</Text>
  <Text Key="5EC55331">Dangerously Overcharged - Final stage of charge. Great power and magic ability. Great chance of failures, backfires, and Curses. Also, chance of Death by Overload. Magic carefully!</Text>
  <Text Key="8FCA2C54">(From Spellcaster Charge)</Text>
  <Text Key="193C7E07">Charged - Spellcasting is more powerful but success chance is lightly decreased. There's also the possibility of becoming Cursed!</Text>
  <Text Key="3AF2B67A">Overcharged - Magic is even more powerful. Success chance is moderately decreased. Curse chances are increased</Text>
  <Text Key="77FDC12B">Regular - In this range all magic behaves normal. No additional benefits or dangers.</Text>
  <Text Key="4F054527">Spellcaster Charge</Text>
  <Text Key="776DFB86">Curse Ranked Stat (Unused)</Text>
  <Text Key="EC21000D">Casting spells and performing magic is becoming second nature. Your skill and power is growing by leaps and bounds. You are able to train less experienced Spellcasters in the magical arts.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE4163F5">In addition to practicing magic you are now able to Ask more experienced, friendly Spellcasters for Magical Training. Potion crafting, spellcasting, and magical studying continues to grant knowledge.</Text>
  <Text Key="2A6264F1">You are able to better control and shape your magical energies by casting Build Charge. This will raise Spellcasting Charge and allow easy access to more powerful spellcasting. Be cautious.</Text>
  <Text Key="5BF76CBE">Your prowess in the magical arts is gaining recognition. A Magical Care Package is sent to every Acolyte containing some everyday essentials for an up-and-coming Spellcaster. Be sure to check your mailbox!</Text>
  <Text Key="28CCAB9D">The spark of magic begins to flow and swirl. Practice Magic, learn and make new potions on the Cauldron, cast spells and search for Tomes to gain experience.</Text>
  <Text Key="6B897DD1">You have become one of the most powerful Spellcasters in all the lands in all the worlds. You may continue to train and overmax your knowledge to gain additional talent points.</Text>
  <Text Key="F1432ECC">Virtuoso</Text>
  <Text Key="B9F182E8">Adept</Text>
  <Text Key="9D47C9BD">Apprentice</Text>
  <Text Key="6E41F7FD">Master</Text>
  <Text Key="349E2934">Acolyte</Text>
  <Text Key="81973407">Neophyte</Text>
  <Text Key="99827A43">Slinger of Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="14A4FB99">Slinger of Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="7789E8DE">A Slinger of Spells generates much less charge when casting spells.</Text>
  <Text Key="355025B9">(From Completing the Spellcraft &amp; Sorcery Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="875C79FD">Master Mixer</Text>
  <Text Key="CC3C18C3">Master Mixer</Text>
  <Text Key="2586822C">A Master Mixer rarely fails when using potions on themselves.</Text>
  <Text Key="C7B05697">(From Purveyor of Potions Aspiration)</Text>
  <Text Key="D07BEDF7">Immortal</Text>
  <Text Key="465817D5">Immortal</Text>
  <Text Key="3A7464CA">{0.SimFirstName} is immune from dying of old age.</Text>
  <Text Key="8617D40F">Curse of Uncontrollable Charge</Text>
  <Text Key="7FB2C08D">Curse of Uncontrollable Charge</Text>
  <Text Key="4C83B412">You now draw too much Magical Energy. All gains are increased.</Text>
  <Text Key="04B0F709">Curse of the Duelist</Text>
  <Text Key="7E0B7AA7">Curse of the Duelist</Text>
  <Text Key="C9848A90">Be prepared to get into more duels! It's going to be a lot harder to win, and rewards won't be as good.</Text>
  <Text Key="8153B968">Curse of Infectious Laughter</Text>
  <Text Key="9CE99470">Curse of Infectious Laughter</Text>
  <Text Key="54389007">Sometimes you just can't stop laughing; even in inappropriate situations and often times spread it to others.</Text>
  <Text Key="CC8DF0D1">Curse of the Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="E94BECCF">Curse of the Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="15DB82A8">A Spectral Stalker is hunting you. But where are they now?! Good luck trying to sleep.</Text>
  <Text Key="DE2F3DA0">Curse of Unwarranted Hostility</Text>
  <Text Key="20CAFC28">Curse of Unwarranted Hostility</Text>
  <Text Key="672DDA0F">For some reason everyone just wants to be mean to you and even start fights with you.</Text>
  <Text Key="9B68067B">Curse of Repulsiveness</Text>
  <Text Key="1B1B35B1">Curse of Repulsiveness</Text>
  <Text Key="91999446">What a horrifying visage! This will cause terror and disgust in all nearby Sims. Socializing will be much harder.</Text>
  <Text Key="370FB8DF">Curse of Uncleansable Stench</Text>
  <Text Key="7F5719BD">Curse of Uncleansable Stench</Text>
  <Text Key="D1CA8B02">You are eternally drenched in the smelliest of gym sweat constantly. Showering does nothing!</Text>
  <Text Key="F8838838">Curse of Awkward Embraces</Text>
  <Text Key="10A89FE0">Curse of Awkward Embraces</Text>
  <Text Key="410D36B7">You're just really into hugging and touching others now. It's too hard to resist. Awkward.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB86C386">Curse of Scrambled Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="D892038E">Curse of Scrambled Spells</Text>
  <Text Key="A76766B9">You're losing control of your magic. Casting will sometimes have random powerful results.</Text>
  <Text Key="65DA2204">Ghastly Consequences</Text>
  <Text Key="A8B8C014">Ghastly Consequences</Text>
  <Text Key="F666582B">The pursuit of immortality is full of failures and accidents. Luckily, it looks like this will pass in a while. Try to enjoy your phantasmal existence while you can.</Text>
  <Text Key="61D2C0D8">Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="C4E78580">Night Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="A9B93983">Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="CA2348D9">Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="A55FD3AE">Ancient Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="2F4C8736">Ancient Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="170A8131">At least one of this Sim's parents had a Strong or Ancient Bloodline trait. Sims with the Ancient Bloodline trait gain an additional talent point at each Spellcaster rank to spend towards perks. They also gain Spellcaster experience faster and reduce the chance of overloading by 50%.</Text>
  <Text Key="0DAE4B35">Strong Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="4A209DDB">Strong Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="42160D94">At least one of this Sim's parents had a Weak Bloodline trait. Sims with the Strong Bloodline trait gain an additional talent point at each Spellcaster rank to spend towards perks. They also gain Spellcaster experience faster and reduce the chance of overloading by 20%.</Text>
  <Text Key="1B8C3510">Weak Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="645DDEF8">Weak Bloodline</Text>
  <Text Key="46FEC1DF">This Sim's parents had no Bloodline traits. Sims with the Weak Bloodline trait gain an additional talent point at each Spellcaster rank to spend towards perks. They also gain Spellcaster experience faster and reduce the chance of overloading by 10%.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A96197C">Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="DD36722C">Spellcaster</Text>
  <Text Key="6BF0E18A">Talent Points: &lt;span class="balance"&gt;{0.OccultPoints}&lt;/span&gt;</Text>
  <Text Key="9AEA8432">Perks contain a variety of helpful ways to increase magical prowess. As one gains more experience and titles they also gain Talent Points. Invest wisely. Your Spellcaster rank determines what perks are available. Perks attached with a line must be purchased in order from the bottom.</Text>
  <Text Key="DAE1B01C">Talent Points:</Text>
  <Text Key="7BF68AA6">Deselect current Perk and return {0.OccultPoints} to wallet.</Text>
  <Text Key="EBCF139E">Select perks to purchase before continuing.</Text>
  <Text Key="F2171CCB">Spend hard earned Talent Points to acquire new magical advantages</Text>
  <Text Key="E259AB6B">Spellcaster Perks</Text>
  <Text Key="761FC85D">There are tomes to find, come to The Magic Realm!</Text>
  <Text Key="029B557F">The Magic Realm</Text>
  <Text Key="2432F68F">The Magic HQ is home to the three sages of magic. Each of them are the most powerful Spellcasters in their respective styles. These sages are sworn protectors of The Magic Realm. Together they are the only thing preventing The Magic realm from collapsing in on itself.</Text>
  <Text Key="0F9D46B9">Venerable Brick</Text>
  <Text Key="C3BC78AD">Magnificent Brick</Text>
  <Text Key="D1BF2FE4">Enchanting Dainty Daisy</Text>
  <Text Key="AC0A0EA9">Spellbinding Tile</Text>
</STBLKeyStringList>